Tsunade-sama!
There's a message from the Fire Temple!
The four hidden tombs have been raided!
They got us.
What's the current situation?
Team Kakashi is heading toward the scene now!
I see.
Yamato reported that the enemies may be more than your
usual grave robbers, and looks like he was right on the money.
So, the thieves were really after...
The physical corpses of the shinobi from the Twelve Ninja Guardians.
Combined with our other recent problems, this has me worried.
We have to deal with Akatsuki being on the move,
and Orochimaru has kept his whereabouts hidden.
And also...
You're concerned about Danzou, too?
Yes.
We wanted to leave Sai in Team Kakashi anyway, but I can't
shake the feeling that he's got something up his sleeve.
I agree that we've got plenty to be concerned about.
But when the seeds of chaos sprout, you have to pick the plants.
We deal with things within our reach.
Then...
Shizune, have those who aren't connected to
Root start monitoring Danzou immediately!
Yes, sir!
I have a request.
A request?
Yes.
May I remain in Team Kakashi for a while longer?
That smile...
Tsunade, what the hell are you plotting?
It doesn't matter. You're already in the palm of my hand.
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
must be expressed with words.
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
Habataitara
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
to that blue, blue sky
aoi aoi ano sora
A New Enemy
Isn't this the opposite direction from where the hidden tombs are?
The thieves are carrying heavy coffins, as well as the corpses inside.
With the Fire Temple at the center, only sheer cliffs
lie in the realms of Genbu, Seiryuu and Byakko.
(These are the Chinese astronomical deities of the north, east and west.)
So if they want to escape these woods,
the only route left is Suzaku, to the south!
(Chinese astronomical deity of the south.)
Got it!
I hate my powers.
But even so, I can't simply rid myself of them.
I need them to get revenge for my father's death... To kill his murderer...
Why do you keep staring at me like that?
Well, you... You said something about revenge, right?
Whoa, this is a killer view.
The enemies won't show their faces out here.
Probably not...
There's nowhere to hide or anything.
Naruto!
What?
Over there.
Sora, check it out! Look, look!
Shut up! I see them!
Those are definitely them.
There's no mistaking it. Those are the stolen coffins.
But, why are they moving them so carelessly?
It's like they want us to notice...
A trap?
If so, then their target is most likely...
We're gonna lose them if we don't do something!
Captain Yamato!
Chiriku-san, please stay here in case
we need to contact the Fire Temple.
Understood.
Naruto and Sora-kun, go straight.
Sakura and Sai, break left.
I'll back you up from the right.
Why am I with him?
Because I'm worried about leaving you by yourself.
Besides, Sora-kun looks pretty helpful.
That's right! "Cure venom with venom". I read that in a book.
Hey, wait!
I said wait up!
I don't need to be paired with a hired goon like you!
Shut up!
Captain Yamato decided this! We have no choice!
Then just shut your mouth and stay behind me!
This is the Fire Temple's problem!
Damn it...
Smart-mouthed little bitch...
Me first.
Bastard!
They fell for it.
If this is a trap, we have nothing to use as cover.
True, but neither do they.
We'd be able to see an attack coming from far away.
If their goal was to steal the corpses,
there's no reason for them to set a trap.
Why are they doing this?
I already told you!
Shut your mouth and stay behind me!
Sorry, I'm going ahead again!
Don't...
...get cocky!
Ouch...
Sora, knock it off al-!
What are you two doing?!
The coffins... They just went underground!
If this goon hadn't gotten in my way,
I could've recovered at least one of them.
You're the one who pulled my leg!
What?
This time, I'll give you your kaimyou!
Bring it! But you'd better choose yours first!
Both of you, knock it off!
This isn't the time for childish bickering!
Something's off.
Their presence has completely vanished.
Long time no see.
I've grown tired of waiting. It's time
for a new dawn in the Fire Country.
You guys don't have time to be dead.
One can never anticipate what luck and chance will bring them.
Or maybe you summoned us?
Fudou! Fuen! Fuuka!
Yes, sir!
I'm going to meet with him for a moment.
I want you to deal with the others.
Yes!
Here are the blueprints.
Follow them exactly.
This will be the masterpiece of the century!
It's absolutely perfect.
You think you're so great.
I'm the one who's doing the carving!
I don't care how great of a masterpiece it is,
until it's made real, it's nothing more than graffiti.
Don't you know?
With traditional woodblock prints, people only remember
the picture's designer, not the one who carved the wood.
What?!
People hate men who talk too much.
Hurry up and get started already.
If you don't, the former Ninja Guardian Furiido will strangle you.
Oh, how scary!
Well, do your thing, Fudou.
Yeah, I'm on it!
Doton, Uitenpen!
(Doton, Uitenpen: Earth Element, Wheel of Fortune!)
What's going on?
Sai!
Ninpou, Choujuu Giga!
This is...
They changed the landscape this much with an Earth technique?
Looks like a certain someone set off their trap.
This isn't the time for that-!
Sakura-chan!
Hey, wait!
They're trying to crush me while I'm stuck down here.
I doubt they'll give me time to get out.
All right, then...
Mokuton no Jutsu!
Their trap covered such a large area...
Right, then you got split up from Sai.
And I noticed Captain Yamato was gone, too.
They're powerful enemies for them to be able to manipulate
such a massive amount of land with Earth techniques.
Anyway, we have to hurry and find the others!
Hey!
Wasn't there a valley here?
What the-?!
Where'd that come from?
Is it an illusion?
It has to be a trap.
Only one way to find out!
Wait, Naruto!
Don't just waltz up to it!
It's okay!
It looks like the ground's real, at least.
I bet they're just stupid and were in
such a rush to make this that they forgot-
Naruto!
Boy, he sure fell for that easily.
We have to hurry and look for him-
I need to get an aerial view of the terrain.
They won't let me out?
You won't be able to escape my masterpiece
with a simple technique like that.
Though I'm surprised that you were able to survive.
I mean, my technique was absolutely perfect.
I guess Fuen's blueprint wasn't aggressive enough.
Impossible... Wood Element?!
Who the hell are you?!
I could ask you the same thing!
What are you going to do with the corpses you stole?
Why do you care? You're about to become a corpse yourself.
Then I'll make you tell me!
You wanna test your powers against mine?
What a waste of time.
Doton, Ari Jigoku!
(Doton, Ari Jigoku: Earth Element, Ant Hell)
I beat you in a second, wood-user!
It's kind of a waste to kill you, though.
What a pain.
I guess I need to make this a close-ranged fight.
You need to do more than just dodge when you're up against me.
Where are we?
I don't know.
Where's Naruto?
He should have fallen into the same area, but I can't sense him at all.
We have to go look for him.
It looks like the enemy wants to split us up.
Ow, ow, ow...
Where are Sakura-chan and the others?
Another fork in the road?
Let's try this way.
Like I'm gonna fall again!
That must mean this is the right way!
Not exactly.
I'm not gonna get killed by some lame trap!
Man, I almost got squashed!
Fuen's traps aren't terribly imaginative, are they?
Kodomo no koro mita niji wo
If I look up now for the rainbow I saw as a boy,
ima miageru to nana iro de wa naku
there are no longer the seven colors,
Yagate kiri ga kakari
only mist and fog...
Jikan wa sugi kawatte yuku
As time passes by, and the world around me changes,
Kimi wo sagashitemo doko ni mo inai
no matter where I search for you, you're nowhere to be found.
Me wo toji, kokoro hiraite
So I close my eyes, and open my heart...
mata nagamete mitemo nanimo kawaranai no ka
I need to know, if I gaze up again,
tashikamete mitai
will things be different this time?
Sunao ni narereba kono kiri ga hareru to
Maybe if I was more honest, the fog would fade away.
kokoro ni negai sou sakenderu
So I pray, screaming that wish deep within my soul.
Nanika wo nakushiteshimatta koto de sou
When you lose one thing,
te ni shita mono mo kitto arun darou
you gain another, don't you?
Dakedo mada bokura wa otona ni tomadoi
But still, no matter how often the adults confuse us,
ikite yuku sube sagashiteru
we'll keep looking for the right way to live our lives.
Next Episode
Dear me.
I can't believe our team was separated so easily.
But what are these guys after?
There are plenty of other ways to steal the Twelve Ninja
Guardians' corpses that wouldn't have stood out nearly as much.
Could they really be after someone in our team?!
It never hurts to be cautious, but I'm
starting to get a bad feeling about this!
We have to get together again as quickly as possible!
Next time: Wheel of Fortune!
Wheel of Fortune
ANBU Investigation Report
ANBU Investigation Report.
Danzou' s
Plot
Danzou's Plot.
Danzou is one of Konoha's most powerful military leaders.
He was the founder of the currently
abolished ANBU secret corps called Root.
But even after losing his position,
his opinion still holds great weight.
He hasn't made any moves in the open
since his plot to assassinate Sasuke failed,
but Tsunade-sama has decided to keep constant surveillance on
him so that we can prevent a repeat of what happened in the past.
I'm still a little nervous about the
idea of leaving Sai in Team Kakashi.
Sai was an excellent student from
Root and was highly praised by Danzou.
I doubt that Danzou would just let him go his own way.
If there's a reason why he's still with us, then it's either so
he can keep an eye on Naruto, who is a Jinchuuriki, or to...
Unfortunately, I can't say that Sai
won't work for Danzou ever again.
So, it looks like I won't be able to take it easy for a while!
Plot
Danzou' s
Continue
Investigating
Danzou' s
Continue
Investigating
Danzou' s
Continue
Investigating