I finally know why I've had a sense of foreboding this whole time.
Considering what Sora said about the kings,
there's no doubt about it.
Someone new is trying to carry out the plans for the coup d'etat!
Maximum power.
Crap, we're surrounded?
But what's all this?
There's so many of them!
And something about them...
...isn't normal!
You guys are late!
Genma-san, what's going on here?!
We're about to find out.
Ino, you serve as back-up for the medics.
We're counting on you!
Yes!
That tattoo...
That's the Kohaku Clan's!
What? The Kohaku Clan?
A shinobi clan that was massacred near the Fire Country's border,
and one of many villages that have been attacked as of late.
We went to check on the other villages,
but almost everyone was killed in that one night.
Our fellow countrymen...
This is unforgivable!
So all of these people were the ones who were killed?
They were probably brought back with a revival technique.
So now they're merely weapons to attack us?
Just how many villages did they attack?
This is horrible!
Forgive me!
Damn it!
Oh no!
Furido, it's time.
Yeah. The fireworks made quite a show, didn't they?
The preparations for the four are just about finished.
Same for Sora...
We will serve as their back-ups, just as planned.
Yes.
Let's go!
Scatter!
Kitane, Nauma, Tou'u, Seito...
They're planning to use that same technique on them!
This is bad!
Uncle Asuma!
Konohamaru, what the hell are you doing?!
We're currently under a Level One state of emergency!
We know!
We're going to help evacuate the children!
I see.
Well then, here's another mission for you.
Tell anyone you see who's chuunin level or higher to come to the power plant!
What's wrong?
The village is in danger.
They're going to kill everyone...?
That's-!
Sora!
Stop!
This is...
What?
Th-This can't be...
It's...
...not just a technique. They really brought you back to life...
Seito, Tou'u, Nauma...
Kitane...
Asuma...
Asuma, is that you?
I see. It's you, right?
Is this your village?
Kitane...
Everyone, I'm sorry.
Please, go back to sleep. Go back to your world.
Sleep? World?
We're dead men. We have no such things.
But, since we've been revived, we have to do what we have to do.
What you have to do?
I said wait!
Wh-What the hell happened, Sora?
What happened between you and Asuma-sensei?
Let me go, damn it!
Sora, you really don't believe that Asuma-sensei killed your dad, do you?!
You heard him, didn't you?!
He admitted it! He said it himself!
He betrayed my father and killed him!
There's no way Asuma-sensei would do something like that!
Even if the Hokage ordered it?
The Third Hokage was Asuma's father!
What are you trying to say?
I'm saying that my father was killed by Konoha's king!
The Fire Country doesn't need two kings!
As long as there are two of them, there will always be war and strife!
My father worked to ensure there'd be only one king.
And all he got for his efforts was a cruel, tragic end.
For the sake of Asuma, who chose the other king...
The other king?
He was ordered by the Hokage to assassinate my father.
The Hokage's orders are absolute, no matter how you feel personally.
That's why my father tried to destroy of that king...
That's not a reason to attack Granny Tsunade!
I'm such an idiot.
The man who killed my father told me that he died honorably,
and I was happy to hear it.
I'm glad you told me about that, Mister Asuma!
You don't have to get revenge.
Getting vengeance will only taint your father's legacy.
I tried to think about it like that.
But still...
Sora...
I'm sorry, I just can't see the Third making Asuma-sensei do something like that!
How can you say that?!
I...
Same goes for you!
Why do you keep saying it's true?
Besides, Asuma-sensei didn't know about you wanting your dad's revenge, right?
So, who told you?!
That doesn't matter!
You...
Are you in league with the guys behind this attack?
Are you trying to wipe out Konoha?
No, I didn't know anything about it!
He wasn't supposed to go that far!
He?
This fight will result in the loss of Konoha's king.
It was only supposed to be the king and Asuma!
Then what is this, then?!
That's what I'm going to find out!
I understand your loneliness.
I know how it feels.
This is the first time I've seriously felt like I wanted to be your friend.
Who will you believe?
Us, or...?
Wait, Sora!
Hello again, little boy.
You again...
I'll be your opponent.
This time, I'll be sure to steal a long kiss from you.
Guys...
Sorry, Asuma. We don't have time for a trip down memory lane.
You can't be planning to use Limelight?!
Tou'u!
Seito!
Nauma!
I won't let you interfere!
Kitane...
It can't be helped.
Since we've been revived, we can't disobey our summoner's orders.
Even if you were once my friend, I'll kill anyone who interferes!
Come on!
You've grown old, Asuma!
Asuma-senpai!
Asuma-sensei!
We saw Konohamaru-kun.
Who's he?
Kitane, a former Guardian Ninja and the man inside one of the caskets you were chasing.
Are you serious?
The other three have been revived as well.
A resurrection technique?
They can use techniques of that level?
Where are the other three?
They've headed east, west and south in the village.
Why did they split up?
Those four were the ultimate lightning-element users.
They're planning to use Limelight, a technique regarded as the greatest lightning-element technique in history.
What is Limelight?
Four people enclose an area from the four cardinal directions,
and reduce it to ash in an instant.
Once they've reached their positions,
the village will be destroyed.
No way...
What do we do?
Don't let the other three reach their destinations!
If we can stop even one, the technique won't work!
Go, Yamato, Sakura!
I'll handle things here.
You two take care of the other three!
Understood!
Now that I've said all of that, I have to give this my all.
You were always like that.
Even when you had no chance of winning, you never held back one bit.
Kitane, you planned everything so carefully, and this still happened.
Yeah. But like I said, I have no choice.
I can't go against the summoner's orders.
Die, Asuma!
Suiton, Ja no Kuchi!
(Suiton, Ja no Kuchi: Water Element, Snake's Mouth)
Now she's using water?
That's right!
She has all five element types.
Crap! After water, she always uses-!
Yes. Now for lightning.
What the heck's going on?!
Is our backup here yet?
Quit your whining, guys.
We have to deal with this ourselves.
That's right!
We are Konoha Shinobi!
I won't let you give up!
Say that all you like, but there's no end to these things!
We have to defeat the person controlling them!
At this rate, the entire village is going to be flooded with corpses.
They just keep on coming!
Seriously!
And what the hell is Shikamaru doing?!
We need him to figure out how to deal with this situation!
I've got a bad feeling about this.
After looking at the data we've collected, it's safe to say that the enemy is able to freely pass through the barrier.
So what was their motivation for leading such a massive attack on the Main Gate?
In other words, it was a diversion.
Most likely, they've got another team somewhere else making their big move.
We're in trouble!
The village is gonna get burned to a crisp!
That's him.
The same technique again.
That's right. I'm surprised you're still alive.
Too bad for you.
Yeah, I'll make sure to kill you this time!
This is...
Oh, no! I was so looking forward to seeing that boy again.
I hate little girls!
Ick! Cold shivers just ran down my spine!
She irks me.
Everyone's going to be burned to a crisp anyway.
Wanna die before them, boy?
Raiton, Jibashi!
Time for me to steal my kiss.
What's holding you back, Asuma?!
Weren't you going to stop me?
If you don't take this seriously, both you and your village will be destroyed.
Just try to stop me, Asuma!
Die!
Where are you?! Get out here!
I want to talk to you!
I'm up here.
Hey!
Furido, I need to ask you something.
Hang on a second.
Take a look at Konoha village.
Don't you love those shining lights?
Those lights...
Yeah. When those four bolts come together, Konoha will be eradicated.
Then you're really trying to destroy Konoha?!
Yeah.
With light...
With light, we will burn Konoha to the ground.