If I focus on the Rasengan, my nature manipulation suffers.
And if I focus on nature manipulation, I lose the Rasengan's form.
This is pathetic.
You're the only shinobi in the world who can surpass the Fourth. That's what I believe.
Kakashi-sensei had such high expectations for me...
And I'm not meeting them at all...
What should we do? Take a quick break?
Only if he wants to.
I...
Damn it!
I don't have time to nap!
Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Guys, watch out!
One of us is going Kyuubi!
Captain Yamato, help!
Tenzou, it's happening again!
Damn it!
You okay?
You've been trying to combine nature manipulation with Rasengan all day,
with about 200 shadow clones.
That the equivalent of 4800 hours of solo training, but it's still not enough.
But this training...
The chakra control's too difficult, so 200 clones is all I can handle!
It...
It feels like I'll never get there.
The Rasengan takes so much focus just by itself.
Now I have to do nature manipulation at the same time.
It's too hard.
You're being unusually whiny. It's not like you.
Is this really the Uzumaki Naruto I know so well?
Sai?
You'll catch a cold.
How's Naruto doing?
It looks like combining Rasengan with nature manipulation is much harder than he expected.
And Naruto's never been a quick study...
That's why Kakashi-sensei's having him learn by doing.
Yes.
It's training only Naruto can do.
One clone doubles the results.
100 clones give 100 times the results.
But...
Combining a technique with nature manipulation is a wall that can't be scaled through willpower and hard work alone.
Remember that Rasengan was originally developed by the Fourth Hokage himself.
Adding nature manipulation to such a high-level technique...
Naruto...
...might not be capable.
That's true.
Naruto's quite stupid.
A clumsy, boorish guy like Naruto trying to master the subtle, complex art of combining shape and nature manipulation?
Of course he's not capable.
And yet, Kakashi-sensei and Captain Yamato have stuck with him the whole time.
Even while the village has deployed squadrons to combat Akatsuki, they're here wasting time on this pointless exercise.
I can't fathom what the Hokage expects from an oaf like Naruto-
Say one more word and your face ends up like the tree.
What do you know about Naruto?!
Sure he's a clumsy, stupid, lunk-headed idiot!
But no one defies the odds like him!
He's saved us countless times!
Every time someone expects him to fail, he proves them wrong!
That's who Uzumaki Naruto is!
And you're his teammate, so don't forget it!
What're you smirking about?
Don't make me smack you!
Please, no.
I must say, these books have taught me so much.
The "Understanding the Feelings of Others" series?
"How words reveal someone's true feelings."
Sai, did you...?
I know you believe in Naruto.
And I know you'd never turn on him.
You...tricked me.
I mean, if he'd kept eating those disgusting mud-balls, there's no way he'd ever succeed.
Mud-balls?!
All I did was focus on nutrition over taste!
Go study how to keep your own feelings quiet before you try to understand other people!
Don't worry, Naruto will get it.
Sheesh...
Naruto, you can do it!
But this time, I just don't think I can.
You have to.
All right Kakashi-sensei, if you're looking to the right, and someone tells you to look left, can you do both at the same time?
That is impossible.
I see. So that's how it is?
Yeah, sure I can.
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Now I'm looking right...
...and left at the same time, see?
That's it!
He got something from that?
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Did you have to call us back just to seal the damn Two-Tails?
This will take about three days. Be prepared.
Three days? That's like, forever! We're out in the rain over here!
Hidan. Shut up.
I was like...a second away from killing all of those godless Konoha idiots.
I didn't even get a chance to tell them about Jashinism!
Konoha is far from godless. They view the generation before them as heavenly beings, and follow the Will of Fire.
Although you could say it's just another excuse to fight.
Are you making fun of me, bitch?!
No, I'm not trying to belittle your reason for fighting.
Remember, I'm in the same boat as you.
Your reasons don't matter at all.
Religion, ideals, resources, land, grudges, love or just because.
Any trivial thing that motivates people to action will eventually breed war.
The reason can be dealt with afterwards, but war will always happen...
...because all people truly want is to fight.
No one's listening to your long-winded bullshit.
I do things my way, for my own purposes.
I'm not gonna give all that up for your group.
Working with us means working for us.
If we achieve our goals, yours will be met that much faster.
Yeah, yeah, preach all you want.
Akatsuki's just being reduced to a get-rich-quick scheme.
You're just like Kakuzu. I hate people who fight for money more than anyone!
It's true that right now we have a pressing need for money.
However, Akatsuki's true plans have always lain elsewhere.
We merely need a vast amount of money to accomplish them.
Well, being the second newest member after Tobi,
I haven't had the chance to hear these amazing "true plans"!
Plotting behind my back...
Did I hurt your feelings?
Fine, I suppose it's time I told you.
Akatsuki's goals can be broken down into three steps.
The first is to amass money. The second is...
...to use the money to create the first true mercenary organization the shinobi world has ever seen.
Huh? That's the same thing the ninja villages do now.
You take a mission, complete it, and get paid.
You wanna be the leader of a tiny, ghetto village with no country to back it up?
That's retarded.
It's the exact opposite of a village allied with its country.
What?
Let's start with the basics.
Countries with large, powerful ninja villages get the bulk of their capital through the shinobi business.
By fighting battles both within and beyond their borders, these villages earn large amounts of money,
essentially acting as the foundation of the country's economy.
So, for these countries to remain financially stable, they need war.
But nowadays, most missions amount to small skirmishes. Large, destructive wars have all but disappeared.
As a result, many shinobi have lost their place as the countries continue cutting expenses.
Shinobi who lived only to fight...
They risked their lives for their nation, and were thanked by being abandoned.
The Five Great Countries are in no danger.
Both the countries themselves and their villages are well respected.
They have many clients, within the country and others past their border, but that doesn't work for the smaller ones.
It costs a lot to maintain a shinobi village, and those costs remain the same in both war and peacetime.
But if those smaller villages reduce their forces too drastically, they won't be able to survive if a war breaks out.
What Akatsuki is doing will change everything.
No allegiance to any country, mobilizing only when necessary, using our shinobi only when required.
We'll build up our forces through those small villages and countries, and create an army to bring war!
In the beginning, we'll fight any war for a minor cost, single-handedly gaining control of the war trade.
As word spreads, we'll start using the Bijuu to manufacture our own wars, ones as big or small as the market requires.
Before long...
...we'll have a monopoly on war.
The entire ninja village system will fail,
and the Five Great Countries will be forced to use Akatsuki.
Then, and only then, will we have achieved our true goal.
The third, and final step.
We will...
...control the world.
I see...
Um, about Kurenai-san...
You three notify everyone about the funeral.
I'll tell Kurenai myself-
No, I'll do it.
I'll tell her.
I have a message for her from Captain Asuma.
Yes!
Yeah, I think I'm getting it!
So that's what you meant.
Makes sense. You learned Rasengan by using a clone to take care of the shape manipulation while you released the chakra.
Yep! I just need a second clone to handle the wind nature manipulation!
I can't look left and right at the same time by myself,
but I can have two clones each look one way!
All you have to do is split the job up into smaller pieces!
So my little shadow clone stunt inspired this, huh?
That said, only Naruto has both the chakra and the skill with shadow clones for that method to work.
I couldn't do it like that. I bet even the Fourth couldn't. But this kid...
No less from Konoha's Number One Most Surprising Ninja, eh Naruto?
I gotta say...
I'm really starting to like you!
Don't say weird shit like that, you freak!
I finally got the technique and your creepy-talk threw me off!
I didn't mean it like that!
Back off!
You see, I, uh...
No!
What the heck are those two doing?
A message.
Just hold on-
What's up?
Kakashi-senpai, we have to stop training and return to the village right now.
What happened?
Sarutobi Asuma-san...
...has passed away.
You okay, Konohamaru?
U-Uncle Asuma... Why...?
Asuma...
Chouji, have you seen Shikamaru?
He still hasn't shown up here.
Weird. I went to his house, but his mom said he'd already left.
Where could he be at a time like this?
Next time: Team Ten.
How can you eat pure syrup?
Actually, should you be goofing off here?
If I leave, I'll just end up doing more errands.
Ah ha! I found you, Kotetsu!
Shit!
Tsunade-sama said to get back to work!
Please, let me go!
You're not going anywhere!
Please, just-
Damn it, wait-
I-Izumo?
You all right?
Kotetsu!
Oh, that'd be good.
And that's how I came up with the Syrup Snare Field.
You can find inspiration in the oddest places.
Make sure you stay focused at all times!
Can I go home now?