I really was young and naïve back then.
Thank you for escorting the Feudal Lord.
What's your problem?!
I protected the king, the Feudal Lord, as you ordered!
Why can't you be proud of me?
The king?
Why don't you acknowledge me for once, Dad?!
You don't understand...
...just how difficult and important the fight to protect the king is!
I know it causes deaths.
But making sacrifices are part of a shinobi's duty!
You don't get it at all.
What it really means to protect the king...
You just don't want to accept me!
Now, I think I finally understand what you meant.
I'm sorry for leaving Konoha and doing whatever I wanted.
Although I don't regret it, either.
And I don't regret being born into the Sarutobi clan.
You carried out your duty as the village leader.
You were a great dad.
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
must be expressed with words.
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
to that blue, blue sky
aoi aoi ano sora
The Approaching Menace
Our mission is to haul these timbers!
So let's get 'em there! Left, right, l-
What happened?
L-Let's take a break!
We're not cut out for this type of work...
You're both being lazy!
The village was saved, and the Fifth was unharmed.
But that's only because Naruto-niichan and everyone else helped out.
We have to help support the village by doing what we can, too!
Well said!
And you guys will be the ones to support Konoha in the future.
And Naruto played a big part in what happened this time, as well.
Iruka-sensei?
I'm so happy to have such wonderful students!
Konohamaru-kun, I'm okay now.
As long as we work together, we'll be fine, no matter what!
Next.
Next!
Yes!
Next.
Next!
You're slow!
What's wrong? Where's the next set of documents?
Um, well, that's all of them.
Really?
H-How rare...
You never get this serious about your work...
I guess.
So much commotion was caused by a handful of bandits?
Pathetic, Princess Tsunade.
Now that the surrounding nations and the Feudal Lord himself knows about this, Konoha's become a laughing stock!
Every single order you gave took far too long to issue!
Your indecisiveness nearly destroyed the village.
It's all your responsibility, as the Hokage!
Don't forget that!
Damn geezers, saying whatever they want!
They already had that little speech planned out despite the fact that the work's not even done.
Shit!
Ah, th-that's right!
A report from one of Jiraiya-sama's assets has arrived!
Oh? He's back?
If you sneak out of the hospital like that, you'll end up right back here.
This book says that your bonds will deepen if you go to help your friends in a pinch.
That's a manga.
You really take everything at face value when comes to this, don't you?
Here.
What?
I read that a kind girl will feed you in this type of situation.
Though it's not like I was testing you.
Jeez, I swear...
Sakura-chan...
Sakura-chan, I can't eat anymore...
I-If you want me to eat it that badly, I can't refuse...
Eat yourself to death!
Hey.
Sakura fed Naruto an apple. So that means...
Oh, come on! Why aren't there any normal people on my team?!
Huh? What? What's wrong?
I've confirmed there were seven battles in five neighboring countries with a two-man Shinobi team.
While they haven't crossed the Fire Country's borders yet,
judging from their path, it's only a matter of time before they try.
Tsunade-sama?
They're on the move.
Akatsuki!
Let's do it.
Hold up.
I gotta make sure I pray first.
You drive me nuts with this crap.
It annoys me, too, but the commandments are very clear!
You probably think you have me cornered, but you're wrong.
I lured you here!
Now that I know you two are from Akatsuki, I can't let you escape.
We're trapped, Kakuzu.
No problem. In fact, it works out better this way.
I swear by my name, Nii Yugito of the Hidden Cloud, that I will kill you!
Say what?
You'll kill me?
It really pisses me off when people scream out battle cries like that!
And when I get pissed, the blood starts rushing to my head, and when blood rushes to my head-
Shut up, Hidan.
Sorry, sorry.
But when blood rushes to my head, I stop caring about our objectives and start thinking "I'll obliterate everything!"
Settle down, Hidan. Our orders are absolute.
This mission really goes against my beliefs.
Slaughter is the core of the Jashin faith.
Leaving people half dead is a mortal sin.
I can't get motivated for missions that require me to go against the commandments.
I may not look it, but I'm very religious.
Basically, not killing you would suck, so can we just talk this over?
Talk it over...?
What's with this guy?
How about you just let us capture you?
Don't mess with me!
Huh? I guess that's a no.
How stupid can you be?
Whoa, whoa, for real?
What's up with this Jinchuuriki?
She's totally become the beast within her.
Shit!
Hot! I thought cats didn't like hot stuff.
So this's the Two-Tailed demon cat they call the 'Living Ghost'.
And I'm a rat in a cage over here.
That's kinda funny.
Sounds like a lot happened while I was gone.
Kakashi-sensei, where the heck were you?
Ah, you know.
Asuma-sensei!
So this is where you were.
Kakashi, can I have a minute?
I need to talk with you.
Naruto, Sai, these are for you.
I've had enough apples...
I heard you were checking up on the outside.
More or less.
Nice day today.
Yeah, sure is.
Naruto and Sakura are developing well.
The same goes for Shikamaru, Chouji and Ino.
The next generation is growing up.
Before we know it they'll leave us in the dust.
Hey, hey! It'll be a long time before they beat me!
But, it'll be a good thing for Konoha.
So?
What'd you wanna talk about?
Well, actually...
There you are.
I finally found you.
Kurenai? What's up?
I heard that Asuma was here.
So, Asuma, what did you want to discuss?
Uh, we'll talk about it some other time.
Sorry.
Now I really want to know...
What are you doing, Naruto?
There's no time to lie around sleeping.
I have to continue my training.
But you aren't...
I'm still too weak.
That's why...I have to develop a power that won't hurt everyone. That can protect them...
I have to become stronger to be able to do that.
Naruto...
Well, don't be in such a rush...
Right now your training is to heal up your injuries.
Kakashi-sensei!
Especially you, Naruto! I'm warning you.
The only thing waiting for you outside the hospital is severe training that could put you right back in here, or worse.
So make sure you're ready for it!
Okay... I get it...
That should be enough to get him to calm down.
Sakura!
Y-Yes?
I've got some stuff to take care of, so please handle things here.
Be sure not to push yourselves too much. Bye!
Jeez, he's always so aloof.
I read your report.
Is Naruto's new technique going to work out?
Well?
I don't know.
But-!
I'm not sure yet, but knowing him, he'll be able to do it.
That training format is improving the results.
And most importantly, he's focused on his goal.
Sasuke, huh?
It's been half an hour.
Are you done yet, Hidan?!
Fuck you! Don't mess with the ritual!
Ow.
You do this Jashin sacrifice thing every time.
Can't you skip it once in a while?
Let's just go and get the next one.
I don't like doing it either, but it's part of my religion, I have to!
And skip it? Skip it?
That's blasphemy against God!
We've still got one left.
We'll have to search thoroughly.
The Fire Country is next!
iijiina riyuu
It's so very easy
issai yurusu jakuhai
for youth to forgive everything
resukyuutai mo yondeoita
I called in the rescue squad
dakara
So please kiss me, please kiss me all night
puriizu kisu mi puriizu kisu mi
datenshi no mahou ka koakuma no chachina itazura
Is it a fallen angel's magic, or a mischievous monster's prank?
tsumaranakunacchau mae ni
Before we get bored
soore de houre
Let's let go
bouringubooru
Of that bowling ball. We lead such strange lives
ibutsu na sonzai daro
shouchi no suke
You've gotta understand
kowaresoude...
We're gonna smash it...
docchirakatta kanjou de kirihirake yo
Cut through the inner turmoil
kowaresou de
We're gonna break...
kowasenai bokura no shouri
I can't break it...our victory.
Next Episode
The next episode of Naruto Shippuuden is: Akatsuki's Invasion!
Chiriku fights against the Akatsuki, who have invaded the Fire Country!
Demons attack the Fire Temple with their terrible destructive abilities.
“Akatsuki” Invasion
I've heard we've learned some new things about the Bijuu.
Yes.
Of the nine Bijuu, Akatsuki has stolen four of them, including the One-Tail, Shukaku.
So nearly half of them.
Remaining are the other four, and Naruto's Kyuubi.
And the information regarding those other four?
It isn't solid information, but I've found out about one of the Jinchuuriki.
Information about Jinchuuriki is supposed to be highly classified national secrets.
Yes, but we've discovered some background information on one of them.
You have?
So, where is she?
She's in the Thunder Nation's Hidden Cloud Village. Her name is Nii Yugito.
Hidden Cloud Village... Nii Yugito...
Well done.
Get everyone you can to continue the investigation.
Okay, got it.
But we still don't know what Akatsuki is after.