Are you really going to kill all the villagers?
Yeah, every last one of them.
That's how the Fire Country will be reborn.
The king... Eliminating the other king, was that your...
No, was that my father's intention?
Why do people uninvolved in this have to die?!
They're not uninvolved.
Even if the king is eliminated, as long as there are people who still follow that king, the Fire Country can't be united.
You get what I'm saying?
Your father was killed by Asuma, who trusts the Hokage.
The problem isn't the king.
It's those who follow her.
As long as the followers remain, you can change the king countless times and it wouldn't matter.
That's where your father slipped up.
Slipped up?
The king isn't what should be eliminated.
It's the pawns!
By killing off the entire village, you ensure the king's downfall.
That's how you can truly unify the Fire Country.
Limelight.
When the four lightning sources gather, everything will be reduced to nothing.
And that's the moment our ambitions, our dreams, will be fulfilled.
Fuuka, Fuen, Fudou, protect their paths.
Protect the paths of Kitane, Nauma, Touou, Seita.
After the preparations are completed for Limelight, we're leaving the village.
And you're coming with us.
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
must be expressed with words.
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
Habataitara
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
aoi aoi ano sora
to that blue, blue sky
Multiple Death Matches
It seems to have something to do with that mountain of dirt.
Looks that way.
The dirt, and villagers buried in it, have been summoned from the village that was attacked several days ago.
And all the buried villagers are being revived one after the other via a resurrection technique, right?
You've got to be kidding me!
Just how many people did they kill?
Baika no Jutsu!
Arm!
There's no end to them!
There are too many!
At this rate, the village will be overrun with zombies!
The enemy corpse unit is currently multiplying in the vicinity of the Main Gate.
The back-up squads are doing all they can to keep them from entering the business district.
I see.
Please let me go to the battle, Fifth Hokage.
We won't get any leads from me wracking my brain here.
Besides, this doesn't suit me.
Very well.
I'll do what I can.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
You're looking kinda good there.
Brave little boy, I'll help you if you give me your body.
I ain't giving you shit!
Get bent, you old hag!
I see.
Hateful child!
Furido told me not to kill you, but...
Everyone makes mistakes, don't they?
Raiton, Hiraishin!
(Raiton, Hiraishin: Lightning Element, Flying Thunder God)
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
As expected, you're pretty stubborn.
I don't have time to waste here!
Then I'll finish this now!
Die!
Mokuton, Mokujouheki!
(Mokuton, Mokujouheki: Wood Element, Wooden Fortress)
Hiding like a rat!
Ah, that's right.
You're also an Earth element user.
Then let's see who's the more skilled one.
Doton: Doryuusou!
(Doton, Doryuusou: Earth Element, Rising Stone Spears)
Looks like my body's harder than your stones.
This is...
I need to get out of here.
Stop it!
You can't stop this, can you?
No, I can't.
I really liked you, you know.
Me, too.
Liked what?
You, of course.
And to think that I have to kill you.
Raiton, Kaminari Shibari!
(Raiton, Kaminari Shibari: Lightning Element, Thunder Binding)
Nah, I'll let you live after all.
I don't have any time to fight you, after all.
Kitane!
Wait!
Kitane...
They're almost there.
The appointed place for Limelight.
I can't.
This village...
I won't let you kill the villagers!
I hate Asuma.
But, this is different!
So you're just like your dad.
Damn you...
Sora, there's just no helping you.
This is what happens when you're nice to someone who's always been hated.
What did you say?!
Your dad was that way, too.
That naiveté ruined everything!
That naiveté ruined the Fire Country!
That naiveté of yours wants to keep the villagers here alive and only kill those whom you have a grudge against!
Am I wrong?!
Do you want to die like your dad did?!
Sakura-chan!
Naruto?
Sakura-chan, you're safe now.
And the enemy?
The wall was covered in moths...
...and they started to attack me.
You're okay now.
Sakura-chan, you had a pretty rough time, didn't you?
But, you can relax now.
I'll put you at ease!
Why are you running?
You don't have to run.
Hey, please die, Sakura-chan!
Now, now, Sakura-chan, quit running away from me!
Wait up!
I'll put you to ease!
Stop it!
At this rate, more people are just going to be injured.
We need to find a way to stop the source of the problem.
What's the situation like here, Ino?
Shikamaru!
She fell prey to the illusion created by that poison.
I wonder what type of dream she's having.
Well, a nightmare is more fitting for that brat.
Release!
Farewell, little lady.
Body replacement?!
Farewell, you sick freak!
Wh-Why?
My technique was...
I had a pretty good idea what was going to happen when I heard your voice.
Back in the maze, there was a poisonous spider.
And this time there were poisonous moths.
I ran some simulations based off of your fighting pattern.
You used an...antidote?!
Someone like you isn't meant for combat if you're not willing to step onto the battlefield.
It was clear who would win when I realized that!
What?
The defensive barrier is...
It's disappearing!
For the barrier to be falling apart, one of the other groups must have defeated the person who set it up.
But as long as these guys are still here,
our situation isn't going to change any.
Even so, we know that the other groups are working hard.
We have to do our best, too!
Well said, Chouji!
Shikamaru!
This is just a distraction. The enemy's after something elsewhere.
We need to hurry up and take care of things here so we can go help the other groups.
We knew that from the start!
Quit yapping and come up with a strategy!
Slave driver...
Chouji, you've got some chakra saved up, right?
Yeah, you bet! I'm good to go!
And everyone else?
I'm in the midst of hard-working youth!
I can't lose to you youngsters yet!
I was just thinking that I'd like to cut lose!
S-Same here, right?
Yeah...
Well then, let's go!
It's too soon to say bye-bye, boy!
Doton, Doro Houshi!
(Doton, Doro Houshi: Earth Element, Mud Indulgence)
Suiton, Ja no Kuchi!
(Suiton, Ja no Kuchi: Water Element, Mouth of Evil)
The mud will gain momentum from the water and form a mud slide.
Damn you!
Start fighting me for real already!
How long are you planning on just running around?
I wasn't just running around.
What?
I was just waiting for my preparations to be completed before attacking.
Suiton, Hahonryuu!
(Suiton, Hahonryuu: Water Element, Destructive Rapid Torrents)
He used Water?!
I should have figured you can use Water since you're able to use Wood.
But that wasn't enough to defeat me.
It made the ground nice and muddy.
With the sandy areas broken up like this,
it's easy for the ground to absorb the water.
Bastard! You were planning this from the start!
After all, there's no need for me to waste time on a mere Earth user.
Mokuton, Jubaku Eisou!
(Mokuton, Jubaku Eisou: Wood Element, Binding Nest)
What's this?!
Become part of Konoha's soil, Earth user.
Stop it!
Go, Chouji!
Baika no Jutsu!
Nikudan Sensha!
Next!
Here I go!
Konoha Daisenpuu!
Next!
Juujin Bunshin!
What...the hell?
iijiina riyuu
It's so very easy
issai yurusu jakuhai
for youth to forgive everything
resukyuutai mo yondeoita
I called in the rescue squad
dakara
So please kiss me, please kiss me all night
puriizu kisu mi puriizu kisu mi
datenshi no mahou ka koakuma no chachina itazura
Is it a fallen angel's magic, or a mischievous monster's prank?
tsumaranakunacchau mae ni
Before we get bored
soore de houre
Let's let go
bouringubooru
Of that bowling ball. We lead such strange lives
ibutsu na sonzai daro
shouchi no suke
You've gotta understand
kowaresoude...
We're gonna smash it...
docchirakatta kanjou de kirihirake yo
Cut through the inner turmoil
kowaresou de
We're gonna break...
kowasenai bokura no shouri
I can't break it...our victory.
Next Episode
Sora's secret is now being revealed.
He stands in a daze before his friends who are fighting.
What's that damned Furido up to?!
Naruto Shippuuden Special
It's a Naruto Shippuuden Special!
It'll air on Thursday, July 31st at 7:00 PM!
It will air July 31st at 7:00 PM!
I'm hungry!
Shikamaru, you got any food on you?
Sure don't, stupid.
I have some!
Then give me some, Chouji!
Okay!
So let me introduce you to my favorite snacks!
First is...
...pork hide flavored Karu B Potato Chips!
The flavor of pork hide oozing in your mouth is just great!
Next is the garlic tablets, Ninsuku!
It's filled with lots of garlic and even has the gentle scent of garlic to it!
This is truly a stamina tablet for fighters!
Next is the gum, Hormone!
No matter how much you chew it, the flavor never dies!
It reproduces the hormones that incite appetite! It's a gum above all gums!
And then there's Shokora Mayonnaise!
It's taken the popular spread and became famous...
Chouji, that's enough!
Huh?
Just listening to you is making me nauseous.
Same here.
Really? But it's so good!
True happiness!