Akatsuki has snuck into the country. The village of Konoha seeks to stop Hidan and Kakuzu from proceeding further.
With the information they received from the Fire Temple,
Team Asuma heads for the five black market exchange points.
Meanwhile, Naruto is struggling to create a new technique,
undertaking an unprecedented challenge that not even the Fourth Hokage could complete.
No fair!
Rasengan's my ultimate technique, but you can do it so easily?!
I had to endure crazy difficult training with Ero-sennin, you have no idea what I went through-
Um, this is just the starting point of what I wanted to tell-
And you can do it with one hand!
I always have to do it with clones...
I don't believe this.
Maybe I should give it another try...
We'll wait for him to calm down.
I didn't show you Rasengan just to brag about it.
Yeah, right.
I told you before that Rasengan is a technique that only uses shape manipulation, remember?
Shape manipulation?
Then I showed a technique that uses both shape and nature manipulation...
By which I mean...
Chidori.
You're just showing off again.
This technique not only uses nature manipulation to turn my chakra into lightning,
but also shape manipulation to transform it into an electrical surge, thereby determining its range and power.
Pay attention.
By using both shape and nature manipulation, a shinobi's attack power increases tenfold.
Although shinobi who can use both together are pretty rare.
I knew it, more bragging.
You're now able to use wind nature manipulation thanks to the previous bout of training.
And you've already reached the ultimate level of shape manipulation.
Wh-! Rasengan?
That's right.
So, that means I can use them both, right?
Yeah, pretty much.
All right!
I'll have my new technique in no time!
Yes! Yes, yes, yes!
I bet this'll be the easiest part!
If it was, I wouldn't have bothered creating Chidori.
I was never able to combine Rasengan with lightning-natured chakra.
You need incredible skill to combine nature and shape manipulation.
Though perhaps "innate ability" or "sense" would be more accurate.
I'm not the only one who had to stop here.
Even my teacher, who created this technique, couldn't get any further.
Teacher?
Yes. Even the Fourth Hokage couldn't do it.
The Fourth took shape manipulation to the highest possible level.
The result was Rasengan.
An A-Rank technique achieved purely through shape manipulation.
Up to that level, even I managed to copy it.
But that's also where things get difficult.
The Fourth originally developed Rasengan intending to combine it with his elemental chakra.
Then, you mean Rasengan's an incomplete technique?
That's a good way to put it.
There's no telling what the next step will produce. It would be S-Rank level, probably higher.
It may even be impossible.
This part can't be taught. It's something you have to figure out yourself.
Do... Do you know why I'm telling you all this, Naruto?
Because you're the only shinobi in the world who can surpass the Fourth. That's what I believe.
Well, let's kill the small talk and continue training after we eat, shall we?
Well done, Kakashi-san.
You really are a smooth talker.
Not really.
I was telling the truth.
Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
must be expressed with words.
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
aoi aoi ano sora
to that blue, blue sky
Collision Course! Akatsuki VS Team Asuma
The Naruto Shippuuden Special
Tsunade-sama!
There's a message from Team Asuma!
An exchange point?
It says those two Akatsuki members are heading towards one.
The closest exchange point to us...
We're right by it!
We're about to face Akatsuki...
It'll be fine, Ino. If we do what Asuma-sensei taught us, there's nothing to be afraid of.
Nah, just kidding.
But that's what Shikamaru said to me on our last mission.
Chouji...
Shikamaru's working hard. We've gotta give it our all, too.
Yo, Asuma-sensei...
What kinda relationship did you have with Chiriku?
Why do you ask?
Because you're a chain-smoker and you haven't had a puff in two whole days.
You only stop smoking when something's bothering you.
Man, you're good.
I must be getting soft if you can read me so easily.
Getting? I can read you like a book when we play shougi.
I haven't seen you like this since the Third passed away.
You know that Chiriku and I were both in the 12 Ninja Guardians, right?
Now that I think about it...
I'd say we were like you and Chouji.
In that case, I hope you never quit smoking.
Never quit, huh?
I probably never will, at this rate.
Shikamaru, I appreciate your concern,
but I didn't stop smoking because of Chiriku.
Now forget me, remember that these Akatsuki guys killed Chiriku.
That means they must have incredible abilities.
Stay focused!
Sit
Make Rasengan in groups of two.
And at the same time, apply wind nature manipulation to it.
I'm not going to tell you what to do here.
Naruto, it's up to you to come up with the method.
Now get started.
Okay!
Si
t
Add wind chakra...
Change it to wind nature!
But how do I do it when I'm concentrating on Rasengan's shape manipulation?
That's what I wanna know!
Shit!
Si
t
It's too much. He just cut the waterfall...
At times like this...
Um, I could just keep quiet,
but I'm going to be frank with you.
Those soldier pills are disgusting.
How can you say that?!
I prepared them so they'd be easily consumed.
Watch. I'll have one.
As I said...
Using the Mass Shadow Clones technique like that must be exhausting.
Crap...
C'mon!
Okay!
Now add wind chakra!
Damn it...
This is...impossible.
I have to concentrate hard enough when using Rasengan as it is.
And now I have to apply nature manipulation on top of that...
It's like trying to look left and right at the same time!
Damn it all...
I don't have time to complain!
Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Hey, where the hell are you going?
The bathroom?
Ugh... Fine, wait up.
This is the exchange point.
Why the fuck did they pick a bathroom?!
This way, please.
Here, please.
Make it quick, will you?
There's no mistaking it. That's Chiriku.
You caught yourself a big one, Kakuzu-san.
Yeah.
This place reeks!
Let's go already, Kakuzu!
Hang on. I need to count the money.
I can't tell whether the stench is the piss or that body, but seriously, it's fuckin' gross.
I'm going back outside!
We're almost to the exchange point!
We're almost there.
Stay on guard!
It's all there.
I look forward to your next capture, sir.
Don't hold your breath.
We're heading to Konoha to search for a Jinchuuriki.
May I offer some advice, sir?
You should ditch your partner.
That man seems far beyond the influence of money.
I'm aware.
He's definitely uninterested in money.
But, there's a good reason why he's the only person...
...who can be my partner.
And that would be?
Every one of my previous partners is dead.
The second I have a problem with someone, I lose it and kill them.
But I just can't kill him.
That's why.
Concentrate!
Mix the two chakras together!
Hurry, Tenzou!
Sit
I know!
Naruto...
If we keep this up, Naruto's gonna get hurt...
Not only that, I don't know if I can keep stopping him-
No, this is the only way.
Whether or not Naruto completes this technique depends on you, as well.
I understand.
Beyond this...is Akatsuki!
Let's go.
Aww, nasty.
I spent all of five minutes in that shithole
and my clothes get soaked in the stink.
Took you long enough, Kakuzu.
Konoha
We Investigate Anything
Squad
Today's question, brought to you by special guests, is...
What's underneath that bandage, Kotetsu-senpai?
This?
Come to think of it,
you didn't wear it when you were a kid.
Let's have a look.
No, no, I don't think so.
Oh come on! Let us see!
You want to see it that badly?
But...
We'll want to see it more if you keep hiding it!
Does he have zits?
Or maybe freckles?
Or maybe even crazy whiskers?
Ew, that'd be awful!
Are you out of your minds?!
Though if you all want to see that badly, I'll have to indulge.
Show us!
Here I go!
Get a good look!
Nah, never mind.
It doesn't matter. In the end, it's troublesome...
I was just about to take it off, damn it!
They haven't come here yet.
Not here yet?
We'll stake this place out until they make a move.
I-I dunno!
And even if I did, I wouldn't tell you!
You heard him.
Should I work him over?
We'll let Ibiki handle him.
There's no sign of Akatsuki having been here.
Same for me, too.
There's no indication anyone's come or gone for a few days.
It's clear that they haven't come by this area yet.
What should we do, Aoba?
We still haven't received any requests for back-up from the other four search teams.
So no one's found Akatsuki yet?
We can't be sure.
They may already be in the midst of a fight.
Don't worry.
The best situation would be for Asuma-san's team to make initial contact with them.
You two know better than anyone how strong he is, don't you?
You're right!
Yeah, and Shikamaru's with him, too.
All right then. Let's leave this village and set up a new strategy.
Move out.
Let's analyze all of the information we've got.
At one point Akatsuki was headed towards one of the five exchange points.
We haven't received any requests for back-up from the other four teams.
And the boss of this bounty collection agency still hasn't come by.
Which means...
There's still a chance that they're heading towards this bounty collection agency.
That's right.
We'll wait for Akatsuki to come to us, and ambush and capture them!
Those are all of the attack patterns I can think of that the enemy may take.
Take up positions around the bounty collector's hideout, as planned.
Yes, sir!
Akatsuki, where did you go?
Took you long enough, Kakuzu.
Too slow!
That's one down.
That freakin' hurt.
What the hell's your problem?
What's going on? We hit his vital organs!
Stop shaking, damn it.
It hurts like a bastard!
Is he immortal?!
No shit, Sherlock.
Now, who the hell are you people?
That sash!
It belongs to those Ninja Guardians!
Oh, god damn it.
I'm gonna have to go back inside that shithole of an exchange point again...
Chiriku!
We're shinobi from Konoha.
We've been ordered to either capture or exterminate Akatsuki.
As you Akatsuki work in two-man teams,
we'd planned on capturing one of you after eliminating the other. But...
...you've got some serious powers.
So this is an Akatsuki!
What an insane ability!
At this rate, my Shadow Sewing won't...
Well, you guys fucked up on the order.
Where's your partner?
He released the technique!
Kotetsu, Izumo, fall back!
So that one in the center really is...
I see the lure of money's got you for once, Hidan.
Kakuzu, stay out of this!
I'm going to use them for my ceremony!
The money's all yours.
Kakuzu and Hidan, huh?
Works for me.
Just don't underestimate them. You'll get yourself killed.
Like they could pull it off, Kakuzu.
If they could kill me, I'd let 'em.
But that's not happening, is it?
What's he going to do with that diagram?
I'll take the lead.
As soon as you see an opening, immobilize the immortal guy with the Shadow Sewing, Shikamaru.
If you can just give me a couple seconds, I'll cut his head off and hopefully keep him from interfering.
That's too risky!
This isn't like you.
I'll go, too.
Don't you get it?!
That's the best strategy we've got right now!
I've never seen Asuma get like this.
They're a hell of a lot stronger than me!
Izumo, Kotetsu, keep an eye on the other Akatsuki and guard Shikamaru.
If we know what they're capable of now,
shouldn't we pull back and set up a new strategy?
They're not just gonna let us run away.
If we run without putting up a fight, we'll be wiped out,
and Konoha will be in even graver danger.
It's like sending in a single unit to break through enemy lines.
Sometimes, that's the only move you have!
I thought you hated those kinds of strategies, like I do.
When you're up against a skilled opponent,
you need to make sacrifices to protect the king.
Don't tell me Asuma's going to sacrifice himself!
One of them's stupidly strong and his abilities are still unknown. The other's immortal.
This really doesn't look good for us.
But that doesn't mean Asuma should sacrifice himself!
Shougi?! Too troublesome.
I know that you're lazy.
I also know that you're good at coming up with ways to avoid as much trouble as you possibly can.
Shougi allows you to work through various situations by utilizing each of the pieces' individual attributes.
This game is a must for people like you who're good at coming up with strategies.
You should get a decent grasp on the rules if you read this book.
Then you'll just need to practice.
It'll be troublesome, but I'll have it down in ten minutes.
I...lost.
You didn't have to hold back, you know.
I never expected the Climbing Silver.
This book said something about soldiers in the front breaking through enemy lines.
Are you that mad about losing?
No. So you used a strategy that calls for sacrifices, like soldiers breaking through enemy lines.
It seems like the rational type of strategy you might use, but I don't like using it very much.
It's just a game.
I guess. The Climbing Silver inflicts great damage to the enemy in exchange for sacrificing your own pieces.
Of course it's natural for you to lose pieces during the game, but to consider throwing your own pieces away an easy decision...
I can't detach myself enough, I suppose.
I'm not as logic-minded as you think.
Wanna play again?
This time I'll take it easy and not use the Climbing Silver.
Break through enemy lines?
Are these enemies so powerful that he thinks we can't avoid making sacrifices?
It's true that we chuunin won't even make them break a sweat.
And we're at a serious disadvantage if he's got to fight them while trying to protect us.
It's like Asuma said.
They could wipe us out.
What's the best move?
They're like the rook and bishop.
To capture a rook or bishop, you need bait.
We need bait that's big enough to make them think they have to chase it.
We're not good enough to be that bait.
The only one who's strong enough to do that is...
You aren't cut out to be the Climbing Silver.
I won't end up a sacrificial piece.
Not with you behind me.
This is pathetic!
I may not be good enough to be the bait or make them break a sweat, but I'll make sure we win!
Did you finish your little strategy meeting?
Ow ow ow!
Getting cut up like that hurt.
God will smite assholes like you who don't understand the pain of others.
You've got some nice looking knives!
Asuma!
Damn it! Get him!
I'm cooked if he gets me with that again.
I'll chase you where ever you run!
Shikamaru, keep it up.
He has to fight while dodging your Shadow Sewing.
I have the advantage!
Damn it!
My Shadow Sewing technique is making the fight easier for Asuma.
The basic plan is definitely sound.
But it doesn't matter if he's got the advantage in a physical fight.
That guy's immortal, and we've got a limit on lives and chakra!
The real fight won't start until we capture him.
I don't have time to sit and think!
I don't think so!
Shit!
That stance...
What did you think of Chiriku's technique?
His was even more impressive, wasn't it?
Damn it!
Hidan, don't let your guard down.
Just shut the fuck up and watch, Kakuzu!
Nice!
These two really work well together.
It looks like that guy really doesn't plan on attacking us.
Not that it means we can trust him to stay like that.
You almost got him, Shikamaru.
Forget that, I need you to back me up with something.
You guys are too desperate!
You keep using attacks that have the highest probability of landing.
I can see right through you!
And you mess around too much when you fight.
Now!
You won't escape this time!
Then I won't dodge.
Unstoppable bastard.
I'll kill off the kiddies first!
Shit!
You're fighting me!
Captain Asuma!
If combo attacks and pin-point combos can't hit him, then...
Katon, Haisekishou!
(Katon, Haisekishou: Fire Element, Searing Ash Cloud)
He stopped moving?
iijiina riyuu
It's so very easy
issai yurusu jakuhai
for youth to forgive everything
resukyuutai mo yondeoita
I called in the rescue squad
dakara
So please kiss me, please kiss me all night
puriizu kisu mi puriizu kisu mi
datenshi no mahou ka koakuma no chachina itazura
Is it a fallen angel's magic, or a mischievous monster's prank?
tsumaranakunacchau mae ni
Before we get bored
soore de houre
Let's let go
bouringubooru
Of that bowling ball. We lead such strange lives
ibutsu na sonzai daro
shouchi no suke
You've gotta understand
kowaresoude...
We're gonna smash it...
docchirakatta kanjou de kirihirake yo
Cut through the inner turmoil
kowaresou de
We're gonna break...
kowasenai bokura no shouri
I can't break it...our victory.
Next Episode
Hidan and Kakuzu's abilities surpass human capabilities.
All plans against them fail.
The horrible ceremony involving Asuma is about to come to an end as his friends stare dumbfounded.
Shikamaru's scream echoes through the air.
Asuma Dies! The Naruto Shippuuden
Special of Despair and Imprisonment
Asuma dies! The Naruto Shippuuden Special of Despair and Imprisonment!
It's a full hour special!
It'll air on Thursday, October 2nd at 7:59 P.M.!
Airing on Thursday, October 2nd at 7:59 P.M.!
It's unfair! Unfair!
You're so lucky!
You're gorgeous, with a great sense of style to boot.
You've had a bit too much to drink.
So, how is he?
Asuma-san!
Well, I wouldn't know...
You're blushing!
Hey! Hey, hey!
Man, I'm so jealous!
I'm stuck with Tsunade-sama all day.
Oh, but it's a great job.
Butcha know, even when we were traveling around together, these were the only kindsa guys we'd meet!
Oh man, at this rate I'm gonna miss my chance to get married, like Tsunade-sama did!
You probably should stop there...
Whatev! I never mention it ta her!
No, I'm saying-
Shizune!
I want to hear you finish that sentence!