Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Damn it!
Hey, don't rush it.
Your training's going fine. It's only a matter of time.
If that were true, then you should let me train longer!
I know that you're pretty tough...
I... I'm ready to go any...time... I'm fine...
C-Captain Yamato is creeping me out!
You carry him for a while.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! You're the one who wants money, not me!
You carry his dead ass!
He's your precious bounty, isn't he?
What're you giving me that look for?
I swear, one day I am going to murder you.
Like you could pull it off, Kakuzu.
Oh, he's doing fine!
Maybe he doesn't need any soldier pills, after all.
I wouldn't say that.
Hey! How long have you been there?
Since before you came by.
Really? I didn't notice you at all!
You really don't stand out.
I'm sorry.
Anyways, that training is much harder than it looks.
From what I could tell, Naruto isn't especially skilled,
yet he has to maintain his focus while using shadow clones to his absolute limits.
What he's doing is on a whole different level from normal training methods, isn't it?
Yeah. It is.
At least,
that's what was written in this book.
You didn't have to hide it!
I thought you'd get sick of me relying on books all the time.
I knew it...
Sorry, that's not what I meant.
It's fine.
You looked into it because you were worried about your comrade, right?
Books are perfect for times like that.
See? You're actually very nice sometimes.
I'm nice?
Let's go. We don't want to interrupt his training.
They've become a good team while I was away.
That's good to see.
Naruto!
Concentrate on everything you've learned so far,
and dispel your shadow clones for now.
It's time to accumulate all that experience.
Okay!
How about it? Feel anything different?
It's still not enough.
I'm gonna keep training-
I keep telling you not to overdo it.
What's that?
A gift from Sakura. There are soldier pills and a note inside.
These are my special Sakura soldier pills.
Eat them and keep training hard! Hell yeah! Sakura
Sakura-chan...
Time to have one of Sakura-chan's homemade soldier pills!
Sakura-chan... The hell?! I can't eat this!
All right, time to get back to it!
Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Naruto's been able to keep his pace up thanks to my soldier pills, I'm sure of it!
Wow...
Naruto, why don't you take a break?
If I keep slacking off, I'll never catch up to Sasuke!
Why hello, Sakura!
Oh, Iruka-sensei!
Naruto's something else, isn't he?
He really helped out during the village's latest crisis, huh?
Hey, I helped, too...
Just kidding!
My bad... You've become Tsunade-sama's pupil, after all.
I'm so proud to have had such outstanding students.
Especially the class clowns, they're so cute.
Even now, Naruto's undergoing some amazing training that only he can handle, right?
That's impressive.
Well, I was outstanding from the start!
Excuse me for not being a cute student!
Boy, you're awfully grumpy today...
But, he really has become stronger.
Yes, he's changed. Everyone's changing.
My students are getting tougher... They're growing up.
That's...
I see. Even Chiriku fell...
I had just left the complex.
By the time I returned, everyone was already...
Akatsuki must be checking places in the Fire Country where they think we'd hide a Jinchuuriki.
They're finally here.
We can't let them leave the Fire Country.
Assemble all twenty of the newly-formed platoons!
Those are my orders.
Are there any questions?
What is it?
I believe that Chiriku, a former member of the 12 Ninja Guardians, was supposed to be there.
What happened to him?
Chiriku-sama was...killed by them.
Chiriku was... You're kidding me!
For the sake of Konoha's prestige,
and above all else, the safety of the Fire Country,
we can't allow these people to move freely!
I also want to know what they are after, but these are dangerous opponents.
Do not let them leave the country!
Find them, no matter what! And if you can't capture them, kill them!
Go!
Dismissed!
I won't disgrace the name of Team Asuma!
I'll give it my all, Shikamaru, Asuma-sensei!
All right...
Let's start our search from Fire Temple.
Somebody's gotta do it.
Let's go!
Asuma-sensei...
What is it?
It sounded like you knew this Chiriku guy from the Fire Temple.
Yeah. Didn't I ever tell you?
We used to fight together.
This is back when I had left Konoha and joined a group called the 12 Ninja Guardians.
The Fire Temple's close! Let's hurry!
The moon's so pretty.
Sakura-chan, you're amazing!
That's what I'd expect from the woman of my dreams!
Everyone's changing.
Yes. We've all changed.
Naruto's pursuing Sasuke-kun and undergoing training that no one else could do.
Owww...
Oh, Naruto!
The only things I can do are small and insignificant.
It's not the size of what you do for him that counts.
What really matters are your feelings for Naruto.
A shooting star?
Sasuke...
Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Damn it...
Sasuke...
I can't give up!
If I keep walking without ever stopping, I'll make it to you!
Come on!
Hell yeah!
This training's something else.
To think that Naruto got here so quickly!
No, it isn't all due to the training method.
Sasuke's driving him, too.
I cut it in half!
I really did it!
Well done!
It's time to start making your new technique.
I know...
Are you okay, Naruto?!
Maybe he overdid it a bit.
Wh-What?
S...tar...ving...
You're one of a kind...you really are.
Shizune, have we found them yet?
The twenty platoons are searching the border and in a 150km radius around the Fire Temple.
However, we are still unable to find the Akatsuki members.
Why not?! We've got them surrounded so tightly even an ant couldn't get through without us knowing!
Why can't we find them?!
Well...
And Team Asuma was heading towards Fire Temple. Where's his report?!
Next time: An Old Priest's Prayer!
Friggin' Kakashi-sensei! He's late again today!
Well, this always happens.
That's true!
What is it?
Boy, am I late.
I can't walk another step!
Sorry for the trouble, sonny!
Not at all! By the way, are we almost to your house?
Huh?!
What a nightmare.
Stay there!
We'll get you down!
What's wrong, you two?
Your cat?
Thank you, gramps!
G-Gramps?
Bye!
This is such a long, horrible day!
Sometimes he needs to be taught a lesson.
Serves him right!