So there's nothing that will make Akatsuki take any action for now.
No, but there's no arguing that this is a serious situation.
It was absolute carnage.
The village was destroyed in one night and
a great many of the villagers were killed.
The Hidden Rain.
Additionally, all of the border villages that
were attacked were in the Fire Country.
Asuma, we can't jump to conclusions.
I know that!
But they're intentionally leaving the
symbol of the Hidden Rain Village.
I can't stand it!
Someone's trying to start a war.
You could say that.
In fact, you've probably hit the nail on the head.
Do you have any information regarding
the Hidden Rain Village's activities?
Not really.
Shouldn't we be concerned?
For the Fire Country?
For the Feudal Lord.
There may be people trying to get the Feudal Lord to make a move,
Just as the Twelve Ninja Guardians did once in the past.
And we can't give Danzou any reason to stick his nose in this, either.
I'm sure he's got a trick or two up his sleeve.
I want the ANBU and jounin to do some
investigating around the country's borders.
But since we don't know what the current situation
is there, I want this treated as a top-secret mission.
Make sure no one outside of our village finds out what we're doing!
I'll send a letter to the Feudal Lord.
Yes.
Team Asuma will take action if there's any new activity.
Until then, you're dismissed!
I understand. Good day, then.
Excuse me.
The Twelve Ninja Guardians... Now that I
think about it, Asuma-san was part of them.
Yeah. Back when he was just a twenty year-old kid, he'd do
whatever he thought would be best for the Fire Country.
He'd go on and on about his ideas.
He and the Third didn't see eye-to-eye, and he left the village.
Although if you ask me, it was a normal
argument between father and son.
That was ten years ago.
Some of the Twelve Ninja Guardians felt that the Fire Country
should become a military nation and tried to stage a coup d'état.
The group was split in half.
Asuma's side disagreed, and the Guardians were destroyed.
Yo, Asuma-sensei!
Hey, Naruto! Is your training going well?
Nah, I didn't really have time for it.
That's too bad. So what're you doing here?
Captain Yamato told us to wait until he calls for us.
Hey, what are you glaring at him for?
I was just-!
I'm sorry he looks so mean!
Come on, you apologize, too!
Why should I?!
So that's what happened...
The corpses that were stolen were of those who helped stop the coup
d'état at the cost of their own lives: Kitane, Nauma, Touou and Seito.
What did you say?!
I'm truly sorry.
There were four thieves. They seemed
to have planned everything out.
I wonder what the thieves are planning to do with the corpses?
This could become a serious problem if there's some sort
of important secret hidden within one of the bodies.
Also, Sai was injured in battle and has to leave the team for a while.
I'd like to replace him with that boy
trainee from the Fire Temple, but... Well...
What's wrong?
I see...
So you think those four grave robbers were lying in wait for you.
All the time I thought we could avoid problems by having Chiriku-san,
who seemed the most likely to be targeted, leave the team.
And Naruto is important to Akatsuki as a Jinchuuriki.
It isn't completely out of the question that they were after
Naruto, but they only found us at Fire Temple by chance.
So that leaves the boy, Sora.
Yes. In which case, bringing him to the village
and working with him isn't the best strategy.
Of course, I've also consulted the Fire Temple on this matter.
Anyway, please, Sora!
Behave properly around Tsunade-sama!
If you don't, it could be disastrous!
For real! Granny Tsunade doesn't have a good sense of humor!
Please! Like that's gonna scare me.
I don't care if she's the Hokage or an old bag,
I'm not acting differently just for her.
Naruto, Sakura, bring Sora on in!
Right! Come on!
Bye, Asuma-sensei!
Hey!
Hurry up!
We're here!
Tsunade-sama!
Apologize, quick!
Even Buddha would only forgive you once!
Who're you calling an old bag?
I said a Bodhisattva!
(Note: Bodhisattva is someone who has achieved enlightenment and guides others.)
Bodhisattva?
Well, aren't you a cute little monk?
You pass. Welcome to Konoha!
W-Wait a sec!
You really grew up, Sora.
Well, I've got to go write up our report, so I'm off.
I'm going to take Sai to the hospital.
Okay.
W-Wait a second here!
I've gotta continue my training!
What training? Kakashi-sensei's out
on a mission, so you're on your own.
Show Sora around the village.
Sora's a member of Team Kakashi now.
You've gotta be kidding me!
Why should I have to hang out with this dangerous jerk?!
I don't wanna stay with this goon, either!
Yeah, yeah. Do whatever you want.
I'm done arguing.
Let's go, Sai.
Right.
Later. Naruto, take care of Sora!
That's not fair, guys!
They're all the same.
In the end, I'm just a bother to everyone.
Hey, that's not true.
Sakura-chan and Captain Yamato don't think of you as a bother!
If they did, we wouldn't have brought you to the village!
I know.
Then what's-?
You should give up on your revenge.
This isn't related to that!
Maybe not, but-!
Dad was my hero.
He was strong in every way. Mind, body and soul.
I can only remember him up until I turned five.
The guys at Fire Temple wouldn't tell me a thing.
But even so, I learned that Dad was murdered.
They spat out horrible things about him.
They said he got what he deserved! That he deserved to die!
There's no way Dad would do anything bad!
It had to be some sort of mistake!
I'm going to set things straight!
And the guy who killed my dad is gonna pay!
You...
So quit following me! It's annoying!
A-Annoying?! Is this how you treat
people who are worried about you?!
That's exactly what's annoying me!
I'm going to learn about the enemy on my own.
I'll be done with this place in ten minutes!
You're such a-! Go on then!
I don't wanna hang out with you either!
What'd he mean, "be done"?
Damn him... Where the hell did he go?
You wanna fight?
I won't go easy on you just because you're a dog, you mangy mutt!
He's picking a fight with Akamaru?
This is bad! If Kiba sees this...
Hey, what's up, Naruto?
So you're back?
Ah, Akamaru! So this is where you were!
Who's that guy? I don't recognize him.
Yeah, he's, uh...
Hey, you! What're you doing to Akamaru?
Are you his owner?
Why don't you keep him on a leash and train him not to howl!
Akamaru isn't a pet!
He must've howled because you're a threat!
Isn't that right?
I'm from the Fire Temple.
I came to deal with Konoha.
Hey, sorry, Kiba! A bunch of things
happened and now this guy's on my team-
He's with you, Naruto?
Yeah, right! There's no way I'd be friends with that goon!
Whatever! Just shut up, Sora!
No fighting, guys.
Let's all stop getting worked up and try to get along-
Beat it, fatty.
You just called me...fatty, didn't you...?
So what?
O-Oh crap...
Oh crap...
Okay! Time for a battle royale!
Are you retarded?! You're on your own!
Let's get him, Chouji!
Like that fatty can do anything!
You called me "fatty" again.
I'm not fat! I'm just husky!
Idiot! Stop it!
Okay! Hold him still, Chouji!
You aren't fighting fair!
They're ganging up on him?
What'd you expect? You reap what you sow.
Yeah, but I mean...
Damn it all!
Hey, stop it already!
Naruto, are you taking his side?!
Not really, but I can't just stand by and watch either!
He's an outsider!
He isn't an outsider!
He's one of Team Kakashi's companions!
Companions?
So let's all calm down and talk this thr-! Ow!
Hey! You're punching me!
You kicked me first!
What?!
Are they both this stupid?
That hurt, damn it!
Ow!
You're not gonna ask why I didn't join in?
That's not your thing, right?
The four of them going at it is enough.
There's one more person around who'll join in.
A meeting where men are expressing their
feelings of friendship through fist-fighting?!
Why didn't anyone tell me about this?!
They're all pretty tough. This could go on forever.
All right, I guess that's enough.
Juujin Bunshin!
(Juujin Bunshin: Beast-Man Clone)
Konoha-
Baika no Jutsu!
(Baika no Jutsu: Size Multiplier Technique)
Kage Bunshin!
Fuuton!
Charge!
This is-!
I'm not fat!
There!
Okay, how about some barbecue now that your fist-fight is over?
Barbecue!
That's great! Now it's a feast among men!
We'll talk all about how hard we work while grilling the beef!
Resorting to the old stand-by...
How's that sound? You're going too, right?
No, I'm not really...
How's Chiriku doing?
That's right. You know Chiriku-san, don't you Asuma-sensei?
Yeah.
H-How about my mom and dad...?
You're not too bad.
Chiriku really toughened you up, huh?
No. Chiriku-sama's an important person
in the Fire Temple, so I trained myself.
That so? You've gotten that good all on your own...
Oh yeah! Asuma-sensei, please show "that" to him!
"That"?
Amazing!
The trick is to make it thin and sharp!
That's right.
Once you get the hang of it, your kunai and
shuriken can easily pierce through an entire tree.
Good luck, guys.
Please wait!
If you knew my dad, I'd like you to tell me about him.
He's Kazuma, a former Guardian Ninja!
Why was he killed?
Dad didn't do anything wrong!
I'm sure of it!
You know, don't you?!
Kazuma...
Kazuma died for his beliefs.
No matter what happened in the end,
he died fighting for what he believed in.
I'm off.
H-Hey...
You're going to train now?
Damn it...
I'm not gonna let you beat me!
One, two, three, four... I think there's about thirty of them.
Yeah. Sounds about right.
This is going to be different from what we've experienced in the past.
We're going to fight against the Kohaku clan's
village, some of the Fire Country's best shinobi.
And we're going to kill every last one of them.
Yup.
Indeed. The other massacres were a diversion.
This time we're finally going to do it.
Well, let me know if there are any wind-natured shinobi.
I'll take them.
Listen, those of the Kohaku clan!
You're all gonna die!
But your souls will protect the Fire Country for all eternity!
I promise! Thank you!
Do it!
Sora and Naruto, huh?
Getting these two to work in formation is probably impossible.
Well, Team Kakashi will be training hard.
So I can go back to my training?
Well, no... Without Kakashi-senpai...
Then what am I gonna do?
Let's see... How about having Asuma-san help you?
Me?!
Next time: The Two Kings!
The Third Konoha Series Super Quiz!
Yeah!
I'm gonna win!
I get a year's supply of fried meat if I win?
No!
This time the Konoha Quiz will be a penalty game!
Among the Ino-Shika-Chou Trio, whom we haven't seen in quite
some time, there's Yamanaka Inoichi who has a special ability-
The Mind-Body Confusion Technique!
And there's Nara Shikaku's secret technique...
The Shadow Neck Bind Technique.
And there's Akimichi Chouza's...
Super Size Multiplier Technique!
So the question is: What technique did Jiraiya-sama use
against the giant snake wreaking havoc on the village?
I have no clue...
We were out chasing after Sasuke-kun...
I was dealing with those Sound guys.
I was asleep.
Time's up!
The correct answer is: The Summoning
Technique: Watchtower Crusher!
Time to pay the penalty!