Sit
Any trouble controlling the Kyuubi's chakra, Tenzou?
We're fine for now.
And please, call me Yamato, not Tenzou.
Yeah, yeah.
One more time!
I did it!
I cut it pretty good!
Damn... I haven't cut into mine at all yet!
I'm different than you guys!
You are me, stupid!
All right!
Damn, the me over there is pretty good...
I need to think of something...
Hey, hey, Kakashi-sensei, I have a question.
What?
Is there anyone else in Konoha with wind element nature?
Are you going to ask for tips?
Well, there is someone...
He's probably playing shougi now.
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
must be expressed with words.
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
Habataitara
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
to that blue, blue sky
aoi aoi ano sora
Checkmate.
Damn, I lost again!
That means the bill's on you after our next job's done, Sensei.
I know.
Hey!
Asuma-sensei!
Hey, how's it going, Naruto?
What's up?
There's something I need to ask you.
Squirm
Tips on how to use wind nature manipulation, eh?
Yeah!
Wow, you're doing nature manipulation training?
Yep!
You've gotta be really sharp to learn that stuff.
You sure you're up for it?
That's why I came to ask Asuma-sensei.
Sensei, you've got wind-natured chakra like me, right?
So you're a wind-type, Naruto?
This is a surprise.
Asuma-sensei, please give me a tip!
Let's see...
Tell you what, I'll consider helping you if you treat
my team to some barbecue after our next mission.
You cheater.
How about it?
That'll be pushing it...
I'll probably lose all my savings...
I guess I have no choice, it's for my training!
Okay, it's a deal!
These are my chakra blades.
They're made of a unique metal that absorbs
its user's chakra and reacts to its nature.
A-Awesome!
Take this one.
Try running your chakra through the blade.
Yes, sir!
My chakra doesn't quite look like yours, does it?
Listen up. For wind, you picture your chakra splitting
into two halves that rub against each other.
Rub against each other?
After they sharpen each other in thin, fine pieces, you rejoin them.
Thin and sharp...like a blade?
Exactly. As thin and sharp as possible.
Uh... One thing...
What's that?
If ninja weapons already have cutting edges,
what's the point of being wind-natured?
I mean, wouldn't it be faster to just attack
with the weapon you already have?
Plus, what's the point of putting cutting
chakra into an edged weapon?
Good question. Let's see if it's pointless or not.
We're going to throw these chakra blades at
that tree over there at the same time, got it?
Why?
Just do it!
Ready, go!
A-Amazing!
It went through the tree and into the rock behind it!
And it cut through pretty deep to boot!
I held back to be on the safe side. If I'd thrown it
hard, it would've gone right through that rock, too.
When the blades of two equal shinobi clash,
the one with the sharper edge will always win.
Wind-natured chakra is the best type for close to mid-range combat.
And there aren't too many wind-types around.
Really?
I'll be happy to lend a hand whenever you need it,
but you'll have to pay for our barbecue, okay?
Deal!
Thank you!
It was a shadow clone?
Poor Naruto. He totally forgot about Chouji, didn't he?
Ouch...
You think he can do it?
Create a new technique before Akatsuki makes its move?
I wonder...
Wouldn't it be better to hide Naruto somewhere?
Before they have a chance to come after him?
That's for the Fifth to decide.
I see, that's how it is!
Okay!
Let's do it!
Looks like he picked up some pointers from Asuma.
He certainly learned how to use the shadow
clones' special attributes effectively.
Naruto?
Social
Interaction
for Dummies
When your friends are working unusually hard on the job or doing their hobbies, it's nice to casually bring them a snack or drink.
Working unusually hard... Seems normal to me.
Social
Interaction
for Dummies
Social
Interaction
for Dummies
Social
Interaction
There's been a report that a village on the
Fire Country's border has been attacked.
Was it Akatsuki?
We can't deny the possibility, but it's believed
the attackers were from the Hidden Rain Village.
Why? Why would a neighboring country's village attack?
If we aren't careful, this could become
all out war between our two countries.
You don't think they found out that the Akatsuki are after
Naruto-kun and are taking advantage of the situation, do you?
They aren't that foolish.
At any rate, we have to find out what's going on.
Call for Asuma!
Yes, sir! But that will mean that there will
be one less jounin here in the village.
If Akatsuki comes after Naruto-kun right now, I'm afraid
we won't have enough people to protect him.
Okay! Time to consolidate all the experience you've gained so far.
Think about your training while you release your shadow clones.
Right!
All right, here goes!
S
i
t
I can do it! I've almost got it!
The downside to this training is that you accumulate
the clones' exhaustion as well as their experience.
I already...knew about that...
But, I've almost got it...
Take a little break, Naruto.
There's no time to rest.
I'm okay, Kakashi-sensei!
Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
H-Hey! Wait!
S
i
t
Wow! Naruto's really giving it his all!
Oh well. With his stamina, he should be okay.
Here!
Who're they for?
Oh! Uh...n-no one special!
S-see you later!
Say hi to Kurenai-sensei for me!
H-How did she-?
There he is!
Sorry to bug you when you're about to go visit Kurenai, but...
You, too?! Why do you guys know-?
Come on, we all know about-
Shikamaru!
I received an order from the Fifth stating that
everyone from Team Asuma, me, Chouji and Ino,
are supposed to leave immediately.
What?!
Everyone from our old group?
Yeah.
Let's go!
Nara Shikamaru, Yamanaka Ino and Akimichi
Chouji will work under Sarutobi Asuma...
...and survey the borderland village that got attacked.
Yes, sir!
I'm also worried about Akatsuki right now.
Exercise extreme caution!
What're you going to do about Naruto?
This B-rank mission should be just right for him...
Am I being foolish?
Yes!
I did it!
I knew I was awesome, but damn!
At this rate, I'll master this new technique in the blink of an eye!
Excuse me, you're progressing quickly
because of my awesome training method.
I think I've done a pretty "awesome" job here too, Kakashi-senpai!
Whatever, let's move on to the next step...
Then again, this is something only you could do.
Naruto!
Yamato, let's take a little break!
Got it.
Is Naruto okay?
He just needs to rest a bit.
I can't believe this guy!
Um...
What is it, Sakura?
Tsunade-sama...
Asuma-sensei!
Okay! We're all here, right?
Hey, hey! Sensei!
What is it?
Come on! You can't tell, Sensei?
This is the first time that we've all worn
the earrings that you gave us, Sensei!
You've done great, Chouji, Ino!
Since Shikamaru already passed the exam, this means
everyone in Team 10 has become a chuunin!
And with that, I am no longer your supervisor.
You all will become captains, and lead your own teams.
These earrings are my present to you for becoming a chuunin.
Don't ever forget that we were Team 10!
I see. This is the first time everyone in
Team 10 has gathered together in a while.
Why do I have to take a break from training to go on some mission?
It can't be helped! It's a mission, after all.
Yeah, but there are missions, and there are missions!
Damn Granny Tsunade!
She's giving us this lame mission for some stupid incident!
Hey, Naruto!
How's the training going?
It's on pause while I go on some mission!
Are you guys going on one now too, Ino?
Yes! It's the first time in a while we've all-
Everyone's gathered together!
Konohamaru?
Naruto-niichan, are you going on a mission?
Yeah, sure am.
What? You were out searching for a cat again?
That's right!
This is our seventh one now!
We're pros at this.
I see! You're really working hard!
Well, I'm gonna go report in.
Later, Konohamaru!
Yeah! Good luck, Uncle Asuma!
Uncle Asuma, huh?
Wait, Uncle? Why?
Why? Because Asuma's Konohamaru's uncle.
Th-Then-!
Asuma-sensei is the Third's son.
I didn't know that!
M-Me neither!
Wh-What is it?
Well, you're the Third's son, and we both have wind-natured chakra.
I feel a lot more pumped up now than I did a little while ago!
Well, you'll always be able to continue
your training regardless of your mission.
Now don't forget what I told you.
Thin and sharp!
I know!
Okay! Time for Team Yamato to head on out!
Wait up!
N-Naruto!
Are you the team captain?
Right. Kakashi-senpai had another mission to take care of.
Take care of Naruto!
I will!
Hey, Captain Yamato, you're falling behind!
Excuse me!
Sorry!
Well then, let's head out as well!
He's improving with amazing speed, but it still
won't be easy for him to develop a new technique.
I'd think not.
Sorry to interrupt you at a time like this, Kakashi.
I'd like you to team up with Jiraiya and
search for clues about what Akatsuki is up to.
I wanted to give Naruto time to train, but...
Naruto is pushing himself too much in order
to further his training as fast as he can.
At the rate he was going, even with Yamato there, I was
getting worried that his chakra would go out of control again.
I don't think this decision is a mistake.
Look at the despair, tears and rage that are in that valley.
The Fire Country doesn't need diplomats.
We don't need to waste words, trying to get along with others.
The Fire Country must take its stance now.
In order for it to unite the world, it must
be made clear that it sits at the top.
And for that to happen, we must rid it
of the disgustingly corrupt Konoha.
We must awaken the Fire Country!
Let's hurry up and finish this mission so I can get back to my training!
Hey, don't let your guard down just because this is a B-rank mission.
I know, I know.
Kodomo no koro mita niji wo
If I look up now for the rainbow I saw as a boy,
ima miageru to nana iro de wa naku
there are no longer the seven colors,
Yagate kiri ga kakari
only mist and fog...
Jikan wa sugi kawatte yuku
As time passes by, and the world around me changes,
Kimi wo sagashitemo doko ni mo inai
no matter where I search for you, you're nowhere to be found.
Me wo toji, kokoro hiraite
So I close my eyes, and open my heart...
mata nagamete mitemo nanimo kawaranai no ka
I need to know, if I gaze up again,
tashikamete mitai
will things be different this time?
Sunao ni narereba kono kiri ga hareru to
Maybe if I was more honest, the fog would fade away.
kokoro ni negai sou sakenderu
So I pray, screaming that wish deep within my soul.
Nanika wo nakushiteshimatta koto de sou
When you lose one thing,
te ni shita mono mo kitto arun darou
you gain another, don't you?
Dakedo mada bokura wa otona ni tomadoi
But still, no matter how often the adults confuse us,
ikite yuku sube sagashiteru
we'll keep looking for the right way to live our lives.
Next Episode
The past sins of the 12 Ninja Guardians come back to
haunt them, and open the curtain on a new story.
Naruto Shippuuden Special
will be airing on Thursday, May 8th at 7:59 pm!
The Naruto Shippuuden Special will be
airing on Thursday, May 8th at 7:59 PM!
Konoha
Cele
Konoha Celebrity Report!
brity
Re
po
rt
Today I'll be introducing my uncle, Sarutobi Asuma!
Hey.
Uncle Asuma is a member of the Sarutobi
clan just like me, and is the Third's son!
Uncle was a real punk back in the day. He even rebelled
against Grandpa and left the village for a while!
He hasn't changed much, either!
Shut up! I'm not a punk!
Even though he acts like that, he's actually
really good at taking care of others.
He treats his subordinates to BBQ
whenever they complete their missions!
But thanks to Chouji, his wallet's constantly empty!
That's none of your business.
Konohamaru, you're forgetting something very important!
Boss!
Come on! You know there's that one
rumor going on about Asuma-sensei!
That's right!
So hey! Aren't you with Kurenai-sensei a lot, Asuma-sensei?
They're holding hands! I bet they're going o-!
No comment.