Hey, he's not getting up!
Naruto!
Naruto, are you okay?
Okay, Chouji, hold him up just like that.
I can only give him first aid for now.
But you know, I never would have thought you'd mix your real self in with your clones.
You're not quite at Shikamaru's level, but you're pretty smart, too, Naruto!
You can't compare me to Shikamaru...
I'm amazed that he managed to use the new technique three times...
He barely got to two during our last training session.
His quick thinking and strong self-confidence allow him to try again if he fails.
Naruto's become so strong.
Taking a technique even the Fourth couldn't complete that far...
It's almost time for his generation to take over.
He's surpassed me.
Can you sense it?
You're always right in front of Naruto's eyes, making him stronger...
Right, Sasuke?
Senpai, it's time.
Yeah.
Think you can walk?
Okay, everyone. Let's go home!
Where's Kakashi-sensei?
Cleaning up.
I can't believe...I lost...to a bunch of children...
That's right.
I have no doubt we look like kids to someone who fought the First Hokage.
But to us, you're just a washed-up, decrepit old man.
That's why you're down at our feet, groveling as you're about to die.
The next generation will always surpass the previous one and take their place.
Excellent job, everyone.
The threat has passed for the time being, but Akatsuki is still out there.
So don't be complacent!
Naruto, your injury...
It's like a badge of honor!
He's been given emergency first aid.
Go get examined at Konoha Hospital, just to be on the safe side.
No, I don't really...
Don't tell her no!
Don't worry, master! I'll make sure he gets to the hospital!
Okay, Naruto?!
Now then, both of your teams have earned a break.
Go and rest up.
Dismissed!
Did you notice?
I did. Naruto-kun's injury, correct?
I wonder what did that...
I've never seen anything like it.
And what's going on with that Akatsuki corpse Kakashi's group brought back?
Right. We're already conducting an autopsy on it, but...
Then tell the person in charge of it to make investigating that effect their top priority.
It's finally over...
Hey, guys.
This is as far as I'm going.
But your house is this way...
I've got something...
What's with him? Sheesh!
Easy, easy.
Should you be out walking around?
Shikamaru.
You don't have anyone to play Shogi with now, do you?
You were Asuma's favorite student, I imagine you'll be a bit lonely now.
He taught me a lot of stuff. Some of it was really profound, and some of it was completely inane.
Shogi was one of them.
I could say I'm not sad, but I'd be lying.
The problem is the world won't let me stay a kid forever, so I can't lie around crying about it, either.
I'd always brush my responsibilities off as being troublesome.
That's why I messed up so often when I was a kid and Asuma would have to protect me.
I gotta say...
He made for a weird teacher that I could never quite figure out...
But I always thought he was the coolest adult I knew.
And now it's my turn.
When your kid's born, it'll be my turn to be the teacher.
So I've gotta grow up to be a cool adult, too!
Thank you.
Damn, Dad. You're a lot better than Asuma.
The Climbing Silver, huh?
When protecting the king from a powerful enemy, sometimes you have to make sacrifices.
Whoa, if you try to run that way, you'll run right into my knight.
No matter where I put my gold, I lose my bishop.
Freakin' knight, that was a dirty move.
If you think of Konoha's shinobi as shogi pieces, I'd be the knight.
Says who?
Says Asuma.
He knew you very well. Good ol' Asuma.
All right, then who's the king?
Then do you know who the king is?
The Hokage?
That's what I used to think, too.
But I was wrong.
Okay, then who is it?
You'll know when the time comes.
The unborn children who'll inherit Konoha from us.
They're the king.
Looks like you understand... And that's checkmate!
You're not strong enough to protect the king yet, boy.
Focus harder!
Bullshit!
You're always overdoing it.
You don't need to get so angry...
No back-talking!
He's got scratches and bruises.
None of his other injuries are a big deal. His arm is the real problem!
His bones are fractured in multiple places.
His body can't handle that technique.
I see.
That's everything the autopsy team that worked on Kakuzu concluded?
Right. They haven't completely finished the autopsy yet, but...
In any case, I need to tell this to his commanding jounin.
What should we do?
Call Kakashi and Yamato to the autopsy room.
Really? Hidan and Kakuzu are dead?
Yes. It appears Naruto-kun and his team were the ones who killed them.
I thought that he might kill one more Akatsuki if we let him live,
but it looks like he's working extra diligently.
Not bad.
I'd wager Akatsuki never even imagined they might lose two members at once.
But they managed to obtain the Two-Tails, as well.
Considering that, it may behoove us to make another attempt to blunt their power.
How's it going with the child?
Ah yes, I was planning to conduct the final experiment soon, but according to the data I have so far, I don't believe we're mistaken.
That's most exciting!
Just a little longer until we reach the final stage.
But there's one more pawn that I must have in order to reach that goal.
Hey, Kabuto, would you mind bringing that woman here?
Her?!
The autopsy isn't done yet,
but we learned something important about Naruto's new technique while studying the corpse.
What actually injured him wasn't related to any manner of blunt physical trauma.
Meaning what?
Every cell in his body has had its chakra vessels severed.
His chakra vessels?
Yes, that's right.
Something like this is completely unprecedented.
Wind Element Rasen-Shuriken... Who knew it would be so powerful...
The body actually looks like it's been poisoned, not physically struck.
The attacks were so minuscule they damaged him on the cellular level.
I assume he changed the wind-natured chakra into countless microscopic blades through shape manipulation,
which then sliced at each individual cell.
What a technique...
Poison, huh?
So it's more appropriate to talk about the attack's precision rather than the number of times it hits.
So what about its user, Naruto?
That's the real issue.
I thought so.
Kakashi, don't let Naruto use his new technique, Wind Element Rasen-Shuriken, ever again!
It's that bad?
Naruto's right arm suffered the same type of damage.
Though not as badly as this guy, of course.
If he keeps using this new technique,
Naruto will lose the ability to manipulate chakra!
With a technique like this, there would be a high risk...
Damage to the chakra circulatory system can't be repaired by any form of medical ninjutsu, including mine.
Make sure Naruto understands that!
I can't believe he wants to see that woman...
That was a hostile welcome, Guren!
Well, if it isn't Kabuto!
I had you pegged as an intruder.
Something tells me you knew exactly who it was.
Who, me?
Besides, I can't have someone who's too weak to handle that little game standing by Orochimaru-sama's side, can I?
There, all done!
Now take it easy, okay?
Thank you, Sakura-chan!
Look, Naruto, don't use that new technique unless you're completely out of options.
Don't rely on it, okay?
I'll be fine! As long as you're around to fix me up-
No, you won't!
Medical ninjutsu can't just magically heal any injury!
But...this all makes me kinda happy...
I feel like the two of us are getting closer to Sasuke.
Oh, jeez...
Tsunade-sama, here's a message from an ANBU we've placed in a foreign country.
This is-!
What's Kakashi doing right now?
I assume he's somewhere with Naruto-kun.
Whatever. Tell him to finish whatever he's doing and come here immediately!
He's found a clue to where Orochimaru is, hasn't he?
Yes, but he was ambushed right before he got the last part.
We need to form a new squad and send them to investigate right away!
Next time: A Shinobi's Resolve!
On today's show, we have a special guest to talk to us about the mysterious organization known as Akatsuki.
Hello! I'm Yamato!
First of all, how many members are there in the Akatsuki?
We believe they started with ten members.
But Orochimaru had a conflict with Itachi and withdrew from the organization.
And then Sasori of the Red Sand died in his fight against Elder Chiyo.
In their fight against Shikamaru, Hidan and Kakuzu were killed and left unable to fight, respectively.
As such, they're down to six members.
We have the names and photos of the following four members:
Uchiha Itachi.
Hoshigaki Kisame.
Deidara.
Zetsu!
We don't know anything about the last two.
We are still conducting investigations.
In order to discover what Akatsuki's true motives are, we consider information gathering to be our #1 priority.
Indeed.
To all of our viewers out there, if you see any of these people, contact Konoha immediately!