I'm not getting away, right?
You can only hold that shadow technique for about five minutes before you run out of juice...
And now we're all alone.
This's the best possible situation for me, you dipshit!
Including my own, I had five hearts total.
Kakashi, it's only fitting that I take yours...
...to replace the one you destroyed!
Everything's ready.
He sent them out separately, and now they're joined?
The masks that merged were the fire and wind ones...
Kakashi, I'm going to rip out your heart to replace the one you destroyed.
That one?!
Is he trying to force me into an open area and shoot me down?
Is that your idea of hiding?
Sensei!
You did an excellent job of concealing yourself this time, Kakashi.
But do you have the courage to stand before me again?
Not again!
Suiton, Suijinheki!
(Suiton, Suijinheki: Water Element, Circular Water Wall)
Water attacks aren't enough to stop a fire-wind combination?
My only option is to fight him at close-range.
Kakashi-sensei!
I guess you couldn't manage to account for my attacks, too.
And now I'll take your heart!
Die!
What do you think?
The pain is glorious, isn't it?
Please, Shikamaru...
What a waste.
Lord Jashin must be disappointed.
Anyway, Kakuzu should be about done by now.
What...?
Looks like he made it.
You couldn't have...
Guess I should head back.
Not deep enough!
You little prick...
Why the fuck are you still alive?!
Why the fuck are you still alive?
I was just playing possum.
The blood on your spike isn't mine.
It's your partner's.
You couldn't have...
Oh, we did.
We used your blood for your partner's ritual.
Kakashi-sensei, take this.
Use it when you see an opening.
I'll give it to you.
Shikamaru knew that blood was the key to his ability.
So he prepared several special blood capsules before we left.
How the hell did you-?
It didn't matter who, we just needed a
chance to get some of Kakuzu's blood.
With this capsule, that is.
Impossible...
When did you even have the chance...?
When I punched a hole in your chest with my Raikiri.
In that same moment, I filled a capsule with your blood.
I'll capture him by myself.
And...
I'll fulfill that role as well.
After I took that, it became my job to corner you.
Where the hell are you taking me?
Trying to separate me from Kakuzu, huh?
You little shit!
You sure you want to let him go alone?
He's severely underestimating Hidan.
That Shikamaru kid would've become a big bounty one day.
But now, he'll be dead by the end of the day.
That was our plan all along.
Sons a bitches...
Impossible...
For that kid...to have planned so far ahead...
Well, that's what happened.
You should have planned more carefully.
You two severely underestimated Shikamaru.
He refused to let the knowledge that Asuma died for go to waste.
Men like you who kill without hesitation could never understand.
Kakashi-sensei!
Are you okay?
Yeah, somehow...
They invaded his body so far in such a short amount of time.
If Shikamaru had taken a second longer, he'd be...
Pull them out slowly, so you don't damage the blood vessels!
I'll heal you with medical techniques right away!
Heal me later!
They're coming!
Baika no Jutsu!
Chou Harite!
(Chou Harite: Mega Palm Thrust)
Nice! Good one, Chouji!
Chouji!
What?
Shit!
He came back to life...
He absorbed the lightning creature's heart.
What is he?
Even his main body is a monster.
You've destroyed two of my hearts.
It's been ages since anyone's managed that...
Even a thickhead like me knows what's going on.
It's been like a thousand times at this point.
Hell, any dumbass could figure out your technique after seeing it so often.
What?
Your shadow ain't as strong as it was before.
Five minutes is your limit.
I can move!
When you bind someone with your technique,
the effect lessens as time passes.
Basically, the longer you use it, the weaker it gets.
You're almost outta chakra, ain'tcha? Huh?!
You won't escape me again.
Here he comes!
Right!
Too fast!
Crap, I can't move!
Hatake Kakashi.
I intended to replace the hearts I've lost with yours,
but I changed my mind.
I can stock up on hearts anytime.
Now die!
Fuuton, Rasengan!
(Fuuton, Rasengan: Wind Element, Spiraling Sphere)
Suiton, Hahonryuu!
(Suiton, Hahonryuu: Water Element, Crashing Rapids)
Gufuu Suika no Jutsu!
(Gufuu Suika no Jutsu: Water Typhoon Vortex Technique)
Sorry we're late.
Perfect timing.
His snoring's so loud that I can't sleep...
Yeah!
Wait up...
Talk about a rough sleeper...
I won't be able to sleep like this!
Hold on, Naruto! Wake up!
That's just going too far!
Good morning!
Captain Yamato, what're you doing?
Well, uh...
I can't believe he slept through all that ruckus...
What's wrong?
Kakashi-senpai, that's just not fair.
You won't escape me again.
Here he comes!
Right!
Too fast!
Crap, I can't move!
Hatake Kakashi.
I intended to replace the hearts I've lost with yours,
but I changed my mind.
I can stock up on hearts anytime.
Now die!
Fuuton, Rasengan!
Suiton, Hahonryuu!
Gufuu Suika no Jutsu!
Sorry we're late.
Perfect timing.
Backup... We're saved...
Sakura! Sai-san! And Naruto, too!
I've never seen you so beat up, senpai.
Well, excuse me.
Our enemy must be extremely powerful.
I see we've got another comedian.
You already look worn out.
Naruto, are you okay?
Where's Shikamaru?
He's fighting this guy's partner somewhere else.
Two of you go back Shikamaru up.
One long-range fighter and one medical ninja.
Leave it to me.
All right! Sai, Sakura, follow Pakkun and help Shikamaru!
Yes, sir!
What do you think your reinforcements will do for you?
Now I have a wider variety of new hearts to choose from.
I can handle him.
Naruto...
Let's go!
Naruto, take care of things here.
Did he finish it?
No, he's about halfway there, if that.
I see.
But...
Actually, just watch.
You're about to see a completely new Naruto!
This way!
No matter what the situation was, he shouldn't have gone up against the person who killed Asuma-san by himself!
Do you think Shikamaru-kun's okay?
Shikamaru's...
Shikamaru'll be okay!
He's the smartest person in the Fire Country.
And also...
All right, I guess we should head out.
Jeez, he isn't the least bit motivated!
I can't believe he's actually a squad captain!
Don't say that.
He's just not good at showing his enthusiasm.
Or rather, he hates showing it.
He'll complain about how annoying it is while working up a sweat.
I really don't get it.
Tsunade-sama, are you sure you aren't overestimating Shikamaru?
Actually, I think I may still be underestimating him a little!
What's this?
We've received a formal request from the Fire Country's Feudal Lord.
It says that he'd like to have Shikamaru join his personal guard.
It seems that Shikamaru caught the Feudal Lord's eye. His people saw how efficiently he ran the last Chuunin exam and thought he'd be a great leader.
Then...
Yes. That's the first step to becoming one of the 12 Guardian Ninja.
It's a pretty big deal.
Amazing!
So did Shikamaru accept the offer?
You know how he is!
I heard that you refused the Feudal Lord's offer.
Yep.
You know, going out and seeing the outside world isn't such a bad idea.
I'm the man I am today because of my experience
with the 12 Guardian Ninja.
I'm not gonna change.
I don't wanna deal with any extra trouble in the future, either.
It's like...
How should I put it?
Chouji, Ino, the guys in my current squad, Naruto...
I'm just staying in the village 'cause I'd be worried about them otherwise.
I see.
So you have the Will of Fire in you, too!
The Will of Fire... That's something the Third talked about.
Yep. It refers to the strong will that protects our village.
Mine's nothing to write home about.
Don't be embarrassed!
You want to protect them because you care about them.
Isn't that right?
We're all Konoha shinobi. It's troublesome, but I can't help it.
The Will of Fire brings light to the village.
Well, at least that's what my dad always said.
Maybe someday you'll illuminate the village to, Asuma!
Nah...
There's no need to worry about Shikamaru!
He's fighting to avenge Asuma-sensei.
I'm sure he made a foolproof plan before challenging the enemy.
Move!
I can move!
Shit!
Had you devoted your life to Lord Jashin, he might've saved you.
Unfortunately, even if you converted right now...
...he'd never forgive you, asshole!
I don't need your messed-up God's forgiveness!
Kageyose no Jutsu!
(Kageyose no Jutsu: Shadow Summoning Technique)
Y-You bastard...
I still have enough chakra for this.
You son of a bitch!
What're you doing?!
Just wait and see.
What?!
What the hell's going on?!
When did you set this up?!
I had this all prepared before we came out here.
So he wasn't just trying to be the hero and separate me and Kakuzu. He led me out here on purpose!
But that means he planned this out, too!
"You dig two holes when you curse someone."
Do you understand what that means?
Of course not!
When you kill someone with a curse, you'll be killed in return.
Meaning that the curse ends up burying two people.
Your curse killed my teacher.
And you thought you'd get away with it?
That hole is your grave.
I'll never die!
Even if you destroy my body, and I'm left with nothing but my head...
I'll escape somehow, and when I do,
I'll find you and bite your fuckin' throat out!
Huh?
Deer?
This forest is a special part of the Fire Country.
Only people from my clan are permitted to enter.
No one else ever comes here.
My clan will keep you trapped here forever.
You got him, Shikamaru.
Yeah...
I entrust my Will of Fire to you.
Damn you! What the hell were you lighting?!
The Will of Fire.
The powerful will that protects our village.
Goodbye, Sensei.
Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Mass Shadow Clones.
I see. You're the Nine Tails Jinchuuriki.
Please brief us on the enemy's abilities and the situation.
We're up against two members of Akatsuki.
Shikamaru is fighting one, as I said before.
The other one is standing right in front of us.
He's able to split off parts of his body.
Both of those masked creatures can be detached as necessary.
Each one of them has its own heart and is able to maneuver on its own.
Originally, he had five hearts.
We've destroyed two of them, so he's down to three.
...Excuse me?
Basically, we've killed him twice already,
and we have to kill him three more times to beat him.
He's a mid-range fighter and can use high-level
techniques of every element.
No wonder senpai had his hands full.
Naruto!
I heard him loud and clear!
You can't just attack him head on!
You only used shadow clones?
That's not nearly enough, kid.
That fighting style combined with his speed means I need at least three shadow clones to distract him.
He used the clones to get some experience fighting him, then gained their knowledge when they disappeared.
And now he's formulating a plan of attack.
He's learned how to use shadow clones on a whole new level.
Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Three clones?
What is that?
That's some screech...
A-And the chakra's incredible!
What is he doing?
This is as far as I've gotten.
All right, we'll test it by smashing it into my Rasengan.
Get ready!
But, what's supposed to happen?
If your technique's almost complete, then my Rasengan should be completely wiped out.
Now come on!
The Fourth!
What is that technique?!
I can't get hit with that,
or I'm finished.
Fuuton, Rasen-Shuriken!
(Fuuton, Rasen-Shuriken: Wind Element, Spiraling Shuriken)
Teamwork's very important.
I know I'm standing at a dangerous bridge.
But I want to cross over that bridge by myself.
If I can't make it to the other side, I'll never grow up!
So please don't take that bridge away from me!
Next episode: Wind Element, Rasen-Shuriken!
It's cold!
I'm so bored!
How long is Team Eight's order to stay on standby gonna last?
It can't be helped.
After all, Kurenai-sensei's heart has been terribly hurt.
I know! I know, but...
Team Ten's taken off to go avenge Asuma-sensei.
And it looks like Naruto's working hard on developing some new technique.
Naruto-kun's working so hard.
Your face is red.
It's nothing! It's nothing at all...
Whatever.
Anyways, I'm gonna drop by and see Kurenai-sensei on my way home.
Let's go, Akamaru!
K-Kiba-kun, wait up! Kiba-kun!
I'm alone again.
This sky is too vast for a person to live life alone.