So, you're Sora?
I've been waiting for you.
Who are you?
Hurry and come over here, Sora.
Tell me who you are!
And why do you know my name?
Just get over here!
What are you plotting?
Contact
All right jerk, what are you-?
What's that smell?
You can have one, too.
Hot, hot, hot!
A potato?
I got tired of waiting!
I was so bored, I started roasting potatoes!
It's pretty tasty!
Sora, come over here and have one with me.
You said that you were waiting for me, right?
You're hungry, ain'tcha?
Damn, this is good!
It is good!
I know, right?
Help yourself!
I smell something...
Well, we're eating potatoes!
The wind carries the scent...
The scent of dirt from Kitane-sama's coffin.
You lying snake!
Damn you...
You should've just shut up and eaten!
Same goes for you!
Now return the four corpses!
If you don't,
you're gonna get punished!
I've been getting punished since the day I was born.
But oddly enough, I haven't died yet.
Do whatever you want.
Although this really isn't the time to be punishing others.
No, I'll take you up on that.
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Son of a bitch!
What's the matter?
Who is...
...this guy?
Oh, he's already finished?
Perhaps I overdid it.
But...
It's fine if I just wipe away the ashes.
You're mine!
Fuuton, Hanachiri Mai!
(Fuuton, Hanachiri Mai: Wind Element, Falling Petal Dance)
Wind element?
Earth,
fire,
water,
lightning,
and now wind.
She can use techniques for all five elements?
Surprised, are you?
There are many things you still don't know, little boy.
Especially about women.
You can't run away!
I'll teach you all the secrets of my lovely body!
The hell with that!
I don't wanna know anything about you!
Katon, Housenka no Jutsu!
(Katon, Housenka no Jutsu: Fire Element, Mythical Firebird Technique)
Suiton, Ja no Kuchi!
(Suiton, Ja no Kuchi: Water Element, Snake's Mouth)
What the hell's going on?
Oh shi-!
Raiton, Jibashi!
(Raiton, Jibashi: Lightning Element, Electromagnetic Murder)
What's wrong?
Finished already?
Damn you!
You've got guts, kid!
It's about time you showed me...
...your real power!
Enough with the silly toys.
Never mind.
Wait...
What is this?
No... This feeling...
If you wanna see my power that badly,
I'll show you every bit of it!
Now you're talking!
But it's still not complete.
Looks like you're finally ready to get serious.
Save your trash talk for Hell!
That's a good wind!
Juuha Reppuu Shou!
We have to hurry and meet up with everyone!
I'm worried about Naruto and Sora.
Sai?
Sai!
I just got a bit dizzy.
Let's hurry and find Naruto and the others.
It looks like the poison spread through his body more quickly than I expected.
How about it?
"Occasionally showing your vulnerable side brings people together quickly". I read-
If you say, "I read that in a book", I'll clobber you.
The things that are most important aren't written in books.
You have to learn them by experiencing them yourself.
I suppose so...
Where is everyone?
Damn it...
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
The wind stopped? Okay!
What the hell?!
How dare you...?
How dare you kill me?
What? A replacement?
You'll make women weep, boy.
How many years do you think it took me to grow my hair this long?
A woman's hair is her life.
You've wounded my life force...and now you'll pay the price!
I can't move... It's a paralysis technique!
Damn it!
When did you-?!
Now, boy, let's have us a nice hot kiss.
But I'll take your soul as payment.
B-Back off!
Come...
Damn it! Where did that bastard go?!
Huh? What the hell happened?!
Your power happened.
It completely changed the land when you tried to repel my technique.
This is your true strength!
This is...my true strength?
That's right.
That power of yours was a gift from Heaven.
And this was just a taste of it.
Your powers could be a million times greater!
You shouldn't be wasting your time in that crappy temple!
You've gotta think long hard about how you want to use that power!
Quit your babbling.
Will you use it when and as you please?
Or will you surpass your family and village,
and devote yourself to this country, the Fire Country?
I see. I may have ulterior motives,
but I'm confident the same was true of those four.
They cared about the Fire Country, fought for it while they were still alive, and eventually died for it.
I wonder if they'd want to punish me if they realized that I'm trying to use their corpses for the sake of Fire Country.
For the Fire Country...?
That's right.
I'm going to use their power for the Fire Country!
Who the heck are you really?
A man who held you as a baby.
A man...who knows your father!
What did you say?!
Shikei Seppun.
(Shikei Seppun: Execution by Kiss)
What? My chakra's...
Where are we?
Naruto!
What the hell are you doing?!
No, something's not right!
You know my father?
Naruto!
Let go of Naruto!
Are you okay, Sakura?
Captain Yamato!
We won't let you interfere!
Doton, Ganchuurou no Jutsu!
(Doton, Ganchuurou no Jutsu: Earth Element, Earth Pillar Prison)
Damn it!
Wh-What is this evil chakra?!
Fuuka?
Damn you, you slut!
I've got a kaimyou ready for all three of you.
Sora?
What?!
This boy is...
It's him.
I came to save you.
No one asked for your help.
Weren't you the one who called out to me?
The hell I did!
I see. Well, I heard what I heard.
Let's go.
Naruto, Sora, it's too dangerous to fight them! Run for it!
We won't let you!
Looks like we've gotta fight.
It's three to two!
You'll just get in my way, so it's four to one.
Naruto!
What is it?
I don't know!
Sorry for the delay!
Help has arrived!
Chiriku-san!
Chiriku-sama!
So what are you gonna do now?
Wouldn't you say it's time we draw back?
Yeah. It looks like we don't have to buy any more time.
Who was he?
Me, go to Konoha?
We have to return to Konoha.
Considering what's happened, we must report to Hokage-sama and get new orders.
I'm quite sure our team will be the one to continue the mission.
How about it, Sora-kun?
Would you be willing to lend us a helping hand?
As you can see, It's going to take a while for Sai to fully recover.
As someone from the Fire Temple who has protected the hidden tombs,
I'm sure you'll be able to fill in for Sai just fine.
You don't have to try that hard to convince him, ya know.
Naruto!
Pay attention to where we are!
You really will get punished!
I think that seeing the outside world would be good training for you, but it's your decision, Sora.
That trap...
They weren't after Chiriku-san.
In which case, the only other person I can think of is...
Next Episode
Well, I've got to go write up our report, so I'll see you later.
I have to take Sai to the hospital.
Let's go, Sai.
Okay.
Wait a second here!
I have training!
Kakashi-sensei isn't back yet, right?
Show Sora around Konoha.
I don't wanna.
No one wants to hang out with-
Stop complaining!
Please, Naruto.
Sora's a member of our team now!
Next time: Teammate!
So your Rasengan you use was created by the Fourth Hokage-sama!
Yeah! And it's a super-high class A-Rank ninjutsu!
I didn't realize it was such an amazing technique!
Ero-sennin taught it to me!
It sounds simple, but the training was really tough!
First there was chakra rotation training, where I had to make the water inside a balloon rotate until the balloon broke.
Next was power training, where I had to do the same thing but with the air in a rubber ball.
Those things just didn't wanna break!
And then there's the last one!
Then there was the compression training, where I had to compact all the chakra into a small sphere in my palm!
That was hard as hell.
But I came up with a way of doing it by using my shadow clones.
And that's how I was able to master Rasengan!
That's amazing! Just what I'd expect-
Well, you know me!
Okay, okay, that's enough! You're praising me way too much, Sai!