Man, I almost got squashed!
Fuen's traps aren't terribly imaginative, are they?
I can't believe they're this skilled.
Are they going to be more than we can handle?
Did it work?
Nope!
Damn you!
Pointless.
Jumpy little pest...
Doton, Ganban Kyuu!
(Doton, Ganban Kyuu: Earth Element, Bedrock Coffin)
That's that.
I guess I'll at least mark his grave.
That jerk Fuen made me break a sweat...
You overestimate your techniques.
Always confirm your kills.
But what are they trying to do?
After they stole the corpses, they deliberately ran out in the open.
They're after one of our group from Konoha!
If that's the case, is Danzou behind this?
Looks like we're completely trapped in the enemy's technique.
We need to rejoin the others.
I'm sure they've taken shelter somewhere nearby-
You go look for your goon of a partner!
Hey, wait a minute!
It won't make a difference whether we're together or not!
Jeez... Now we're all split up!
I guess I'm not surprised. Not like he's
had teamwork training or anything.
Actually...
Didn't Naruto fail his teamwork classes, too?
Who's there?
Yuck, manual labor.
I was hoping that the traps would work
so I wouldn't have to dirty my hands...
But I guess there's no avoiding it.
Let's do this quickly!
Oh, I'll make it quick!
Here I come!
What the hell are you doing?!
Mmm... The taste of the chakra leaking from your circulatory system...
You have wind element nature, that's pretty rare.
What about it?
Why don't you join my collection?
French or soft, which do you prefer?
Are you talking about food?
Oh, lord... Kissing.
So you mean...
Y-You wanna make out?!
Yes. You're such a naive boy.
Have you not had your first kiss yet?
Don't take me lightly!
Even I have kissing experience!
Although it was a boy...
Oh? Well, it doesn't matter.
We're going to have lots of fun together.
Quit joking around! Like I wanna hook up with you!
Oh dear. I've been rejected.
What's with that chick?
I'm not good with her type.
You can't reject a woman's advances, you know.
You...can't...escape...
N-No! Stop!
Kiss of death.
What?!
You lose! Too bad!
You kiss was a little cold, baby, but those lips were nice and soft!
If you had just stopped resisting, you could've died happy!
So, which one's the real me?
Now you've made me angry.
This isn't a genjutsu.
My blueprints are summoned from another dimension.
Unfortunately for you,
there is no way out.
I'm not stupid enough to fight in terrain created by the enemy.
There's no point in hiding.
My eyes are glued to you.
After all, I've already left my mark on you.
No matter where you run, I can see you!
Did I get away?
I need to hurry and find the others.
So that's the route you've chosen.
They shouldn't have any idea where I am!
Why are there traps wherever I go?
The fun and games end here.
Sorry.
I've been tracking your movements on this blueprint.
Doton, Gansetsukon!
(Doton, Gansetsukon: Earth Element, Rock Staff)
You're finished!
Ninpou, Choujuu Giga!
Gansetsukon!
He got away.
To mock me like that...
And to land a hit on me to boot...
He might actually be decent.
This isn't the time for them to be keeping watch over an old man.
A night messanger?
What is that?
An owl.
I think it might be a Blakiston's Fish Owl.
Why is there an owl here?!
It brought us an urgent message from the Fire Temple.
Apparently Team Kakashi fell into a trap
while chasing after the grave robbers.
You should've told me that first!
I took care of one of them.
Unlike your opponent, mine was a decent fighter.
So he got away?
The labyrinth I've created is absolutely flawless.
They'll never make it out alive.
I wonder.
There are still plenty of other traps.
They'd deserve a huge round of applause
if they make it through all of them.
This stinks like...sulfur?
Looks like it isn't poisonous.
Sai!
Ninpou, Choujuu Giga!
Sai, don't move.
Your arm's broken.
This will hurt a bit, but bear with me.
There we go!
Now to take care of the spider's poison.
It's a weak venom, so there's nothing to worry about.
I'll have it cured in no time.
Um, were you impressed?
You were impressed, weren't you?
That's why you're doing all this.
What's that?
"Self-Sacrifice and How it Works"?
Yes!
It says that when trying to form relationships, sacrificing yourself is very effective, especially when doing it for a woman.
It really does work!
I wonder if I should give it a try with Naruto-kun, too!
Cut it out already!
Your luck ran out the moment you made me angry, boy!
So you're gonna come at me for real now, huh?
That's more like it!
Bring it on!
You think you can kiss all of us?
Katon, Housenka no Jutsu!
(Katon, Housenka no Jutsu: Fire Element, Mythical Firebird Technique)
You are just a boy, after all.
Now, I wonder where the real one's hiding.
Did I get her?
What?!
Damn, what the hell happened?
I know I made contact!
Doton, Iwagakure no Jutsu!
(Doton, Iwagakure no Jutsu: Earth Element, Hiding in Stone Technique)
You're not half bad.
I want that wind chakra of yours even more now.
Are you an immortal or something?!
There's no way you could have been hit
by my Rasengan and not gotten hurt!
Your attacks are so easy to read.
But more importantly, I'm going to make
sure you receive my Kiss of Death this time!
I won't let you get to first base that easily!
But before that, I'm going to shut that
filthy mouth of yours up for good!
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
My, my! You don't have any real skill, do you?
You're using shadow clones again?
Then I'll use...
Suiton, Ja no Kuchi!
(Suiton, Ja no Kuchi: Water Element, Snake's Mouth)
What?
She's used fire, earth and water techniques.
So she can use three elements?
Raiton, Jibashi!
(Raiton, Jibashi: Lightning Element, Electromagnetic Murder)
What?! Lightning?!
She can use four?!
What the-?
Who're you?
So you're Sora.
I've been waiting for you.
Damn it, why are women such a mystery?
"A woman's hair is her life?!"
Like I give a rat's ass!
But I can't believe this chick can manipulate her
chakra to use earth, fire, water, lightning and wind!
She's got all five elements!
But my wind won't lose to hers!
I'll show off the fruits of my hard training!
Hey, wait a second.
I still don't know any Wind Element techniques!
Next time: Contact!
I'm fine, thanks!
That looks heavy!
Captain Yamato, what brings you here?
I came to turn in my mission report.
Then, could you put it on top of this stack?
Do you need a hand?
Excuse us!
I never thought there would be so much paperwork!
Please certify and stamp all of these mission reports, as well!
Sheesh, give me a break, Shizune!
No time! After these, you have to go over
Ninja Registrations, mission information,
have a meeting with your top aides,
another meeting with the feudal lord...
All right, all right!
Hokage-sama, your job is very difficult, isn't it?
Only because everyone bothers me about everything.
The worst part is babysitting the councilors!