So, how is Naruto's training going?
According to Kakashi-sensei, he's making good progress.
But it'll take a little longer until he's perfected the technique.
I see.
Kakashi-sensei went with Team Ten because Team Seven works well with them, and he thinks we should be their backup, right?
Very perceptive.
But we don't know when, or even if, Naruto-kun will complete his technique...
Perhaps we should send a different squad?
Sakura! Tell this to Yamato.
Naruto has twenty-four hours to complete his technique.
If he doesn't, I'll send another team as backup.
Yes!
Shizune, if Naruto doesn't finish in time, I'll need you to check the schedules and organize the team that will best compliment Team Ten.
Understood.
And so it begins...
Shikamaru, let's hear your plan first.
Sure, I just have to change it a little to account for you, Kakashi-sensei.
Right. Whenever you're ready.
I'll break it down into several different scenarios and explain each one.
Things will vary depending on what happens, so I need you to remember them all.
Kakashi-sensei and Team Ten went after Akatsuki?
Yeah, they just left.
I see. And what did Tsunade-sama say?
That we're best suited to be their backup.
But she won't let us go unless Naruto completes his new technique.
My new technique...
If you can't do it within twenty-four hours, she'll send another squad backup instead.
Twenty-four hours, huh?
Naruto?
You shouldn't eat-
Naruto...
Captain Yamato, let's keep training!
Kakashi-sensei, take this.
Use it when you see an opening.
I'm counting on you.
Got it.
I've gotta hand it to you. You've learned a great deal about the enemy for having only encountered them once.
There's still a lot we don't know about the other one, unfortunately.
To be able to come up with a new strategy so quickly after I joined the squad... Very impressive.
Those are all the strategies I have based on the information I've gathered.
Once you've memorized our simulations,
replay each one in your head at least three times.
Our probability of success depends on whether or not you commit them to memory.
Okay!
Ready to go?
Yes!
First, we have to pick up their trail.
Trail?
I see! We'll search the path they took from the Fire Temple to the exchange point!
We have to look for any remaining footprints or scents, right?
I doubt we'll find anything quickly, though.
Well then, let's get a move on.
Yes!
The sealing of the Two-Tails is complete.
Only four more remain.
Dismissed.
Finally!
Time to head to Konoha, Hidan.
Did you say Konoha?
Kakuzu, Hidan, if you're going to Konoha, let me warn you.
The Jinchuuriki Uzumaki Naruto lives there. Watch yourselves if you run into him.
Whoa, whoa! Don't put me in the same boat as you, Deidara-chan!
I'm not the little pussy who had to get his arms reattached by Kakuzu!
Better the arms than the head.
Hey, fuck you, Kakuzu! Who's side are you on?
We're supposed to be partners!
Why do you always-
Shut up, Hidan.
Come on.
Sitting still for three days sucked.
Time to let loose.
Just you wait, bounty guy.
Kakuzu, where the hell're you going? The exchange point's this way, right?
Are you brain dead?
Say what?!
Our target is the Jinchuuriki.
Just because we said we'd be back doesn't mean we're required to waltz right into an ambush.
We'll take a different route to Konoha.
It's been three days. The bounty's probably been sent back to Konoha.
Yeah, I guess he would've been.
That reminds me...
Wh-What now?
That wound on your neck is ugly. Cover it up.
Hey, my forehead protector!
Wow, you actually picked it up for me?
Kakuzu, you can be a nice guy when you try!
Shut up, Hidan!
Come on!
Hey! Wait a sec!
Yo, Kakuzu!
You may act like a prick, but you really like me, don't you?
Keep talking and I will kill you.
Aw, don't get shy on me...
Well, there's no trail left because of the rain.
So, what do we do?
Any plans we come up with are pointless if we can't find the enemy.
Come to think of it...
We'll be right back, so make sure you're ready.
We told you to stay here until we get back!
That's what they said, right?
But, they wouldn't return to the same spot.
There should be two squads watching the exchange point...
It wouldn't be a problem if we were only dealing with the loud one, but he's with that other guy.
Even if they take a different route, their destination and targets are the same.
Stealing Asuma's corpse to collect the bounty, and capturing Naruto, a Jinchuuriki.
They're heading for Konoha.
That narrows the area we need to search.
How do you propose we find them?
We'll use that.
Got it!
Found them!
No doubt about it, they're heading straight for Konoha!
Oh no!
You okay, Ino?
That was close...
Did they notice?
I think we're okay.
They're definitely taking a different route towards Konoha!
Both of them are at 2 o'clock, ten minutes from here.
What'sa matter, Kakuzu?
Nothing.
Just my imagination.
Then move your ass!
All right, let's go.
Hidan...
I know.
Shit!
Explosive tags?
Kakuzu!
I hardened my arm, I didn't get hurt!
More importantly, watch out for that shadow.
Like I'll fall for the same thing again!
Hidan, above you!
More explosive tags.
Hidan, dodge!
It's not exploding!
He got us.
Shuriken Shadow Mimic...successful.
I can't move!
Bastard...
Your shadow never touched us. How'd you-
Those knives I threw at you are chakra blades.
I'm sure you're familiar with them.
They're made from a special metal that lets them absorb their user's elemental chakra.
Kakuzu, what the hell's this dick talking about?!
Moron. Just shut up, Hidan.
Using the chakra they absorb, their wielder can use them as a base for his techniques.
But all you need to know is that I'm using my Shadow Mimic through the blades.
They're mementos from Asuma, the man you two murdered!
Huh?
The 35 million ryou?
Asuma!
If Konoha's shinobi were shogi pieces, I'd say you'd be a knight, Shikamaru.
Why?
It doesn't have much traditional strength,
but it can jump over its enemies to move forward.
That unique ability is similar to how quickly you adapt your thought process.
I see.
So these explosive tags are fakes.
Ordinary pieces of paper.
He was aiming to trap us with the chakra blades from the start.
He used real explosive tags on the kunai to make sure we'd dodge the chakra blades he threw next.
On top of that, he used his shadow to make sure we'd focus on the ground,
so that we'd barely notice his attack from the air and have almost no time to avoid it.
That gave him all he needed to stab our shadows.
He's very smart.
Now, it's time to end this.
Why the hell are you being so quiet?!
You had to go and get yourself caught too, didn't you!
Oh man, oh man, we're screwed, aren't we?!
Oh, you're screwed. According to my plan, the second I captured you, it was over.
He got them.
You little bitch...
Damn it, what're you gonna do now?!
I'm not gonna make the same mistake twice in a row.
You two are about to be cornered!
You guys fucked up on the order.
I'll make sure to target the right guy first this time.
Shit...
I've got your face memorized.
I'm gonna destroy you, if it's the last thing I do!
Not the sharpest knife in the drawer, are you?
Kakuzu, duck!
Nice!
What happened?
I never imagined his arms could still move on their own after being detached!
But when did he...?
When I threw the explosive tags?
He hid in the smoke long enough to send his right arm underground!
He's a true blue Akatsuki. Their abilities are all out of this world!
You said we were finished, but you still had no idea what I was capable of.
So you kept your distance and came up with a new strategy.
You actually think, unlike my partner.
But even if you analyze every aspect of a battle, things don't always go according to plan.
Kakuzu! What the fuck was that "unlike my partner" bullshit?!
Exactly what it sounded like, moron.
Damn it! My body-!
Kakuzu, do something!
You're forcing me back!
Shit!
Now, Chouji!
Nikudan Harisensha!
(Nikudan Harisensha: Spiked Meat Tank)
Kakuzu!
What the hell is going on?
Why?!
It looked like Kakashi-sensei's attack hit him!
Yeah, there's no question!
I know his heart was destroyed, but...
What's on his back?!
I feel a really awful chakra coming from there!
I'm getting a really bad vibe from him.
Be careful, Chouji!
Right!
So this is Kakuzu!
Looks like there's more to him than meets the eye.
Next time: Kakuzu's Ability.
Now, we're going to go over your criminal charges.
But first you're going to tell me who you are.
And about this man you've made contact with.
Tell me everything you know about him.
I ain't sayin' nothin'.
Well, I tried asking nicely.
Now we do things my way.