Just a dream...
What was that?
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
must be expressed with words.
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
aoi aoi ano sora
to that blue, blue sky
The fastest way to get others to understand you...
...is to close the distance between yourselves.
For example, honorific suffixes.
By adding "-kun" or "-san" to a person's name,
you project an air of being polite, but
reserved, and the gap does not shrink.
Have the courage to simply call them by their name,
or even come up with a nickname or pet name.
By doing so, you become special to
them and a lasting friendship will form.
Makes sense.
There it is!
Hey, Sai's here.
Looking at an art book?
Sakura-san.
Oh, you're reading!
Just a bit...
I guess even Sai acts normal sometimes...
Naruto and I are going to visit Kakashi-sensei. You wanna come, too?
Kakashi-sensei...
You're a member of team Kakashi now.
You should at least introduce yourself.
My revenge is everything to me.
As long as I can exact it, I don't care what happens to me or anyone else.
If sacrificing my body to Orochimaru is the only way to kill him,
I'd give up my life a million times over.
I can see it now.
So this is the source of your hidden powers.
I never would've thought you'd have something like this inside of you.
Why am I dreaming about that?
Naruto!
Ah man... Sai's coming, too?
I bumped into him at the library.
Damn it! I planned this out so it'd just be the two of us, like a date!
Jeez! If you've got enough time to think up
stuff like that, go study some ninjutsu!
Bah, studying...
I can't believe you guys go to the library. It's so lame...
Naruto, you don't just need to train physically, but mentally, too!
You're a complete dunce!
Ah ha. Sakura-san doesn't use any honorifics with Naruto-kun.
Sakura-chan, that was harsh.
N-Naruto... S-Sakura...
May I join your conversation?
Uh, you see, I was reading about how to open up to people...
And it said to try dropping honorifics, or use a nickname.
By doing so, you can become friends faster and easier.
What? That's what you're so nervous about?
Then that book you had earlier...
I was trying to come up with nicknames for both of you.
But I couldn't think of any,
so I thought dropping the honorifics was good enough.
I can't believe Sai's taking this so seriously.
You don't decide on nicknames, they just kinda happen!
They usually have something to do with
the person's traits or characteristics.
Like, take Naruto.
"Naruto the Idiot" or "Naruto the Jerk" fit him perfectly.
Sakura-chan, you're killing me!
Traits... I see.
Sai's changed so much since we first met him.
You don't have to stare at me like that!
Thanks. I think I get it now,
Ugly.
Damn you!
Sai, you're killing me!
I am? How?
Sakura-chan, why'd you hit me, too?
So you're the new team member...Sai, right?
Nice to meet you.
Yes, sir.
Come here, Sakura.
I see they've got some scratches. Did they get in a fight already?
I know Naruto well enough to not be surprised, but...
No, it's not that.
Honestly, we get along very well!
Oh, I see. Well, that's good.
So this is the fabled Hatake Kakashi we heard about in Root.
Naruto...
Kakashi-sensei, while we were on our mission-
Yamato told me about everything, including Sasuke.
We're running out of time!
At this rate, he'll...
We can't bring Sasuke back, not like we are now.
He's too strong.
Then, you just need to become even stronger, right?
From what I saw, he's gotten so strong, so fast, it was unbelievable.
I asked Tsunade-sama, she said he's
probably learning forbidden techniques.
And considering he's got Kabuto behind
him, probably using special drugs as well.
Just reading isn't going to help me understand
people who experiment on human beings.
Then we'll have to get strong in an
unbelievably short amount of time, too.
But how?
You think I've just been lying around doing nothing?
I've been mulling over this the whole time
I've been here. And I've finally got an idea.
But the training's more suited for Naruto.
Or more accurately, Naruto's the only one suited for it.
Naruto, if this works, you may, in a sense, even surpass me.
Me surpass you?
Yes.
I'll be working with you the whole time,
but it'll be unlike any training you've done before.
Wh-What'll we be doing?
You're going to learn the most powerful
technique you can do by creating it yourself.
Meaning you're going to learn a technique
more powerful than Rasengan.
But to do so, you'll need to invest a
massive amount of time and effort.
It's not like those stories where the main
character gets ridiculously strong in a few days.
And it's also going to be different from
Rasengan, which someone else created,
and which you learned through careful instruction.
Massive amounts of time...
But we don't have time! Sasuke's-!
Relax. I figured out how we can do it in no time at all.
How?
Well, we-
How ya doing, Kakashi?
Asuma-sensei! Would you at least knock first?!
Heggo!
If it isn't Naruto and Sakura!
You already finished your mis-?
You're that guy...
Wh-Who?
Why did this have to happen today?
Okay, relax... Start with a smile...
Hi there.
Good job on your report.
Thank you. I'll take my leave, then.
Akatsuki is finally starting to get serious.
It's only a matter of time before they target Konoha.
It's definitely a dangerous situation,
but it's also our chance to take them out.
We need to get serious, too.
Oh, so that's what you were doing.
All right, good enough for me.
You can just call me Sai.
Don't worry about any suffixes.
He's kinda cute, isn't he?
He reminds me of Sasuke-kun...
Physically, yeah. But he's nothing like him.
He's totally clueless.
I heard about Sasuke from Tsunade-sama.
I can help you out the next time something comes up,
now that that stupid Chuunin exam's finally over.
I figured you'd make Chuunin easily this time, too.
Yeah...
Ah well, maybe next time.
So why're you all here?
This isn't a lounge.
True, true.
You guys go on ahead to the barbecue.
Team Kakashi's invited to join you, too.
Yeah, barbecue!
I'm in!
I call the seat next to Sai-kun!
Kakashi and I have a few things to discuss.
It's my treat, so no objections, right?
Hey, hold up!
What were you gonna say? About the training?
What's the training?
Oh yeah...
We'll have to save it for later.
Later? But I wanna know now!
Look, we can't start while I'm still in the hospital.
Don't be so hasty.
Hurry up, Sakura-chan!
Huh? Where's Shikamaru?
He said he had to go home and help his dad
collect deer antlers for making medicine.
He's always right on time for meetings about missions and stuff...
Weird!
She mustn't have heard my warning.
Sweet, I call his share!
Chouji! At least introduce yourself to Sai-kun first!
O-Oh, right...
Word is the other villages are gearing up, too.
So it's true...
If they're after the Bijuu, they'll clearly
target the village. Well, Naruto, at any rate.
You don't have to leave me out.
I'm concerned about Akatsuki's movements, too.
Will Naruto be all right?
I mean, they even took out Gaara. If they come after him...
He wouldn't stand a chance.
Not yet.
Hello.
First impressions are extremely important to friendships.
I have to come up with a nickname right away, or else...
Um, I'm Akimichi Chouji from the Akimichi
clan. Nice to meet you. Sai, right?
Nice to meet you, um...
Traits, characteristics...
Oh, no!
He wouldn't... Not that...
Fa-
Sai, never ever ever say the word "fatty" in front of Chouji, got it?!
Were you gonna say something?
No, nothing at all!
Oh!
Coming up with nicknames is hard work...
And I'm Yamanaka Ino, from the Yamanaka Florists!
It's such a pleasure to meet you!
Damn you!
If you simply use a girl's actual traits for a nickname, they get mad.
So perhaps if I try the opposite, that won't happen.
Don't do it, Sai...
Do it, Sai!
Teach her a lesson!
Nice to meet you, uh...
Um...
...gorgeous.
Why does Ino get to be gorgeous?!
S-Stop, Sakura!
Rat, Sheep, Monkey, Rabbit, Rabbit, Bird, Ox, Ox, Monkey...
Rat, Sheep, Dragon, Rabbit, Rabbit, Horse, Rabbit, Horse...
Tiger, Ox, Bird, Boar, Boar, Rat, Rat...
Bird, Rabbit, Rabbit, Horse, Dog...
Bird, Dragon, Snake, Dragon, Monkey...
Dragon.
Wrong one, eh?
Kodomo no koro mita niji wo
If I look up now for the rainbow I saw as a boy,
ima miageru to nana iro de wa naku
there are no longer the seven colors,
Yagate kiri ga kakari
only mist and fog...
Jikan wa sugi kawatte yuku
As time passes by, and the world around me changes,
Kimi wo sagashitemo doko ni mo inai
no matter where I search for you, you're nowhere to be found.
Me wo toji, kokoro hiraite
So I close my eyes, and open my heart...
mata nagamete mitemo nanimo kawaranai no ka
I need to know, if I gaze up again,
tashikamete mitai
will things be different this time?
Sunao ni narereba kono kiri ga hareru to
Maybe if I was more honest, the fog would fade away.
kokoro ni negai sou sakenderu
So I pray, screaming that wish deep within my soul.
Nanika wo nakushiteshimatta koto de sou
When you lose one thing,
te ni shita mono mo kitto arun darou
you gain another, don't you?
Dakedo mada bokura wa otona ni tomadoi
But still, no matter how often the adults confuse us,
ikite yuku sube sagashiteru
we'll keep looking for the right way to live our lives.
It's almost time.
For what?
Naruto's new training.
I wonder how long it'll take.
Kakashi-senpai claimed to have a brilliant idea.
Don't get soft!
Naruto's the kid even Jiraiya had trouble handling!
This'll be a true test of Kakashi's skill.
The next episode of Naruto Shippuuden,
Wind, airs Thursday 4/17 at 7:30 PM!
Wind
Hey, Chouji.
This is my meat, got it?
It belongs to whomever's faster.
That's why I was going to call you f-
Sai, I just told you never to call him that!
What was that?
Nothing, nothing.
I cooked a piece for you, Sai-kun! Here!
That was mine!
Stop acting like such a bimbo, Ino.
It's sickening.
Sickening?!
Ah ha! You just want Sai-kun for yourself!
Forehead Girl!
Who's a forehead girl, Ino-Pig?!
I'm not interested in Sai-
Pig?! Why you little-!
Come on, Sakura-chan, take it easy-
Stay out of this, stupid Naruto!
Wha-?! Stupid?!
Cut it out, Ino.
Clam it, fatty!
I am not fat!
I'm just husky!
Nikudan Sensha!
(Nikudan Sensha: Meat Bullet Tank)
Coming up with nicknames is so hard...