Asuma...
Uncle Asuma...
Where's Shikamaru?
His mom said he already left...
Hey! I've told you a million times not to play up on the roof!
Sorry.
Okay...
Hi, Shikamaru!
Oh, hello.
I haven't seen you around lately.
You been busy?
Kinda...
Come on by sometime!
Say hi to Asuma-sensei and Chouji-kun for me.
Oh, yeah! One of these days I need to call in your sensei's tab!
U-Um, Asuma...
He died in the line of duty.
Then the person they said died yesterday was...
How horrible...
Shikamaru.
Dinner's almost ready.
No thanks. I'm not really hungry.
Shikamaru...
Come hang out with me.
You're being unusually careless today.
You won't beat me like that.
Shut up.
Akatsuki, huh?
Are they strong?
Yep.
So, what're you going to do?
I guess if a man of Asuma's caliber couldn't beat them, you wouldn't stand a chance.
He was a hell of a guy.
Yeah.
Terrible Shogi player, though.
You okay with that?
Don't nag me about how I play.
Not that!
What do you want to do now?
At least I know you're not stupid enough
to play into enemy hands and die.
As your father, I'm grateful for that.
I don't want to attend my son's funeral.
You're doing well.
I'm proud to be your father.
You're smart and talented.
Someone Konoha can depend on in the future.
But...
Asuma's dead.
What're you getting at?!
I'm speaking my mind.
Your prattling is making me sick to my stomach!
I'm nothing but a useless coward!
No.
Then what is it?!
Let it out.
Let out all the sadness, fear and anger that's building up inside of you.
That's the first step.
I'll pick up the pieces.
Hey!
Shikamaru!
Hello.
It must have been so horrible for you.
I can't believe what happened to Asuma!
I don't know what to say...
It's so sad.
Shikamaru.
Darling?
You're here to see Chouji, right?
He's up on the mountain behind our house.
You made another huge hole there!
Shikamaru!
Your mom told me to give this to you.
So, when is it?
We're gonna do it, right? What do you want me to do?
Don't tell me I'm not...
Can I get you to take care of something for me right now?
Shikamaru!
We're doing this, right?
Thank you.
Sorry I'm late.
But...I'm no longer lost about what to do.
What we're about to do might be completely insane,
but you'll watch over us, won't you?
Asuma-sensei...
Asuma...sensei.
We're ready.
Let's go, Shikamaru!
Yeah!
Freeze!
The Fifth?
Where do you think you're going?
Your orders are still in effect.
We regrouped with different team members and are going to continue our mission.
I don't tolerate selfishness!
Shikamaru, I'll add you to a platoon I've organized personally.
And I'll deploy you once we've come up with a sound plan.
Just send them as backup later.
I've already got a plan worked out for the three of us.
Enough!
Asuma is dead.
It's just the three of you now!
Asuma is still with us.
You're putting revenge before common sense?!
This isn't like you at all.
You'll be throwing your lives away.
We're not stupid enough to go out there planning to die.
It's just...
It's just...what?
If I let it go like this, I'd live the rest of my life regretting it.
And I can't think of a more troublesome way to live.
Grow up.
Shinobi will always be surrounded by death.
Some deaths are harder to deal with than others...
But you have no future if you can't get over them!
Carrying this lighter that Asuma-sensei gave me,
I feel like Asuma-sensei's nearby. That he's watching us...
That he's protecting us.
This lighter stays with me until I've settled things.
Get real!
There are only three of you!
Platoons are a four-man cell-
So you just need a fourth member, correct?
Kakashi-sensei?
I'll serve as captain for Team Ten.
How's that sound?
Kakashi, what are...?
They're going to go anyway.
If you assign me as their captain, I'll keep an eye on them,
and make sure they don't do anything drastic.
Fine. Do what you want!
Yes!
Kakashi-sensei, is Naruto gonna be okay?
Your right arm...
Yep! Naruto doesn't need me around anymore.
So, I left him with another captain.
Naruto...
Okay, Team Asuma, ready to move?
Yeah!
Thanks a million, Kakashi-sensei.
It's time to go after Akatsuki.
First, let's hear your plan, Shikamaru.
Sure, I just have to change it a little to account for you, Kakashi-sensei.
Right. Whenever you're ready.
I'll break it down into several different situations and explain them.
Things will vary depending on the situation, so I need you guys to memorize all of them.
Roger.
Next week: Locked On Target.