The battle with Akatsuki has finally begun.
Hidan's ability is revealed to everyone.
The team struggles in their fight against an amazingly powerful opponent.
With the situation growing desperate, Asuma tries to break through enemy lines, and his comrades can only watch.
With Shikamaru backing him up, he managed to pull off an explosive combo attack.
And Hidan was engulfed in the blast.
Hurts, doesn't it?
God has judged you.
Wh-What's going on?!
Do you get it now?
Do you understand what it means to suffer?
He got my arm, too?
This must be one of his techniques or something...
No!
You're already under my curse.
Now the ceremony can begin.
Now...
We'll suffer the unfathomable pain together!
You're already under my curse.
Now the ceremony can begin.
Now we'll suffer the unfathomable pain together!
Why did Captain Asuma get burned, too?
Didn't his fire technique hit the enemy?
Yeah, it definitely hit him.
But for some odd reason it hit Captain Asuma, too!
You're kidding me...
This'll make another 35 million ryou for us.
I've got everything set up!
Get ready, this's gonna hurt like hell!
Suck on this!
Hurts good, doesn't it?!
But it's nothin' like hitting an organ!
Man, that shit is the best!
As the other dies, his agony radiates through my body!
And living through it is pure ecstasy!
Captain Asuma's holding his left leg...
Something's definitely wrong here!
That guy stabbed himself in the same leg!
Then why?!
You're already under my curse.
I get it!
I see.
He's somehow managed to link our bodies together.
In other words, if I attack him, I'll get hurt, too.
But...he can't be killed.
Where do ya want it next?
How 'bout here? Or here?
Getting it in both legs would be pretty sweet.
Or...
...should I just end it now?!
Shikamaru, don't use a physical attack like your Shadow Sewing!
Use the Shadow Neck Bind to keep him from moving! Hurry!
I'm already trying!
Make it...
Please be in time!
Now you die!
I don't think so!
Nice job, Shikamaru!
This's nothing.
Izumo, how long has it been since you called for back-up?
Only about ten minutes. It'll take at least another twenty for them to get here.
I see.
Damn it! What do we do?!
If we kill him, we kill Captain Asuma.
Techniques like this usually remain in effect until the user releases them or gets killed.
But that's not an option.
Every technique has some kind of risk, or restrictions on its use. There's gotta be a loophole.
I've gotta calm down and analyze him carefully.
Shikamaru bought me some time.
I have to use this opportunity to figure out how to undo this technique!
His Shadow Neck Bind won't last long on an enemy of this caliber. I've only got a little time left to think!
If it's gonna take much longer, I'll kill them myself.
I'm not letting all that money get away.
I told you to back the fuck off, Kakuzu!
I can handle these pussies on my own!
We're beyond lucky that this other guy hasn't attacked us,
especially considering the situation we're in.
Even so, what on earth should we do?
I guess it's just a matter of time.
That guy...
That's right. Think back!
I came here prepared to fight enemies with abilities, didn't I?
Akatsuki had ten official members.
But Orochimaru abandoned them.
Sasori of the Red Sands is dead.
There are only three others that we know anything about.
Hoshigaki Kisame, who apparently took on Gai-sensei with ease.
He uses water techniques?
Sasuke's older brother...
...the Sharingan user, Uchiha Itachi.
A man who in one second put Kakashi-san in the hospital for over a week.
And the guy Naruto fought, Deidara. He used explosive clay bombs that he controlled remotely.
He died trying to suicide-bomb them?
Sounds fishy to me.
There're still five other members of Akatsuki.
And not a single one listed in this file is normal.
Taking time to study their techniques won't even scratch the surface.
I'd bet anything the remaining five have special abilities beyond my or anyone's imagination.
Crap, these guys are ridiculous.
Trying to come up with a strategy beforehand is totally pointless.
I'm gonna have to figure out how to handle them during battle.
So, how do I prepare?
Obviously, I'll train and try to get stronger.
But what should I do if I come across an opponent I just can't beat?
The enemies' abilities...
Analyze them, get the upper hand...
Ninjutsu, taijutsu, genjutsu...
Determine which type the person is.
Since they're two-man teams, it's possible they'll use combo attacks.
Consider how their abilities complement one another.
So I'll have to make judgments the moment I learn something about them.
And against someone like Akatsuki, they probably won't give me time to figure anything out.
Akatsuki, eh?
A-Asuma?
Are you already trying to come up with strategies to use against Akatsuki?
Nope. I've just reached the conclusion that it's impossible.
Not for you.
I bet you'd come up with a strategy the second you got any information on them at all.
Assuming I get any information in the first place.
Even that'd be difficult if we went up against Akatsuki head-on.
They could kill me in an instant.
Yeah, I suppose.
It sucks, but these guys are something else.
That's only if you were fighting an Akatsuki one-on-one.
Your abilities to analyze and make decisions under pressure are considered some of Konoha's best.
If you can't find time to do that in a one-on-one fight, then ask your friends for help.
You have a responsibility to your team, but if you're unable to rely on your teammates, then you're not fulfilling that responsibility.
There will be times when you'd be toast on your own, but with your comrades' help, things will work out.
Just saying things will work out isn't good enough.
Then you figure it out!
And do it before your friends get killed.
Asuma's given me tons of information!
Think, think!
His speech, personality, tone...
The things he carries...
Consider everything he's done up to now.
What those actions mean...
...and how they're related to one-another.
That will tell me how and why his technique works, and the way to counter it.
God will smite assholes like you!
God...smite...
You're already under my curse.
Now the ceremony can begin.
Curse...ceremony...
I've got everything set up!
Set up...
Shikamaru's got an idea.
Did you figure something out, Shikamaru?
Yeah.
How can he think so clearly when he's gotta focus that hard on keeping his technique going?
Shikamaru can think ten steps ahead and consider 200 possible moves in a second.
But his real strength is his knack for choosing the best one.
Get ready, Captain Asuma.
That shadow technique forces the target to mimic the user's movements...
Damn it, he knows...
What're you doing?
I'm forcing him out of that weird symbol he drew on the ground.
If I get him out, then his technique, that curse, will be negated!
What on earth are you talking about?
That big scythe of his has three blades on it.
The design suggests it's meant to broaden the attack area rather than kill to deal a one-hit kill.
It doesn't matter if it's a serious wound or a minor one, their only purpose is to draw blood.
Basically, as long as he lands one attack,
he can use that technique to kill his opponent.
You mean the curse?
But how are injuring the enemy and the curse related?
The blood.
In order to form a link with the person he wants to curse, he has to ingest that person's blood.
I saw him lick off the blood, too.
I get it.
He just needs to open a wound, get a little blood on his scythe, and use it to curse his opponent.
I see!
His body changed colors after he swallowed the blood...
That was easy to notice.
But there's more.
There's one other condition for activating the curse, but it was pretty obvious, too.
There's more?
This kid's pretty smart.
Earlier, he rushed over to that symbol he drew on the ground even though it meant running through Asuma's fire technique, remember?
And as soon as he was standing inside the diagram,
he said he was gonna start the ceremony and screamed about how everything was set up.
I determined that his curse technique was only ready once he entered the circle.
You piece of shit...
You talk too much.
He figured all that out...
You little bitch!
After I get free I'm gonna slash, bash and smash your ass!
There won't be an after for you!
He's out!
Right! Let's see if the curse has been lifted!
Yes!
Damn you...
I'm trapped!
I'm wiped out.
I don't think I can hold him much longer.
Good work, Shikamaru.
Kakuzu, help me!
Now! Hurry the fuck up!
I told you not to underestimate them.
Didn't you tell me you thought your room was a bit bare?
I may have...
Ino recommended these, hope you like them.
They're supposed to be poppy seeds.
Thanks for the thought, but I'm sure I'd kill them.
She said they aren't too hard to manage.
But...
Well, plant them if you feel like it.
He dumped them on me...
He said to plant them if I felt like it, but I can't just leave them like this...
Let's see... Poppies...poppies...
In the language of flowers they mean "to comfort someone."
H-He did it!
He did it!
We got him...
Sheesh, talk about your close calls.
We would've been completely wiped out if it hadn't been for Shikamaru's analytical abilities.
God, he's amazing!
No wonder Asuma-san's so confident in him.
Shikamaru, are you okay?!
Yeah. Now there's just one left...
Just him, huh?
If you needed a hand, you should've asked me earlier.
Fuck you and your slow ass!
You let that happen!
I believe before this all started you said,
"Just shut the fuck up and watch, Kakuzu!"
Now, as a goddamned head, do you still think you can yell at me?
Uh... Okay, yes, I did tell you not to get involved.
But it's not like I was trying to embarrass you or make you look bad.
Whatever, man. C'mon and get my body!
Kakuzu, would you mind bringing my body over here?
Kakuzu-chan, pretty please? With sugar on top?
H-Hey! W-Wait! Cut it out!
Kakuzu, my body! Bring my body here, damn it!
Your head's lighter.
That's not the issue!
Are you ignoring me?!
Ow, ow! You're ripping my hair out!
If you're going to whine about pain, at least complain about your neck.
You stupid dick! My neck isn't even in the same league!
This isn't some tiny little boo-boo, asshole!
Even beheaded, he's still alive?!
This fucking hurts like hell!
You cut my goddamned head off! This's like, hyper-mega-ultra pain!
What the hell? What is this?
I... There's just no way to explain this...
It doesn't matter if he's still alive, not in that state.
Without being attached to his body, he can't move or use any techniques.
He may be immortal, but in that condition, he can't actually do anything.
That's true.
One down, one to go.
Right.
But even so,
he's probably stronger and faster than that immortal bastard.
He's also calm enough to not fight if he doesn't think he has to.
And he's so cruel and heartless that seeing his friend get his head chopped off didn't even faze him.
I can't discern his true power from that, not yet.
Then again, he's so confident that I bet we haven't even seen it.
This is the type of enemy that calculates the gap between his and his opponent's strength first.
So the best thing we can do is demonstrate that we've got the upper hand.
Shikamaru!
Shikamaru's exhausted.
And Captain Asuma's injured.
We've gained the upper hand by disabling one of the Akatsuki, but...
But it also means we've given ourselves a chance to escape.
I'm just worried about Shikamaru if we try...
We can't give him an opening!
Get real.
Captain Asuma!
Now that I've helped you,
I'm gonna have to stay involved.
Yeah, whatever.
Sit still, you baby.
He's...
What is he doing?
There.
His head...
...got reattached!
All back together again.
Watch the stitches, they'll break if you move too much.
You know what, Kakuzu? Eat a dick.
What on earth are we fighting?
Now we've got a man who can't die and a man who can sew severed body parts back on like nothing.
Shit!
It's just one thing after another!
They trump us no matter what we do.
Your stupid ceremony is bad enough, but I'm sick of you dragging fights out with your blabbering.
You take care of the bounty.
Right. I'm gonna get him for what he did.
I can't go breaking the commandments, now can I?
That again? Whatever.
I'll take the other three.
Izumo!
On it!
All right!
Suiton, Mizuame Nabara!
(Suiton, Mizuame Nabara: Water Element, Syrup Snare Field)
Yes!
Did we get him?
I assume this was a combo where you force the enemy to focus on the flashy aerial attack, creating an opening.
Then you attack from the ground with this strange liquid.
So simplistic.
Too much wasted movement.
Now!
What?!
Okay!
When did he...?
Way to go, Izumo!
You're mine!
Kotetsu!
Shi-!
Wasting my time with your flailing...
Man, looks like Kakuzu's already done.
I'd better get moving, too.
Otherwise he'll bitch at me about my ritual taking forever.
Bye.
Asuma! Behind you!
You won't get me with the same trick-
It wasn't the same, you retard!
Damn it...
Shit!
You... You said you wouldn't...
You're sacrificing yourself to protect your comrades!
I'm not convinced.
Why won't this plan work?
If my Shadow Sewing is successful, it'll bind one of the enemies and halve their fighting potential!
But if I'm going to connect from far away, we'll need to set a trap.
Shadow Sewing gets weaker the further I am from the target.
But if I use it at close range, the restraining power will increase, along with our chances for success!
That's what this strategy does, right?
A two-man lead placing you at the front next to me and my blades, so you can use Shadow Sewing as close as possible.
Exactly, that'd give me the best chance of snaring the enemies.
Shikamaru. I can't stress enough how highly I value your insight.
Then why?
That's why we can't do it.
Everyone in this group is a superb ninja.
We're a four-man cell comprised of three chuunin and a jounin,
but I have a superior tactician in my squad that no one else has.
You, Shikamaru.
The tactician bases his platoon's movements on the rear guard's situation.
We rely on your judgment to make the right moves.
But I need to make sure we're using our group's assets properly.
If you're out on the front line, it puts the mission's success at risk.
I...
I know how painful it is to lose a comrade!
That's why this's the best strategy!
I'm aware of the risks!
But if it means I can protect my comrades...
If by comrades you mean this group, then you don't understand.
What we're protecting... The real reason we fight...
If you still don't understand, then there's no way I can put you out in front.
It's my fault! If...
If I'd just thought of a better plan...
...this wouldn't be happening!
Don't you get it?! That's the best strategy we've got right now!
I've never seen Asuma get like this.
It's like sending in a single unit to break through enemy lines.
Sometimes, that's the only move you have!
You aren't cut out to be the Climbing Silver.
I won't end up a sacrificial piece.
Not with you behind me.
Shit... Shit!
It's my fault.
It's all my fault!
If I wasn't such a moron, this wouldn't have happened to Asuma!
So? Does it hurt?
Does it fucking hurt?!
Finally...
I'll finally be able to experience the pain!
The pain that comes with killing you!
Captain...
Damn it!
It's over.
No!
Asuma...
So wonderful...
Asuma!
Don't bother trying to heal me.
I'm done for.
I can already tell.
I think I finally understand why the Third did what he did to protect the village.
But, as always, I took too long to figure it out.
Ino, Chouji, Shikamaru... I have one last thing to tell you.
Next time: Last Words.