Get back in your cage!
Sora, I'm gonna save you!
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
must be expressed with words.
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
to that blue, blue sky
aoi aoi ano sora
My Friend
Even the real Jinchuuriki can't stand up to Sora!
Return him to normal!
He's out of my control now.
Sora's going to break loose anytime now and destroy Konoha!
We won't let him!
Just try to stop us.
I don't plan on losing.
Get back here!
Sora!
I managed to push that damned Kyuubi back...
...by borrowing your power!
Now I'm going to lend you mine.
Don't even try to turn it down!
Sora! Wake the hell up!
Naruto!
You okay?
Hang on, Naruto.
I'm going to heal you now!
There's no time to heal him.
Sakura, get out of there!
Everyone, run!
Is everybody okay?
Yes.
We're okay!
But what about Sakura-san and Naruto-kun?
Naruto...!
Sakura-chan, you okay?
That's a relief...
Forget me, Naruto. I need to heal you!
You know how quickly I recover,
better than anyone else.
I'm going to bring Sora back no matter what.
I need you to heal him when I do.
Naruto...
Got it.
Sora...
Naruto!
I'm fine!
Sakura-chan, go join the others.
This is between Sora and me.
How is it?
I couldn't heal him at all with my medical ninjutsu.
Just as I thought.
It's just like when you got hurt, Sakura.
Injuries dealt by the Kyuubi's chakra take longer to heal than normal ones.
It's probably going to feel like someone's jabbing you with needles for a while.
I'll be okay.
So what the hell?!
Are you saying Naruto's the only one who can stop him now?!
Essentially, yes.
No way!
Naruto-kun!
This wouldn't have happened to Sora if I had defeated you for good back then!
But aren't you happy?
This means that you aren't the one who killed Sora's dad.
It will be.
This time I'll be sure to...
Working under the Hokage's orders again?
No!
I can't forgive you.
I can't forgive you for doing this to your own son!
Who gives a rat's ass about the whole father-son thing!
You think that garbage is enough to change the Fire Country?!
It's not about changing the country, it's about being connected to it.
Well, too bad! I'm going to change this country, no, this world!
In order to do that, I need a king!
You're wrong!
You're the one who's wrong!
Ninpou, Choujuu Giga!
Damn it! What is this?!
Did you sneak out of the hospital to take a late night walk?
The village was in such a ruckus that I couldn't fall asleep.
If you say so.
Now then...
We can take our time and talk things over, Kazuma.
I don't have anything to discuss with you!
Sora!
That hurt...
Come on, think back, Sora.
Think back to when we first met.
When we fought each other by mistake.
When you saved me.
Sora...
Sora!
Damn it...
We were both wrong the whole time.
We never realized who the king truly is.
I'm not wrong.
I'm not wrong, Asuma!
What...
What's going to happen...to the Fire Country...if I die?
Nothing's going to happen to it.
What a joke...
I don't really remember my dad's face.
But even now, I remember that sash and how clean and spotless it was.
To me, Dad was sparkling white just like that.
Kazuma...
Your duty was...
Sora!
Who's that?
Oh, it's Naruto.
Let's calm d-oof, and talk things ov-ouch!
Hey! You're hitting me!
Man, he's so loud!
Are you okay, Sora?
Naruto?
Why the hell did you come here?!
I couldn't help but come.
He's too straight-forward.
Hey! What happened, Sora?!
What happened between you and Asuma-sensei?!
Let go of me, you jerk!
He's an annoying goon.
What is it this time?!
What on earth's happening?
That's...
Captain Yamato, he's reacting differently than Naruto did!
You're right.
This is just a theory, but I don't think Sora's body can handle the Kyuubi's chakra.
Meaning, all the chakra that's built up in Sora's body is trying to break free.
That means...
Sora, that power...
That power won't help you!
Instead of that power, I will...
Everyone here in Konoha will become...
...become your strength!
Naruto!
Tsunade-sama!
Shizune, we're going!
Y-Yes, sir!
What is that?
Is that the Kyuubi?
What an unbelievable amount of chakra.
What?
What's going on now?
It looks a little off.
Captain Yamato!
Most likely, after leaving Sora's body,
it needed a vessel in order to maintain its form.
Then that means...
Sora...
Are you okay, Sora?!
Hey, can you hear me?
Wake up, Sora!
Sora!
Who's there?
I hear someone again...
Someone calling...
...calling out to me.
Sora!
You're so annoying, Naruto!
You finally awake?
Naruto...
Sora, let's go home. Come on!
Go home? What home? Where am I supposed to go?
What're you saying? Our home is Konoha.
Konoha?
The Konoha I tried to destroy?
That doesn't matter!
You're our friend!
I don't care what anyone else says.
You and I are friends!
Friends...?
That's right!
It looks like he'll be okay.
Thank goodness!
Um...
Sai!
May I join you?
No, you can't.
Excuse me?!
I wonder what's so funny...
Sai doesn't get it.
Friends, huh?
So, you aren't going back to the Fire Temple?
Nah. I wanna travel around the world and meet people.
I want to take my time making friends, just like you did.
I see.
But drop by sometime!
Konoha will always welcome you with open arms!
That's right. Come by anytime.
Thank you.
Later!
Say "Hi" to Mister Asuma for me, will you?
Sure!
Come to think of it, next time I come by, I'm going to give you a Kaimyou name.
Bastard! I just learned that you only give that name to dead people!
You goon! You're so slow!
Later!
The Climbing Silver? That's a rare move for you.
Let's take our time. We've got plenty of it.
It's an excellent way to break through the enemy's defenses.
Sometimes you've gotta fight like this!
I thought you hated those kinds of strategies, like I do.
When you're up against a skilled opponent,
you need to make sacrifices to protect the king.
Something wrong?
Not really. It's nothing.
It's just that I've only recently come to realize how important the king really is.
Well, duh. If the King's captured the game ends, that's what shougi's all about.
If Konoha's shinobi were shougi pieces,
I'd say you'd be a knight, Shikamaru.
Why?
It doesn't have much traditional strength,
but it can jump over its enemies to move forward.
That unique ability is similar to how quickly you adapt your thought process.
Then what about you?
Me? I'm nothing.
I'm just...
A sacrificial piece?
So...
Do you know who the king is?
Isn't it the Hokage?
That's what I used to think.
But I was wrong.
Okay, then who?
You'll know when the time comes.
You've got some nice moves.
My attacks are seriously the slowest in Akatsuki, so I never manage to hit anyone.
I see. So you really are Akatsuki.
You're the only one left.
Pretty tough-looking, too.
Remember, Hidan. This is the Two-Tails Jinchuuriki.
Don't take her lightly. You'll die.
Give me a break, Kakuzu.
Seriously, I wish the bitch could kill me.
iijiina riyuu
It's so very easy
issai yurusu jakuhai
for youth to forgive everything
resukyuutai mo yondeoita
I called in the rescue squad
dakara
So please kiss me, please kiss me all night
puriizu kisu mi puriizu kisu mi
datenshi no mahou ka koakuma no chachina itazura
Is it a fallen angel's magic, or a mischievous monster's prank?
tsumaranakunacchau mae ni
Before we get bored
soore de houre
Let's let go
bouringubooru
Of that bowling ball. We lead such strange lives
ibutsu na sonzai daro
shouchi no suke
You've gotta understand
kowaresoude...
We're gonna smash it...
docchirakatta kanjou de kirihirake yo
Cut through the inner turmoil
kowaresou de
We're gonna break...
kowasenai bokura no shouri
I can't break it...our victory.
Next Episode
The next episode of Naruto Shippuuden is: The Approaching Menace.
We've finally been able to restore peace.
Naruto's looking forward to resuming his training now that Kakashi's back,
but new information from Jiraiya throws Konoha into shock once again.
The Approaching Menace