Damn, the third tail's already sprouted...
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
must be expressed with words.
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
to that blue, blue sky
aoi aoi ano sora
Resonance
Sora...
Sora!
Naruto, watch out!
Naruto!
Crap...
Are you okay?
Sora... His consciousness...
I refuse to believe...that his mind is gone!
Sora's already lost control over there.
No one can stop him now.
Kazuma, you dirty...
Mokuton no Jutsu!
What destructive force!
Stop it, Sora!
Kage Kubi Shibari no Jutsu!
(Kage Kubi Shibari no Jutsu: Shadow Neck Bind Technique)
Damn it, it's no use!
I'll go!
Chouji!
Leave it to me, I'll heal him!
Shit...
Wake the hell up!
Kazuma, you bastard. Why?
Why would you, his own father, do such a thing?
You placed the Kyuubi's chakra into Sora to make him a killing machine.
Do you even realize what you've done?!
It was all for the sake of duty.
And Sora will live on as the man who carried it out.
Enough of your bullshit!
I'll go next!
Bastard!
Gatsuuga!
Shit!
You no longer have any honor!
It's my honor to ensure that the Fire Country remains as it should!
How I accomplish it is irrelevant!
Then what about your child's...
Sora's honor?!
What about your pride, as the Third Hokage's son?
I...
I protected the king, just as you did!
That's enough, isn't it?
You're right. I'm protecting the king.
But it's not the king you're thinking of!
You just proved my point!
It doesn't matter who or what the king is.
In the end, we're merely pawns who exist to protect it.
So as pawns, we have our duty laid out for us!
That's why I made Sora what he is!
A pawn who'll advance into enemy territory until he becomes king!
Children...
...are not simple pawns to protect any king!
That doesn't matter!
Since we've come this far, we'll have to have a match to see who's king is the true one.
How we do it doesn't matter.
We could completely rearrange the pieces, and I'd still win.
Mokuton no Jutsu!
Shit!
Why are you protecting an outsider?
He's not an outsider!
He's a part of Team Kakashi!
It's the same thing again, huh, Sora?
Remember, Sora!
How we were all acting like idiots.
How we tried to stop each other.
I guess there's no choice, huh?
Did he do it?
Naruto!
Sora!
Sora, come back!
I know you're in there!
Sora!
Sora...
Stop it!
Get away from Sora!
Naruto!
Sora!
Come on, Sora, come back to us! Sora!
Sora, you...
What?
What's going on?
The Kyuubi's chakra is coming out on its own!
Now!
Hokage Shiki Jijun Jutsu: Kakuan Nitten Suishu!
What's going on?!
It isn't working like normal!
Something from the outside is causing this!
Naruto!
Damn it! Don't come out!
Why?!
Coincidence sure can be funny sometimes.
It's just like Fuuka said.
Furido, it's about that spiky-haired punk I fought against.
He's kinda like Sora somehow.
She said that Naruto and Sora were connected somehow.
Both of their chakra originally comes from the Kyuubi.
The rage from Sora's Kyuubi chakra is resonating with the real thing.
What?!
This is so interesting!
Now the true Jinchuuriki, no, the Kyuubi itself, is gonna go nuts and destroy the village again!
Damn it!
Damn...
Enough... Stop it!
Sora! Sora!
No way...
Wh-What is that?!
This isn't good!
Everyone, run for it!
Naruto!
Sakura-chan...
Sora, snap out of it! Now!
Atta boy, Sora!
Keep it up and destroy Konoha!
Oh, no...
Sora...
Naruto!
No chance... There's no way I'm gonna let the goddamned Kyuubi take over again!
That's-!
Great! That's the spirit, Sora!
I didn't tell you to come out!
Get back in your cage, you monster fox!
You can't pop out whenever you feel like it!
Captain Yamato, isn't there anything we can do?!
No, my techniques aren't working on Naruto right now.
We just have to trust Naruto's willpower.
But-!
Bastard...
Leave him to me, boy.
Go screw yourself.
I'm not going to run away!
I'm not going to let some stupid fox take over me!
Naruto!
Naruto-kun...
Damn it!
I made...a promise!
I won't let you take over every time something happens!
And I can't do the exact same thing I kept telling Sora to not let happen!
Why are you holding back?
Why don't you ask me just like you always do?
Say, "Lend me your power!"
Shove it.
I'm going to bring you back with my own two hands, Sora!
Naruto!
Sora...
Who's there?
Sora! Come back!
Get back here!
Just how long are you gonna stay asleep?!
Snap out of it already!
Wake the hell up!
Sora!
Who's there?
Who's out there?
What? It's me!
It's me when I was young...
When I was always crying...
When I was all alone...
Sora...
Who?
Who's voice is that?
Sora...
I knew it. It's just as I thought!
Nothing's changed!
I'm still all alone!
Sora.
Wait for me.
I'm coming to save you now.
Just hang in there, Sora!
Who's voice is that?
iijiina riyuu
It's so very easy
issai yurusu jakuhai
for youth to forgive everything
resukyuutai mo yondeoita
I called in the rescue squad
dakara
So please kiss me, please kiss me all night
puriizu kisu mi puriizu kisu mi
datenshi no mahou ka koakuma no chachina itazura
Is it a fallen angel's magic, or a mischievous monster's prank?
tsumaranakunacchau mae ni
Before we get bored
soore de houre
Let's let go
bouringubooru
Of that bowling ball. We lead such strange lives
ibutsu na sonzai daro
shouchi no suke
You've gotta understand
kowaresoude...
We're gonna smash it...
docchirakatta kanjou de kirihirake yo
Cut through the inner turmoil
kowaresou de
We're gonna break...
kowasenai bokura no shouri
I can't break it...our victory.
Next Episode
The next episode of Naruto Shippuuden is "My Friend!"
Even as Naruto sacrifices himself, will it be enough to reclaim Sora's mind from the beast within?
This all-out, destined battle is drawing to a close!
My Friend
Ninja Academy
Special Class
Today we're going to take a look at when the Kyuubi has appeared in the past.
Naruto first released the Kyuubi's chakra in his fight
with Haku during our mission in the Wave Country.
It appears to have just popped out due to his highly emotional state,
rather than something he consciously controlled.
The first time he used it of his own will
was when he summoned Gamabunta after using up most of his chakra during training with Jiraiya-sama.
After that, he used it to beat Neji-san in the Chuunin Exams,
and when he fought against Gaara-san as he tried to destroy Konoha.
He also used it when fighting against Sasuke, to counter the power of his cursed seal.
It's saved Naruto from a bunch of tough situations.
But the strength he gets from the Kyuubi isn't real strength.
If he relies on it too much, he may hurt his friends, as well as himself.
That's why Naruto's trying so hard to save Sora with his own power.