You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
must be expressed with words.
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
Habataitara
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
to that blue, blue sky
aoi aoi ano sora
Hooked Claws that Slash the Darkness! The Strong Wind that Blows Past
A Naruto Shippuuden Special
Quit fooling around, Naruto.
We'll leave you behind!
Is he shaking?
Even on a mission, I can do it whenever I want!
He must still be scared.
It's what happened yesterday...
Captain Yamato sure is taking a long time.
I know. How far could he have gone?
Ah! Captain Yamato...
Captain Yamato, don't scare me like that!
Sorry, sorry. I couldn't resist.
Trust me, you're scary enough without any pranks.
Well, you're a very easy target, Naruto.
So, Captain, getting back to the topic
at hand, why would they defile a grave?
That's so cruel.
Usually grave-robbers target the tombs of rich
people hoping to steal the treasures inside.
But in this case, the body and the treasures were left intact.
These incidents have been occurring frequently within a 50-60 meter radius of the Fire Temple, where we're headed now.
The Fire Temple?
They're the ones who requested this mission.
And since they specifically requested Konoha's
help dealing with these tomb raids,
I have a feeling there's more to this than meets the eyes.
There are actually four hidden tombs in this area.
And the raiders are after them?
Yes, that's a strong possibility.
Wait a second! What do you mean by hidden tomb?
Even in death, a ninja's body contains all sorts of information.
In some cases, that information can be worth a fortune.
Take your fight with Sasori, for example.
He turned the Third Kazekage's corpse into a puppet.
That's right.
The more capable the ninja, the more use they have.
In order to keep the bodies from being stolen or misused, barriers are often erected around the tombs, and their locations are kept secret.
That's what I meant by a hidden tomb.
So, there are some really awesome ninja buried there, right?
Yes, especially these four.
The information contained in their bodies is unbelievably valuable.
But, there's also another possibility.
And that is...
...that the tomb wasn't broken into from the outside.
In other words,
the corpse came back to life!
Gotcha!
He actually believed what Captain Yamato said.
Gotta keep practicing!
This is our rendezvous point.
A group from the Fire Temple will be here shortly.
I'm so tired!
I'll just have a seat...
You're too close!
There's room over there!
Don't make too much noise, please.
I knew it. He's scared.
They're late.
Did we stop at the wrong landmark?
I'm going to check.
I'll go with you.
Me, too.
You and Sai wait here.
Otherwise we might miss them.
I got it.
It'll be fine.
I'll stay by Naruto's side.
Quit trying to scare me!
When your friend is frightened or scared, try
gently placing your hand on their shoulder...
...to show them in a warm, friendly way that they're not alone.
Th-This is much harder than I thought...
What the hell are you doing?!
I-I thought it was a good idea-
It wasn't!
I don't swing that way!
Wait, that's not what I meant!
Um, when your friend misunderstands you...
Hanging around with you is too dangerous!
I've had enough. I'm gonna go find Sakura-chan!
And then you... Naruto!
What did I do wrong?
I don't understand how Sai's brain works...
Sakura-chan...?
Could it be the tomb raiders?
A warthog?
Oh, crap!
S-Sorry, sorry!
Hmm... I've seen one of these before...
Forbidden
A barrier?
Could this be...?
The hidden tomb?
What is this place?
The coffin is gone. I'm too late.
Who's there?!
So he's the tomb raider?
Wind?
Wh-What?
Take this!
Juuha Shou!
(Juuha Shou: Beast Wave Strike)
Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Here I come!
He did that before!
Juuha Shou!
Damn it. His wind techniques are tough!
Wind? Oh yeah!
Hey, do you also have wind ele-
Repent now. I'll give you three seconds.
Time's up. Time for your punishment.
What the hell is with this guy?
You're the one who's getting punished!
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Juuha Shou!
Eat this!
Juuha Reppuu Shou!
(Juuha Reppuu Shou: Beast Wave Violent Wind Strike)
Die!
Stop it, Sora!
Naruto!
Chiriku-sama, you were right to be worried.
I got worried about the hidden tomb on the way
to meet our guests, and came to investigate.
When I did, the barrier had been torn down,
the coffin was stolen, and he was inside.
Hey! Are you trying to pin your crimes on me?
You're the real thief, aren't you?!
What are you saying?! You were in the tomb first!
And the coffin was already gone when I went in!
Oh yeah? Prove it!
You prove it!
I'll kick your ass, bastard!
Take your best shot, loser!
Right here, right now!
You can't beat me, wuss!
Brethren from Konoha, I am Chiriku of the Fire Temple.
I apologize for the mistake in establishing the rendezvous point.
He's the guest?
From Konoha-?
So, he's...?
This is Sora, a monk in training, also from the temple.
Sora-kun, is it?
I am the captain of this team, Yamato.
This is Naruto, and...
I'm Sakura.
My name is Sai.
I already said it, didn't I?
We don't need any help from Konoha!
Sora.
Chiriku-sama!
Kitane-sama's coffin has been stolen, with no traces of forced entry.
To break the barrier so easily, they
must be extremely capable shinobi.
If the enemies are that skilled, we definitely
have good reason to call on Konoha for help.
You two go back and make arrangements
to defend the remaining three tombs.
Also, strengthen the temple's security and start
preparations for an emergency situation.
Yes, sir!
Let us return to the Fire Temple for now.
Understood.
Hey, is your chakra wind-natured?
Don't ignore me, I'm talking to you!
I wanna know about that technique you used!
It was this hand-
Don't touch me!
Jerk...
Are we there yet?
This is exactly like that dream I had...
Naruto...
Sakura-chan...
Naruto!
How long are you gonna sleep?
We'll be late for our mission!
Sakura-chan...
Wake up!
By the way,
I can't believe you live in such a filthy room.
Half-eaten ramen on the floor,
and expired milk left out!
Why don't you clean up for once?
Well...
Sakura-chan...
Ow...
What is this...?
Naruto, you stupid slob!
This way.
It's real... It actually exists.
Whoops. Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks-!
Son of a bitch!
Serves you right.
I'll kill you!
You can't do that.
Damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it, I'll kill him-!
Sora, how could you do that?
Yes, yes. I'm very sorry!
I'll kill him if it's the last thing I do!
You'd better not, or you'll be punished for real.
Welcome back, Chiriku-sama.
Where is Shubi?
He is leading a group to the other three hidden tombs:
Nauma-sama's, Tou'u-sama's and Seito-sama's.
They are all skilled monks from our Temple.
If anything happens, we'll know immediately.
Kitane-sama is conducting an investigation
of the area, and the others are standing by.
We have reinforced the temple, and everyone
is prepared for an emergency situation.
I guess we can relax for a while.
It's too late.
Sora.
What's with his attitude?
He...
I have returned. These four are from
Konoha and have come at my request.
Hello. I am Captain Yamato.
With me are Sakura, Sai and Naruto.
From Konoha? That's reassuring.
Leave everything to me!
We're prepared to take action anytime.
We still have to wait for the news from our ninja monks in the field.
For now, please follow me.
I wonder what they want to use the stolen body for.
Indeed. Either he wants the information within the body, or...
Kuchiyose Edo Tensei!
(Kuchiyose Edo Tensei: Summoning - Resurrection to the Impure World)
First!
First
Second!
Second
First
It seems the third one failed.
Oh well.
They may want to use the actual body itself, like Orochimaru.
But I doubt there's anyone around here who uses techniques like him.
So the guys inside these four hidden tombs
must've been pretty awesome, huh?
Wh-what?
They were indeed "awesome".
But more importantly, they were good people.
With the Fire Temple in the middle,
to the east, west, south and north...
...lie the graves of Nauma, Seito, Tou'u, and Kitane.
They were also members of The Twelve Ninja Guardians.
The Twelve Ninja Guardians?
I've heard of them.
I've only heard the name.
For real? Are they famous?
I guess you either know of them or you don't.
The Twelve Ninja Guardians is an organization whose members are gathered from all across the Fire Country to protect its Feudal Lord.
Isn't protecting the Fire country our job as Konoha shinobi?
Protecting the Fire Country is the responsibility of our village, yes.
But therein lies the difference. Konoha is an organization that protects the entire country, whereas the Feudal Lord is just one man.
Okay, so...
In order to protect a country, you need
to protect the top, the Feudal Lord.
The Twelve Ninja Guardians were formed
by people who shared that view.
I was very young back then.
I was all too eager to sacrifice my life for
the Fire Country, and I joined the Twelve.
Then, Chiriku-san, you're-
I used to be, anyways.
By the way, Asuma-san is also a former member of The Twelve.
Asuma? Is he doing well?
He's doing great. Actually, he just
gave me some advice for my training!
Is that so?
If that's the case...
Then these incidents are, to you and Asuma-sensei,
equivalent to your friends' graves being defiled.
Those four gave their lives for the Fire Country at a young age.
A few members of the Twelve tried to stage a coup d'etat,
and the resulting clash resulted in the entire group falling apart.
A coup d'etat means that a person or group tried to usurp power and change a country to match their own ideals.
I knew that.
"I want to protect the Fire Country." A simple wish that resulted in serious disagreements between the Twelve Ninja Guardians.
Got it. So that means-!
It means they didn't want to leave
the Fire Country in Konoha's hands.
They'd rather have used military power to
create a country with themselves at the head.
Yeah, really! You can't let people get away with that!
Naruto.
Huh?
Shut up.
You are correct. They wanted to dismantle Konoha village,
and place all military power under the Feudal Lord's control.
Their plan got as far as preparing to move the Feudal Lord.
And at the same time, they had prepared
to attack several other countries.
They had?
They didn't care about the fine balance of
peace between the Five Great Countries,
believing that true peace would only come if the Fire Country conquered the world and united all nations under its banner.
But that's so selfish!
We tried all kinds of negotiations, but in the end, war is war.
The Feudal Lord realized how far they had taken things, and...
...the six who staged the coup died.
But Kitane, Nauma, Tou'u and Seito were sacrificed, too.
Who could have known that happened...
In these hidden tombs lay the friends of Chiriku and Asuma-sensei.
If one of Naruto or Sakura's friends, such as
Sasuke-kun, died, and his body was stolen...
Right?
We can't let the person who stole
Kitane-san's body to get away with it.
You got that right.
The men are beginning their evening practice.
Freakin' Sora...
Take your stances.
Begin!
What?
Weird.
What is it?
He's pissing me off!
Bow!
Thank you very much!
You...
Hey, is this good enough?
You... Are you trying to mess with me?
You're the one messing around.
I dunno what kinda training that was, but all I saw was this.
You...
Don't get so angry.
You were making fun of it all.
I dunno why, but I didn't like it!
Naruto! You moron...
Your name is Naruto, right?
Yeah.
I'll give you a better name.
A kaimyou.
(A new name created by Buddhist priests for a recently departed person.)
Kaimyou?
Naruto!
So you're finally serious?
That's more like the strength you showed me earlier.
You're making me angry!
Whoa, aren't you getting too worked up?
Again...
What's wrong with him?
It's like his power just drained away.
Those eyes... Sora?
The same eyes.
Why...do you have eyes like-?
Enough, Sora!
Damn it, I can't stop!
I guess I couldn't think of a kaimyou for you.
Wh-what are you doing?!
I was going to wipe your sweat off.
Don't! It's just...wrong.
Hey, Sai.
What's a kaimyou?
I suppose it's like a nickname, perhaps?
But they're only for dead people-
Oh, like how you always try to think of nicknames?
So it's a sign of friendship.
Sora!
You here?
What's wrong?
Naoma-sama's tomb has been defiled...
Juuha Shou!
Juuha Reppuu Shou!
Your techniques are awesome.
So are you doing wind-element chakra manipulation?
What did you come here for?
Oh, I thought of coming here to give you a kaimyou.
Sure. I'll give you a nice kaimyou!
Sora...Sora...Sora-chi, Souran, Sora-chan!
Damn you, how dare you mock me?!
What happened back at the temple?
You disgust me.
Yeah, that's how people thought of me when I was a kid.
Same for you, right?
So what?! So what...
Yes, I disgust them! But I don't give a rat's ass about them.
I disgust myself!
That's right.
I hate my powers.
You...
But even so, I can't simply rid myself of them.
I need them to get revenge for my
father's death... To kill his murderer...
Revenge?
It's Momo Midori. Did something happen at a tomb?!
Naruto! Where were you?!
Sorry.
There is a report from the people that went to Nauma's location.
The tomb had been broken into, and the corpse was removed.
What?!
At this rate, the other two will be...
We're ready to move. Let's go.
I'm coming, too!
Good!
All right, time to beat the crap outta these grave robbers!
Kodomo no koro mita niji wo
If I look up now for the rainbow I saw as a boy,
ima miageru to nana iro de wa naku
there are no longer the seven colors,
Yagate kiri ga kakari
only mist and fog...
Jikan wa sugi kawatte yuku
As time passes by, and the world around me changes,
Kimi wo sagashitemo doko ni mo inai
no matter where I search for you, you're nowhere to be found.
Me wo toji, kokoro hiraite
So I close my eyes, and open my heart...
mata nagamete mitemo nanimo kawaranai no ka
I need to know, if I gaze up again,
tashikamete mitai
will things be different this time?
Sunao ni narereba kono kiri ga hareru to
Maybe if I was more honest, the fog would fade away.
kokoro ni negai sou sakenderu
So I pray, screaming that wish deep within my soul.
Nanika wo nakushiteshimatta koto de sou
When you lose one thing,
te ni shita mono mo kitto arun darou
you gain another, don't you?
Dakedo mada bokura wa otona ni tomadoi
But still, no matter how often the adults confuse us,
ikite yuku sube sagashiteru
we'll keep looking for the right way to live our lives.
Next Episode
We've received word from the Fire Temple.
The four hidden tombs have already been raided by the enemy.
They got us. What's the situation now?
Team Kakashi is heading to their location.
So they're after the actual bodies of the
members of the Twelve Ninja Guardians, then?
We're also unsure of what Orochimaru and Akatsuki are plotting.
And there's the issue of Danzou-sama's loyalties...
We've really got our hands full here.
We'll just have to do whatever we can!
A New Enemy
Next time: A New Enemy!
Konoha
Brigade
ask us anything
Konoha's Ask-Us-Anything Brigade!
Konoha
Brigade
ask us anything
This week's question is:
I want to smack the crap out of that wimp Sora, but the Fire Temple's his home turf. Anything I should know?
This from you?
But he's such a jerk!
Sheesh...
The Fire Temple is Konoha's largest ninja temple.
It's an old temple with an ornate design and impregnable security.
The Ninja Monks are said to have the knowledge
of sages, and use a wide variety of techniques.
Since he's a former member of the Twelve Ninja
Guardians, no one doubts Chiriku-san's strength.
I just noticed this, but how come so many
of them haven't shaved their heads?
Hmm... Well, they might just be apprentices-
Oh, that makes sense! They're just trainees!
No, I said might-
Well, if he's just a trainee, I'll cut him some slack.
In fact, I think I'll go give him a few pointers!
Well, I guess we answered his question... See you next time!
Problem NO. 4
Secret of the Fire Temple
Solved
Problem NO. 4
Secret of the Fire Temple
Solved
Problem NO. 4
Secret of the Fire Temple
Solved
Problem NO. 4
Secret of the Fire Temple
Solved
Problem NO. 4
Secret of the Fire Temple
Solved
Problem NO. 4