Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
He made three shadow clones this time...
What is that?
That's some screech...
A-And the chakra's incredible!
What is he doing?
What is that technique?
I can't get hit with that,
or I'm finished.
Fuuton, Rasen-Shuriken!
(Fuuton, Rasen-Shuriken: Wind Element, Spiraling Shuriken)
This is it for you!
I'll back him up, too!
No!
Stay away from Naruto, or you'll get caught in the blast.
So this is the Kyuubi Jinchuuriki's power.
A fitting technique for a monster.
What?!
Shi-!
What? Did he get him?
He lost it!
mijika ni arumono
You've gotta be extra careful
tsune ni ki wo tsuketeinai to
with the things nearest to you
amari ni chikasugite
You know the closer you get to something
miushinatteshimaisou
the tougher it is to see it
anata ga saikin taiken shita
Explain to me this happiness
shiawase wa ittai nan desu ka?
that you just got to experience.
megumaresugeteite
Or maybe you're so blessed
omoidasenai kamo
that you can't even remember?
ima koko ni iru koto
That you stand here now
iki wo shiteiru koto
That you live and breathe
tada sore dake no koto ga
They're all little miracles
kiseki da to kizuku
just by themselves.
mijika ni arumono
You've gotta be extra careful
tsune ni ki wo tsuketeinai to
with the things nearest to you
amari ni chikasugite
You know the closer you get to something
miushinatteshimaisou
the tougher it is to see it
You know the closer you get to something
And I'll never take it for granted
oitsuzuketekita yume
It's fine to say "Never give up."
akiramezuni susume yo nante
and "Keep chasing your dreams."
kirei koto wo ieru hodo
But the more time you spend talking big
nanimo dekichainai kedo
the less you get done.
hitonigiri no yuuki wo mune ni
I'll press that handful of courage against my heart
ashita wo ikinuku tame ni
and with its help, survive another day
And I'll never take it for granted
Let's go
Wind Element: Rasen-Shuriken!
The number-one most surprising ninja strikes again.
Yamato!
On it!
Your heart is mine!
Damn it all...
Acting tough and screwing up... I guess that was pretty Naruto-ish.
Since it was called Rasen-Shuriken or whatever, I thought you'd throw it at him...
Do you have to actually get in his face and punch him with it?
Hey, if I'd hit him there'd be nothing left!
Yes, it's called the Rasen-Shuriken, but it only works as a point-blank attack.
That's why its use relies on shadow clones for a diversion.
He still hasn't had enough training time.
If it had just lasted a couple more seconds...
Exactly.
It'll never work now.
Not against someone like him.
That Kyuubi kid's technique...
It seemed very powerful, but I'll be fine as long as I keep my distance.
As long as I avoid close-range combat and stay focused on the original body using the technique, I have nothing to fear.
Let me try one more time.
I'll finish him with my new technique.
You're going up against Akatsuki!
If you do the same thing, he'll just dodge it again!
He'll know you're trying to distract him.
We need to fight together.
That's true.
Currently, it's five against one.
There's no need to cross a dangerous bridge like that.
So, what's your next move?
Kakashi-sensei.
Do you remember what you told me when I was training?
"The only shinobi who can surpass the Fourth Hokage is you."
"That's what I believe."
Naruto...
I know that teamwork's important.
I also know that this is a dangerous bridge to cross.
Even so, I...
I want to cross that bridge alone.
If I can't make it to the other side, I'll never be able to grow up.
So...
So please...
Don't burn that bridge just yet.
Yamato, what do you think?
You still haven't noticed, huh?
This is a completely new Naruto.
That settles it then.
Shikamaru...
Pakkun, what was that?!
They're close!
Man, this is ridiculous!
You really messed me up...
Lord Jashin will punish you for this!
He'll bring His great vengeance down upon you, like in the scriptures!
Your bullshit doesn't scare me.
See, you and I have very different beliefs.
I believe in the Will of Fire.
And that pathetic Lord Jashin or whatever isn't your God anymore.
I am.
The only one bringing down vengeance is me.
Bastard...
Remember what I said!
The Jashinist scripture says He will smite you! Got it?!
And I'll carry out his judgment!
My teeth are enough to take you on!
I'll bite you to death, motherfucker!
We found you!
You're my backup, huh? You're a few minutes too late.
Wh-What?
Shikamaru! Don't tell me you took out an Akatsuki all by yourself?
You're much more capable than I assumed.
I guess.
This was one of those things I had to do myself, no matter what.
That's right.
How's it going with the others?
We came here right away, so...
Let's hurry and rejoin them.
Shikamaru!
Hey, are you okay?
I'll heal you right away!
This is nothing!
But-!
I don't want to see any more of my friends get hurt.
Let's go!
Right!
Everyone, please be okay!
Go, Naruto!
Right!
They're sending that little snot in again?
I'd better switch to a long-range mode, just to be on the safe side.
He's not just shape-shifting, he's drawing up a huge amount of chakra!
It must be to counter Naruto's technique.
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Here we go again.
It's ready!
He's flying!
I can ignore the distraction shadow clones coming from the rear.
I just need to go after the original.
If I can eliminate his technique, there's nothing else to worry about.
It's no good! He sees through it!
He knows to attack from a distance!
Naruto!
There!
What?! That was a clone?!
He mixed himself in with the fakes?!
Eat this!
The blast's coming!
The number of attacks was unreal.
Even with my Sharingan, I couldn't count them all.
What a technique!
Ho-
Holy cow...
Naruto...
You...
You really have...
There... I did it!
kondo wa itsu aeru ka nante
What made me think
sonna kao shite yoku ierutte
"How can you say that with a straight face?"
omotteta yo nande darou
when you asked, "When will we meet again?"
any time shaberisugi no KY
Any time you talk too much, I know you don't get it.
chirari miseru tsuyogari na “I cry„
For a moment, I see your bluff and I cry.
namida no kouka wa dore kurai?
Do my tears even work on you?
watashi narini “ai saretai„
I keep saying "I want to be loved"
afureru no ni kimi ga mienai
in my own special way, but you still don't get the hint.
nido to kimi ni aenai
I have this nagging feeling
sonna ki ga surunda...
that I'll never see you again...
tsutaetai no ni umai kotoba miataranai
I wish I could tell you, but I can't find the words
watashi tabun uso demo ii no ni
Maybe I'd rather listen to you lie,
“ikanai de„ mo ienai yo
I can't even say "Don't leave me."
nigitteta te ga hanaretara
When you let go of my hand,
kimi wa itsuka wasurechau no?
will you forget
watashi no koto
about me?
tsutaetai no ni umai kotoba miataranai watashi tabun
I wish I could tell you, but I can't find the words
uso demo ii no ni “ikanai de„ mo ienai yo
Maybe I'd rather listen to you lie, I can't even say "Don't leave me."
Next Episode
Shizune, have you noticed?
You mean Naruto-kun, don't you?
Yeah.
What was that?
I've seen a lot of strange cases before, but never anything like that.
And what's going on with that Akatsuki corpse Kakashi's group brought back?
We're already conducting an autopsy on it, but...
Then tell the person in charge of it to make investigating that effect their top priority.
Next time: The Price of Power!
The Price of Power
Everyone doing well?
Today's challenge for you is...
Let's try it together!
Kuchiyose no Jutsu
...the summoning technique!
Summoning technique?
Yes!
It's a space/time technique that lets you call out an animal helper if you've made a contract with it.
Since no one here has a contract with an animal yet,
we'll just practice the hand symbols today.
Let's try it together!
Kuchiyose no Jutsu
The symbols we need are:
Let's try it together!
Kuchiyose no Jutsu
The symbols we need are:
Boar
Boar!
Dog
Dog!
Rooster
Rooster!
Monkey
Monkey!
Ram
Ram!
Then all you need to do is draw out your chakra and slap your hand where you want the animal to show up!
Ram
Let's try it together!
Kuchiyose no Jutsu
Ram
Let's try it together!
Kuchiyose no Jutsu
Then all you need to do is draw out your chakra and slap your hand where you want the animal to show up!
Ram
Let's try it together!
Kuchiyose no Jutsu
Then all you need to do is draw out your chakra and slap your hand where you want the animal to show up!
Ram
Let's try it together!
Kuchiyose no Jutsu
Then all you need to do is draw out your chakra and slap your hand where you want the animal to show up!
Ram
Let's try it together!
Kuchiyose no Jutsu
Then all you need to do is draw out your chakra and slap your hand where you want the animal to show up!
Let's try it together!
Kuchiyose no Jutsu
Then all you need to do is draw out your chakra and slap your hand where you want the animal to show up!
Let's try it together!
It's important not to rush and make mistakes!
So, let's give it a try!
Okay! Boar! Dog! Rooster! Monkey! Ram!
Put down your hand and...
Hello! He called for me, so I came as quickly as I could! I'm Pakkun!
Awesome! So cool!
To succeed, all you need is patience, effort and training!
It's not like Naruto could summon the Toad Boss right away, either.
Practice hard so you can master this technique!
That's it! Bye-bye!