Asuma...
Asuma!
mijika ni arumono
You've gotta be extra careful
tsune ni ki wo tsuketeinai to
with the things nearest to you
amari ni chikasugite
You know the closer you get to something
miushinatteshimaisou
the tougher it is to see it
anata ga saikin taiken shita
Explain to me this happiness
shiawase wa ittai nan desu ka?
that you just got to experience.
megumaresugeteite
Or maybe you're so blessed
omoidasenai kamo
that you can't even remember?
ima koko ni iru koto
That you stand here now
iki wo shiteiru koto
That you live and breathe
tada sore dake no koto ga
They're all little miracles
kiseki da to kizuku
just by themselves.
mijika ni arumono
You've gotta be extra careful
tsune ni ki wo tsuketeinai to
with the things nearest to you
amari ni chikasugite
You know the closer you get to something
miushinatteshimaisou
the tougher it is to see it
You know the closer you get to something
And I'll never take it for granted
oitsuzuketekita yume
It's fine to say "Never give up."
akiramezuni susume yo nante
and "Keep chasing your dreams."
kirei koto wo ieru hodo
But the more time you spend talking big
nanimo dekichainai kedo
the less you get done.
hitonigiri no yuuki wo mune ni
I'll press that handful of courage against my heart
ashita wo ikinuku tame ni
and with its help, survive another day
And I'll never take it for granted
Let's go
Last Words
Asuma...
I'm finished.
I'll just be another minute.
Damn it...
Damn you...
You son of a bitch!
Shit...
I'm so powerless...
Feathers?
The hell?!
You think you can take us out with some gay little crows?
Fuck that shit!
Trying to hinder our view?
A black sword...
Shikamaru...
We're here to help you.
Ino...
Get Shikamaru somewhere safe!
Right!
Stay on guard, Chouji!
Reinforcements, huh?
Are you okay?
Yeah, but forget me, Captain Asuma is...
Asuma-sensei!
It's faint, but he still has a heartbeat!
Chouji, take Asuma-sensei to Konoha Hospital right now!
Ino, accompany him and use your medical ninjutsu to heal him as much as you can!
Hurry!
Okay!
I'm not giving up my bounty.
Shit!
We'll deal with them while you guys get Asuma-san out of here!
You can struggle all you like, but in the end you'll all be sacrificed to God!
That's why-
Can it wait a little longer?
Seriously, we're right at the best part.
It's time to seal the Two-Tails.
That takes priority. Return immediately.
C'mon! All I'm asking for is like another minute!
Knock it off, Hidan.
Are they communicating with someone?
We'll be right back, so make sure you're ready.
You two really test my patience.
Let's go, Hidan.
That shithead leader... Next time I'm cursing him!
What's going on?
Are they just going to pull back?
Sensei!
Asuma-sensei!
Ino, Chouji, hurry up and get Asuma outta here! Now!
Hey! We told you to stay here until we get back!
He's about to die, anyway!
Later, bitches!
Chouji, Ino, get going!
I'll use my healing ninjutsu!
Don't...
I'm done for...
Even I...can tell...
You three should realize it, too.
Shut up! Don't speak!
Ino!
Right!
Ino?
Here...
And here, too!
They got four vital organs!
There's nothing more I can do...
I think I finally understand why the Third did what he did...
But, like always, I took too long...to figure it out.
Ino, Chouji, Shikamaru... I have one last thing to tell you.
Sensei, you shouldn't talk anymore!
Chouji!
And Ino...
These are Asuma-sensei's last words.
Just listen.
Ino...
Yes!
You're strong willed, dependable and responsible...
Chouji and Shikamaru... They're total goof-offs. Keep them in line...
Okay...
And don't let Sakura beat you...
...in ninjutsu or romance.
Okay!
Chouji, you're a kind man who cares for his comrades.
That's why...you'll become a shinobi more powerful than anyone else.
Be more confident in yourself.
And...maybe diet a little.
That might be too much, but I'll give it my best shot!
And Shikamaru.
You're so smart...and have great sense as a shinobi.
You could definitely become Hokage.
But...you're too lazy... You'd probably hate it.
I never even beat you once at shogi...
Ah, yes... Remember our talk about the King?
If we thought of the shinobi in Konoha as pieces of shogi,
then, Shikamaru, you would probably be the Knight.
Then what about you, Sensei?
I'm nothing.
I'm just...
A sacrificial piece?
So...
Do you know who the King is?
Isn't it the Hokage?
That's what I used to think, too.
But I was wrong.
Okay, then who?
You'll know when the time comes.
I'll tell you who it is.
Come closer.
Asuma! You...but-
Please, Shikamaru...
It doesn't matter now, does it? Even though I quit...
They're in my pouch...
I want one last smoke...
Sorry 'bout that!
I'm Sarutobi Asuma, and from today on I'll be leading Team 10.
It's not gonna be easy, so I hope you're all ready!
Come on, don't cry!
All I did was say that I'm going to be strict!
Your stupid smoke's making our eyes water!
More rice!
Also bring out four more servings of Kalbi ribs!
Here you are!
Chouji-kun, have you ever heard of the word restraint?
The bill's already 3,000 ryou.
It's not like I'm trying to be stingy.
I'm just worried about you.
If you keep eating like this, eventually you're gonna get really f-
That word's taboo!
"F-" what?
Something wrong, Shikamaru?
Well, h-h-h-h-he was saying you can order a full course meal!
Wha-?!
Really, Asuma-sensei?!
Thanks a million!
Waiter, bring two full course meals!
And pile on the rice!
Boy, I'm stuffed!
All set!
So who's it for?
Oh, uh... It's not really for anyone!
L-Later!
Say hi to Kurenai-sensei for me!
H-How'd she know?!
Shogi? Too troublesome.
Shogi allows you to work through various situations by utilizing each of the pieces' individual attributes.
This game is a must for people like you who're good at coming up with strategies.
You should get a decent grasp on the rules if you read this book.
Then you'll just need to practice.
It'll be troublesome, but I'll have it down in ten minutes.
I...lost.
You didn't have to hold back, you know.
You're the only one who passed the Chuunin Exams this round.
So, as your supervising jounin, I'm very proud.
Now we need to get Chouji and Ino there. Keep working hard!
Excellent work, Chouji, Ino!
Since Shikamaru previously passed the exam, everyone in Team 10 is now a chuunin!
And that means I'm no longer in charge of you.
You three will go on to become captains and eventually lead your own teams.
These earrings are a present to celebrate your promotions.
Don't ever forget that the four of us were Team 10!
Sensei!
He died the death of a true shinobi.
I really, really hate cigarettes...
The smoke always makes...my eyes water.
kondo wa itsu aeru ka nante
What made me think
sonna kao shite yoku ierutte
"How can you say that with a straight face?"
omotteta yo nande darou
when you asked, "When will we meet again?"
any time shaberisugi no KY
Any time you talk too much, I know you don't get it.
chirari miseru tsuyogari na “I cry„
For a moment, I see your bluff and I cry.
namida no kouka wa dore kurai?
Do my tears even work on you?
watashi narini “ai saretai„
I keep saying "I want to be loved"
afureru no ni kimi ga mienai
in my own special way, but you still don't get the hint.
nido to kimi ni aenai
I have this nagging feeling
sonna ki ga surunda...
that I'll never see you again...
tsutaetai no ni umai kotoba miataranai
I wish I could tell you, but I can't find the words
watashi tabun uso demo ii no ni
Maybe I'd rather listen to you lie,
“ikanai de„ mo ienai yo
I can't even say "Don't leave me."
nigitteta te ga hanaretara
When you let go of my hand,
kimi wa itsuka wasurechau no?
will you forget
watashi no koto
about me?
tsutaetai no ni umai kotoba miataranai watashi tabun
I wish I could tell you, but I can't find the words
uso demo ii no ni “ikanai de„ mo ienai yo
Maybe I'd rather listen to you lie, I can't even say "Don't leave me."
Next Episode
I see.
Um, Kurenai-san should be...
Inform all the relevant parties about his funeral.
I'll break the news to Kurenai-
No, I'll go. I'll tell her.
I have a message for her from Captain Asuma.
Devastating News
Next time: Devastating News.