Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
He made three shadow clones this time...
What is that?
That's some screech...
A-And the chakra's incredible!
What is he doing?
What is that technique?
I can't get hit with that,
or I'm finished.
Fuuton, Rasen-Shuriken!
(Fuuton, Rasen-Shuriken: Wind Element, Spiraling Shuriken)
This is it for you!
I'll back him up, too!
No!
Stay away from Naruto, or you'll get caught in the blast.
So this is the Kyuubi Jinchuuriki's power.
A fitting technique for a monster.
What?!
Shi-!
What? Did he get him?
He lost it!
The number-one most surprising ninja strikes again.
Yamato!
On it!
Your heart is mine!
Damn it all...
Acting tough and screwing up... I guess that was pretty Naruto-ish.
Since it was called Rasen-Shuriken or whatever, I thought you'd throw it at him...
Do you have to actually get in his face and punch him with it?
Hey, if I'd hit him there'd be nothing left!
Yes, it's called the Rasen-Shuriken, but it only works as a point-blank attack.
That's why its use relies on shadow clones for a diversion.
He still hasn't had enough training time.
If it had just lasted a couple more seconds...
Exactly.
It'll never work now.
Not against someone like him.
That Kyuubi kid's technique...
It seemed very powerful, but I'll be fine as long as I keep my distance.
As long as I avoid close-range combat and stay focused on the original body using the technique, I have nothing to fear.
Let me try one more time.
I'll finish him with my new technique.
You're going up against Akatsuki!
If you do the same thing, he'll just dodge it again!
He'll know you're trying to distract him.
We need to fight together.
That's true.
Currently, it's five against one.
There's no need to cross a dangerous bridge like that.
So, what's your next move?
Kakashi-sensei.
Do you remember what you told me when I was training?
"The only shinobi who can surpass the Fourth Hokage is you."
"That's what I believe."
Naruto...
I know that teamwork's important.
I also know that this is a dangerous bridge to cross.
Even so, I...
I want to cross that bridge alone.
If I can't make it to the other side, I'll never be able to grow up.
So...
So please...
Don't burn that bridge just yet.
Yamato, what do you think?
You still haven't noticed, huh?
This is a completely new Naruto.
That settles it then.
Shikamaru...
Pakkun, what was that?!
They're close!
Man, this is ridiculous!
You really messed me up...
Lord Jashin will punish you for this!
He'll bring His great vengeance down upon you, like in the scriptures!
Your bullshit doesn't scare me.
See, you and I have very different beliefs.
I believe in the Will of Fire.
And that pathetic Lord Jashin or whatever isn't your God anymore.
I am.
The only one bringing down vengeance is me.
Bastard...
Remember what I said!
The Jashinist scripture says He will smite you! Got it?!
And I'll carry out his judgment!
My teeth are enough to take you on!
I'll bite you to death, motherfucker!
We found you!
You're my backup, huh? You're a few minutes too late.
Wh-What?
Shikamaru! Don't tell me you took out an Akatsuki all by yourself?
You're much more capable than I assumed.
I guess.
This was one of those things I had to do myself, no matter what.
That's right.
How's it going with the others?
We came here right away, so...
Let's hurry and rejoin them.
Shikamaru!
Hey, are you okay?
I'll heal you right away!
This is nothing!
But-!
I don't want to see any more of my friends get hurt.
Let's go!
Right!
Everyone, please be okay!
Go, Naruto!
Right!
They're sending that little snot in again?
I'd better switch to a long-range mode, just to be on the safe side.
He's not just shape-shifting, he's drawing up a huge amount of chakra!
It must be to counter Naruto's technique.
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Here we go again.
It's ready!
He's flying!
I can ignore the distraction shadow clones coming from the rear.
I just need to go after the original.
If I can eliminate his technique, there's nothing else to worry about.
It's no good! He sees through it!
He knows to attack from a distance!
Naruto!
There!
What?! That was a clone?!
He mixed himself in with the fakes?!
Eat this!
The blast's coming!
The number of attacks was unreal.
Even with my Sharingan, I couldn't count them all.
What a technique!
Ho-
Holy cow...
Naruto...
You...
You really have...
There... I did it!
Shizune, have you noticed?
You mean Naruto-kun, don't you?
Yeah.
What was that?
I've seen a lot of strange cases before, but never anything like that.
And what's going on with that Akatsuki corpse Kakashi's group brought back?
We're already conducting an autopsy on it, but...
Then tell the person in charge of it to make investigating that effect their top priority.
Next time: The Price of Power!
Everyone doing well?
Today's challenge for you is...
...the summoning technique!
Summoning technique?
Yes!
It's a space/time technique that lets you call out an animal helper if you've made a contract with it.
Since no one here has a contract with an animal yet,
we'll just practice the hand symbols today.
The symbols we need are:
Boar!
Dog!
Rooster!
Monkey!
Ram!
Then all you need to do is draw out your chakra and slap your hand where you want the animal to show up!
It's important not to rush and make mistakes!
So, let's give it a try!
Okay! Boar! Dog! Rooster! Monkey! Ram!
Put down your hand and...
Hello! He called for me, so I came as quickly as I could! I'm Pakkun!
Awesome! So cool!
To succeed, all you need is patience, effort and training!
It's not like Naruto could summon the Toad Boss right away, either.
Practice hard so you can master this technique!
That's it! Bye-bye!