I never imagined his arms could still move
on their own after being detached!
But when did he...?
When I threw the explosive tags?
He hid in the smoke long enough to send his right arm underground!
He's a true blue Akatsuki...
Their abilities are all out of this world!
You said we were finished, but you still had no idea what I was capable of.
So it was better to keep your distance as you played your next hand.
You actually think, unlike my partner.
Shit! Kakuzu!
Do something, Kakuzu!
Shit!
Now, Chouji!
Nikudan Hari Sensha!
(Nikudan Hari Sensha: Spiked Meat Tank)
Kakuzu!
My god...
It doesn't look like Naruto's taken a single break.
I wouldn't think so. He has to perfect his new technique as soon as possible, if we're going to be sent as Kakashi-sensei's backup.
The time limit's twenty-four hours, right?
It's a difficult situation, but all we can do is believe in Naruto.
Right now, we're the only team who can
work smoothly with Kakashi-sensei's.
mijika ni arumono
You've gotta be extra careful
tsune ni ki wo tsuketeinai to
with the things nearest to you
amari ni chikasugite
You know the closer you get to something
miushinatteshimaisou
the tougher it is to see it
anata ga saikin taiken shita
Explain to me this happiness
shiawase wa ittai nan desu ka?
that you just got to experience.
megumaresugeteite
Or maybe you're so blessed
omoidasenai kamo
that you can't even remember?
ima koko ni iru koto
That you stand here now
iki wo shiteiru koto
That you live and breathe
tada sore dake no koto ga
They're all little miracles
kiseki da to kizuku
just by themselves.
mijika ni arumono
You've gotta be extra careful
tsune ni ki wo tsuketeinai to
with the things nearest to you
amari ni chikasugite
You know the closer you get to something
miushinatteshimaisou
the tougher it is to see it
You know the closer you get to something
And I'll never take it for granted
oitsuzuketekita yume
It's fine to say "Never give up."
akiramezuni susume yo nante
and "Keep chasing your dreams."
kirei koto wo ieru hodo
But the more time you spend talking big
nanimo dekichainai kedo
the less you get done.
hitonigiri no yuuki wo mune ni
I'll press that handful of courage against my heart
ashita wo ikinuku tame ni
and with its help, survive another day
And I'll never take it for granted
Let's go
Kakuzu's Ability
Yes, I've almost got it!
And when I finish, I'll catch up to Sasuke!
Indeed.
But you need to be wary of Sasuke's fire element.
It's time I explained the elemental vulnerabilities
of the five nature manipulation types.
What're elemental vulnerabilities?
To put it simply, fire, water, wind, lightning and earth each have an elemental advantage and vulnerability connecting them to the other elements.
What's that mean?
Let me draw you a picture.
There are five types of nature manipulation.
Here they are, drawn in a circle.
Fire
Wind
Water
Lightning
Earth
Here they are, drawn in a circle.
So, let's take fire.
Now I'll add its relationships.
Fire
Wind
Water
Strong
Weak
It's stronger than wind,
but at the same time, it's weak against water.
Weak
Each element has an advantage over another and is weak to another.
Fire
Wind
Water
Lightning
Earth
Strong
Weak
Okay...
And?
He doesn't get a word I'm saying...
Dumbing it down even further,
Naruto, your wind element techniques will lose
against Sasuke's fire element ones.
The only way to beat fire is water.
Why can't wind beat fire?
Think about it for a minute.
When fire comes into contact with wind, it burns stronger.
But if you throw water on it, it goes out.
In other words, if you countered Sasuke's fire techniques with a wind one of the same strength, it'd backfire by making the fire even larger.
But take a look at wind's relationships.
Wind is weak against fire, but strong against lightning.
Fire
Wind
Water
Lightning
Earth
Strong
Weak
Meaning that your new technique can overcome Sasuke's ultimate lightning technique Chidori!
Naruto, it's a good thing you didn't have an earth affinity.
So I have the correct affinity for Sasuke, right?
Right. Wind is the one element that can defeat lightning.
No, I mean...
The only thing that can save a fire from dying, and give it even more power, is wind.
Yeah, that's true.
Naruto!
You're awesome!
Your training is progressing well, I see.
I guess!
You'll be finished soon, right?
No, hold on a minute.
Give us a little more time.
There's something I want to try.
What's going on?
This is just like Raidou-senpai described!
It's gotta be a body-solidifying technique!
That's his ability!
Another good analysis.
You're right. No physical attack can harm me.
I accounted for their abilities up to a point, but this is...
If direct attacks won't work, what do we do?
Shikamaru...
Cower in fear, you pathetic atheists!
Yeah, now it's our turn!
Kakuzu, break this technique already!
Sure.
H-How the hell...? I couldn't even sense you, and you got me from behind?
Too bad for you.
Cower in fear, you pathetic atheists!
Yeah, now it's our turn!
Kakuzu, break this technique already!
Sure.
H-How the hell...? I couldn't even sense you, and you got me from behind?
Too bad for you.
Amazing!
What the hell happened?
I thought physical attacks didn't work on you!
That's right! Kakashi-sensei, how did you...?
I saw everything. I watched you perform that iron-skin technique.
The seals you used were for earth-typed nature manipulation.
It only took me a second. You managed to read my seals at that speed?
And to use such a powerful lightning technique...
Now I get it! You're Sharingan Kakashi!
Earth is weak against lightning.
You got matched with the wrong guy.
And now you're dead.
Kakashi-sensei really is amazing!
Now we've just got one left to worry about!
He was so quick! Kakashi-sensei really is incredible!
Yeah. Things would be a lot tougher if we
didn't take out the mortal one first.
Are you okay, Shikamaru?!
It's getting tough.
Kakashi-sensei!
His Shadow Mimic's reaching its limit.
Did he get your heart?
You can't just go around getting killed outta nowhere. Man, you suck!
You're next.
We've got him!
That's what he gets for acting cool and saying crap like, "You're dead."
What happened?
There's no way I missed his heart!
Nice. Now let's slaughter these idiots!
I intend to.
I can't hold the Shadow Mimic any longer.
Um, Shikamaru, what's going on?
And why didn't that guy die after getting hit by Raikiri?
Dunno.
But with these two, nothing they do surprises me anymore.
Finally, I can move.
What are those?
So, are you ready to kill them, Kakuzu?
Yeah.
Wh-What are those?!
The chakra they're giving off is disgusting.
Lord Jashin, watch me!
I'm gonna go nuts, seriously, go crazy, non-stop insane on all of 'em!
Get ready, Chouji!
What?
Kakuzu! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
One of 'em died right after you let it out!
God, could you suck any more?
If one of those masks died right after it was released,
then it must've been what I hit with Raikiri.
I have to remember that.
Hidan, sit this one out.
I'm going to fight him.
Hold up!
No way! I'm getting really pissed that they keep tricking me!
Let's do it like always, 'kay?
Fuuton, Atsugai!
(Fuuton, Atsugai: Wind Element, Bleeding Force)
Chouji, be careful!
Kakashi-sensei!
No way... He even attacked his partner!
That's right! They're taking advantage of his immortality!
Here it comes, Chouji.
No, they can't let that hit them!
Chouji, Shikamaru, get away!
Raiton, Gian!
(Raiton, Gian: Lightning Element, Mock Darkness)
Shield
It won't make it in time!
Watch out!
Kakashi-sensei...
Are you okay?
Well, I'll survive.
These guys are strong!
Especially the one in the mask.
No one should be able to use elemental attacks at this level unless they had the innate affinity for the element.
But he's already used earth, wind, and now lightning!
What the hell is going on?!
I'm impressed.
You're the first person to survive that combo, Hatake Kakashi.
His Sharingan saved him again.
But can he keep it up?
What?!
Katon, Zukokku!
(Katon, Zukokku: Fire Element, Cranium Carver)
kondo wa itsu aeru ka nante
What made me think
sonna kao shite yoku ierutte
"How can you say that with a straight face?"
omotteta yo nande darou
when you asked, "When will we meet again?"
any time shaberisugi no KY
Any time you talk too much, I know you don't get it.
chirari miseru tsuyogari na “I cry„
For a moment, I see your bluff and I cry.
namida no kouka wa dore kurai?
Do my tears even work on you?
watashi narini “ai saretai„
I keep saying "I want to be loved"
afureru no ni kimi ga mienai
in my own special way, but you still don't get the hint.
nido to kimi ni aenai
I have this nagging feeling
sonna ki ga surunda...
that I'll never see you again...
tsutaetai no ni umai kotoba miataranai
I wish I could tell you, but I can't find the words
watashi tabun uso demo ii no ni
Maybe I'd rather listen to you lie,
“ikanai de„ mo ienai yo
I can't even say "Don't leave me."
nigitteta te ga hanaretara
When you let go of my hand,
kimi wa itsuka wasurechau no?
will you forget
watashi no koto
about me?
tsutaetai no ni umai kotoba miataranai watashi tabun
I wish I could tell you, but I can't find the words
uso demo ii no ni “ikanai de„ mo ienai yo
Maybe I'd rather listen to you lie, I can't even say "Don't leave me."
Next Episode
It'd be easier to fight them if we could just split them up.
Which means we need someone to take care of Hidan.
Then we'll use my Mind-Body Switch technique!
No, that's too risky.
Then I'll fight him.
I can't let you go, either!
If he even scratches you with an attack and gets your blood, you're finished!
But-!
I'll handle him all by myself.
And fulfill that role as well.
The Terrifying Secret
Next time: The Terrifying Secret.
Sai-kun, what are you doing in a place like this?
Just drawing...
What's this? You're not very energetic.
You look pale!
I always do.
A burning vigor is what makes the youth young! And you're lacking passion!
Okay, I'm going to give you a very special item as a present!
This!
What is that?
This gorgeous suit is specially made so it breathes,
is durable, and always fits perfectly.
It's the perfect bodysuit!
Of course, I wear one, too!
This is a highly sought-after item and is hard to get your hands on!
Look at these beautiful body lines!
I guarantee that if you wear it during training once,
you'll never be able to stop!
This is truly a miracle gown for all youth!
A miracle gown?
Just between the two of us, this suit has made
both Naruto and Lee power up big time!
Naruto, too?
So that's what happened. So how does it look?
To be blunt, gay.