While Sai is recovering, Sora-kun will be a member of our squad.
So we need to practice our formations again.
Yes, sir!
Screw that. I wanna do nature manipulation training!
The goon says something smart for a change!
What do you mean, for a change?
Oh, yeah!
There's something I want ask you, Captain Yamato.
I've got a bunch of questions about
chakra elements and nature manipulation.
Oh, boy... If I answer you, you'd better take today's training seriously!
All right...
Good. What's your question?
Captain Yamato, you said you make wood element
by combining water and earth, right?
That's right. I have two attributes, water and earth.
And Kakashi-sensei said that once you become
a jounin, you'd be able to use two or more.
Will I be able to use water element or something else someday?
That depends.
You carry an affinity for certain nature
elements from the day you're born,
so the only way to know if you're also water-natured is to research.
Meaning no matter how much I train,
it'll be pointless if I don't have it.
Since your main nature is wind, any
others you might have are too faint.
Jounin train in order to draw out their
second and third element natures.
So is it rare for someone to have all five elements?
There are no shinobi that can use all five. At least, none that I know of.
Then how...?
Fuuton, Hana Chiri Mai!
(Fuuton, Hana Chiri Mai: Wind Element, Falling Petal Dance)
How could she...?
Was that your only question?
Then we'll start our formation training.
You're going to make a temporary team like
that learn formations? That's a waste of time.
Asuma-san!
Naruto isn't the type to think before acting, for starters.
The same goes for Sora.
Don't lump me in with him!
What?
They're both power-types who are
better suited to charging straight in.
Put them in front, let them clear a path,
and send the rest of the team in after them.
I don't disagree, but...
Follow them?
There's no way you'll get those two
to learn a new formation so suddenly.
Just have them work alongside one
another for a while to get a rapport going.
And after that?
Then comes formation training.
You're right. For the time being, they should work individually.
Yes!
That means we can continue our training from before, right?
Right?! Right, Captain Yamato?!
Err, not without Kakashi-senpai here...
Come to think of it, Asuma-san,
you're on standby right now, aren't you?
Since you all have wind-natured chakra,
it'd be best to have Asuma-san train you!
Thanks a bunch, Asuma-sensei!
I asked him first!
So what?
Get lost!
Shut up, you stupid-!
He completely turned it around on me...
Jackass!
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
must be expressed with words.
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
Habataitara
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
to that blue, blue sky
aoi aoi ano sora
The Two Kings
The two of you did this?
Yeah!
The ones more than halfway in are mine.
You liar!
You want a piece of me?
The hell was that for?!
Let me remind you that I have no obligation to help you train.
Now if you're ready to behave, take your kunai,
focus on a mental image of wind chakra, and throw.
You didn't have to hit me...
Just wait, I'll show you!
Their throws are this powerful without using a chakra blade?
I see.
How was that, Asuma-sensei?
Mine was better than his, right?
Take a closer look, you goon!
What was that?
Listen up!
Watch me carefully.
Can you see the difference?
The hole is smaller.
Yes. The point of this training is to improve
your ability to mentally focus on wind chakra.
You two opened big holes in the tree bark.
In other words, you're thinking about destruction, not wind.
If you're thinking about anything besides
making it thin and sharp, it won't come out right.
The size of the hole represents how far your thoughts have strayed!
I see! The size of Sora's hole represents
how far his thoughts have strayed!
It's not as big as yours, though.
That's bull! Mine's three times better than yours!
Mine's five times better!
Oh yeah? Mine's seven!
Well, they can do this because they have incredible chakra.
I already knew about Naruto, but Sora, too?
This isn't about how many kunai you throw!
Concentrate on the image each time!
Yes, sir!
Okay!
Make your chakra more and more like the wind.
Here I go!
I won't lose!
This is Sora's...
You said there's a message from Chiriku-san?
We've learned something unexpected about Sora.
Sora is Kazuma's son?
Kazuma is old news. The problem is what happened after that.
This information is unknown to the outside, but about ten years ago,
there was a disaster that almost
completely wiped out the Fire Temple.
Once I received word of it, I ran back to the temple, but what I saw...
...was like a scene straight out of a nightmare.
The Fire Temple, the impenetrable iron fortress...
...was completely destroyed.
Clear the way!
Are you all right?
Chiriku-sama...
What happened here?
It wasn't human!
Not human? What did it look like?
Everything...was engulfed in an evil chakra...
Hey!
We'll take him.
It was horrific.
What the hell happened here?
I don't know.
Sora suddenly started acting strangely,
and we weren't able to do anything about it.
We all tried keeping him under control, but
what you see are the results of what happened.
Sora did this...?
After that, we thoroughly investigated Sora's body,
but we never found the cause.
We kept Sora under tight surveillance,
but he never lost control after that.
But, those who remembered the incident feared and loathed
Sora's powers, and began ostracizing the boy himself.
So this is why Sora seemed so alone at the Fire Temple.
But what caused it?
Unfortunately, we still don't know what
caused Sora-kun to go out of control.
That's right.
And that's why Chiriku is concerned as well.
It seems like he wants us to find out
more while Sora is here in Konoha.
I see.
When you think about it, Sora is just like...
He is.
All right!
It's getting dark!
You can continue tomorrow!
Tomorrow?
Kickass!
He's gonna train us tomorrow, too!
Um, no-!
Yes! Yes!
Damn it all...
Okay! I'm gonna train my ass off again today!
No fair!
Damn it... One more round!
I'm not done yet!
Jeez... I can't believe their stamina!
Why exactly do I have to treat you to lunch
on top of babysitting your training, again?
Here! Sorry for the wait!
Let's eat!
Check please!
Okay!
Come again!
Boy, I'm stuffed!
Well then, I'm done watching over you two now.
Now you've gotta work on getting the hang of it on your own.
Yeah! I'll master it in no time!
That's one dirty loincloth.
It's just old!
Dad's was nice and clean!
I don't really remember Dad's face.
But even now I remember that spotless loincloth.
To me, Dad was just like it, a shining bright light.
But I heard people say things.
Gossip about how he was assassinated
for trying to take over the Fire Country.
So I was really happy when you told me it wasn't true, Mister Asuma!
Okay! I'm off to continue my training!
That's cheating!
Wait, Sora.
It's just about time. Come hang out with me for a bit.
Mantendou
Ninja Tools
Here we are.
This is...
Pops, is my order ready yet?
Oh, Asuma!
I went through a lot of effort trying to get all the metal for this.
Here!
Th-This is...
My...
Why?!
I had your broken claws repaired with
the metal that chakra-based blades use.
This is the right size for you, right?
I always feel naked when I don't have this on me!
How long have you been using that?
From the day I was born!
But, why'd you...?
Oh, did Chiriku-sama ask you to?
There's something you're supposed to say when
someone gives something to you, remember?
Ow! That hurts, Mister Asuma!
Don't call me Mister, I'm not that old!
This is all the help you'll be getting from me.
The rest is all up to you and your motivation.
I've always been all on my own!
I don't need your help!
Sheesh, what an ingrate.
But Chiriku was right.
He'll do better in our village than in that temple.
The Fire Country doesn't need two leaders!
Konoha is nothing more than one of his armies!
There doesn't need to be a Hokage!
We only need one leader, the Feudal Lord!
Feudal Lord-sama, please forgive me for disturbing your sleep.
You're betraying us, Asuma?!
The Feudal Lord doesn't agree with your plans!
He left things here to me and went somewhere that he'll be safe!
Asuma!
Kazuma!
I'm the one who killed Kazuma.
You look really wound-up.
Kurenai? Wanna go see a movie?
That's not like you.
You smoke too much.
Why don't you quit?
Hey, I would if I could.
Dad, buy me some fried sweet potatoes!
Hey, pops, three fried sweet potatoes please!
Comin' right up!
I thought Sora would follow me.
Kid, you're so cute I'm gonna give you an extra one for free!
Thank you so much!
Hey, say thank you!
Thanks, Mister!
Atta boy! Here's another one for ya!
There's something you're supposed to say when
someone gives something to you, remember?
Thank you, huh?
Come again!
Hey.
You're from the other day!
Walking around enemy territory out
in the open... What are you scheming?!
So close-minded.
You telling me Konoha's on your side?
I told you, you've got an incredible power
that the heavens bestowed upon you, didn't I?
What a waste.
I could use that power of yours for the greater good!
Like I'm gonna listen to you!
Don't make a scene.
I came out here because there was
something I had forgotten to tell you.
You'll love this.
The one who killed your dad was the traitor and former
member of the 12 Ninja Guardians, Sarutobi Asuma.
Of course, whether you believe me or not is up to you.
Why would Mister Asuma...?
Those are for him.
Later!
Danzou's vanished?!
Sora!
You've been acting kinda weird ever since you came back.
Did something hap-?
Shut up!
Don't bug me!
Kodomo no koro mita niji wo
If I look up now for the rainbow I saw as a boy,
ima miageru to nana iro de wa naku
there are no longer the seven colors,
Yagate kiri ga kakari
only mist and fog...
Jikan wa sugi kawatte yuku
As time passes by, and the world around me changes,
Kimi wo sagashitemo doko ni mo inai
no matter where I search for you, you're nowhere to be found.
Me wo toji, kokoro hiraite
So I close my eyes, and open my heart...
mata nagamete mitemo nanimo kawaranai no ka
I need to know, if I gaze up again,
tashikamete mitai
will things be different this time?
Sunao ni narereba kono kiri ga hareru to
Maybe if I was more honest, the fog would fade away.
kokoro ni negai sou sakenderu
So I pray, screaming that wish deep within my soul.
Nanika wo nakushiteshimatta koto de sou
When you lose one thing,
te ni shita mono mo kitto arun darou
you gain another, don't you?
Dakedo mada bokura wa otona ni tomadoi
But still, no matter how often the adults confuse us,
ikite yuku sube sagashiteru
we'll keep looking for the right way to live our lives.
Next Episode
The coup d'etat that the 12 Ninja Guardians began is underway.
The requiem is playing.
Konoha, caught up in the affair, has lost all of its light.
It's being devoured in darkness.
Everyone is clutching their own beliefs as the final battle begins.
Konoha completely locked down! The strict guard
Naruto Shippuuden Special
It airs on Thursday July 3rd at 7:59 PM!
Hey, Asuma-senpai, lissen to this!
I'm listening!
This is such a pain...
I know that my wood element moves are the
only thing that can hold back Naruto, but...
Oh yeah?
But'cha know, he's got a like hunnerd times more
chakra than any normal person! A hunnerd times!
There's no way I can hold out!
And Kakashi's just watching, right?
I've heard this like three times already!
Damn it! Why's he so good at manipulating people?
He always dumps alla the hard labor on me!
I already heard that one, too.
It's all good! I'm the one who's at fault, after all!
Back when I was in ANBU, he'd change our strategy outta nowhere!
It always worked for the best in the end, though.
But'cha know, I think that's pretty dangerous sometimes!
Hey, Asuma-senpai, are you listening to me?!
Karaoke Bar
Sorrow and Joy
Oh man, now he's gonna sing?
Karaoke Bar
Sorrow and Joy