Press down hard on the gas
That's right' there's no compromise
We'll slip through the night
At the final moment push hard
That's right' all the way to zero'
Until we wipe away the days
Gently open your heart
If you pull it close to you
It will reach you' without a doubt
It will come' closer
Now
We're speeding through life' squeezing it for all of its worth
Our feet are tied
But we still keep going farther
Even if i take it back' and grasp it
If you're not the one
There will be no meaning
And so we'll go far off into the distance.
I like your determination!
Then...
For those who are still here...
the first test...
you have passed it!
You've passed through the gates!
The first test for the chunin exams has been completed...
i wish you well.
All right! Wish us well!
What a funny guy...
huh...
i didn't think that there would be a guy who would pass the first test
With a blank test sheet.
Naruto uzumaki. He really is a funny guy.
The chunin exam stage 2. The forest of death!
There's something kind of creepy about this place.
This place is called the forest of death, you'll soon realize why.
"The forest of death, you'll soon realize why."
That kind of threat won't work on me one bit!
I'm not scared!
Really?
You've got a lot of energy.
A kid like you dies at very beginning,
Dappled with the red blood i like.
I'm returning your... kunai knife...
thank you for taking the trouble...
But... don't stand behind me, thirsty for blood.
If you don't want a quick death...
well, it's my nature to act up at the sight of red blood.
And my precious hair was cut, so i got excited...
naruto...
i'm sorry...
w what with that proctor?
Frankly' she's psycho!
This one' too...
that girl' why was her tongue so long?
Evidently, we've got a lot of hot blooded kids this time.
This will be fun.
You're the most hot blooded! Believe it!
Well, before we start the second exam, i have to pass this out to you!
It's a consent form,
Before you can take part in the test you have to sign this.
Why?
F-Rom here on out, corpses are going to come out,
I have to get your consent to that!
Or it'll be my responsibility.
Well, i'm going to start the explanation for the second exam.
In a word, the limits of your survival will be challenged.
Survival' huh? This test is a total pain.
F-Irst, i'll give you step-By -Step instruction on the terrain of this training f-Ield.
Training field number 44 is surrounded by 44 locked entrance gates,
There are rivers and a forest and a tower in the middle.
It's about 10 kilometers from the towers to the gate...
in this confined area, you will go through a certain survival program.
The contents of which are...
anything goes scroll battle!
Scroll...?
Yes...
i want you to fight for two scrolls, the heaven scroll and the earth scroll.
All together 26 teams got through the fiirst test.
HaIf of them...
13 teams get the heaven scroll, the other haIf get the earth scroll.
I'll hand over one scroll to each team.
To put it simply, that 'swhat you 're vying for.
And the conditions to pass?
Three of you bring both the heaven and earth scrolls to the tower in the center.
That means that of the 13 teams, haIf of them will fail for sure...
Ex. Cept it has to be in time.
For this second exam, the time limit is 120 hours.
Do it in exactly fiive days!
F-Ive days.
What do we do about food?
Be seIf sufficient! It's a treasure trove in the wilderness.
There's more than enough for food...
however...
it's teeming with fierce people eating animals,
Poison bugs, poisonous weeds and much more.
Noway...
f-Ool, that 'swhy it 's called survival!
Besides, it's improbable that 39 people, 13 teams will pass.
The interval for activity gets longer with passing each day,
While the time for recovery gets shorter...
seems pretty grueling!
On top of that, you're surrounded by nothing but enemies,
Even falling asleep will be a problem...
and, besides those injured during attempts to capture scrolls...
therewill defiinitely be people
Are unable to endure the rigors of the course.
Umm... so you can quit in the middle of it?
According to the rules, you cannot give up in the middle of it!
I want you to spend five days in the forest.
Just like i thought...
this is going to be a pain!
Moving on, conditions of disqualification.
Number 1, if all three members of the team can't make it to the tower
With the heaven and earth scrolls within the time limit.
Number 2, if a team loses a member or if a member became incapacitated.
There's that, and this is a supplement...
absolutely do not look at the contents of the scrolls
Until you have reached the tower!
W what happens if we look at it haIfway through?
When you look at it you'll find... out!
Huh?
There are times when a chunin must deal with super secret text.
This is to test your reliability.
That's all the explanation!
I'll exchange your three consent forms for the scrolls in that hut over there.
After that, pick your entrance, and all the gates will open simultaneously!
F-Inally, just aword of advice...
don't die!
I see' so you won't know which scroll was given to each team...
and you won't know which of the three people is carrying the scroll.
If what lbiki said was right'
There will be life or death struggles for information in this test.
Everyone is an enemy!
The resolve of everyone here is strong.
That means that it might come to killing each other.
It looks like they understand the meaning of the consent form a little bit...
heeey, lookwho 's here!
It's billboard brow, isn't it?
I thought you went home long ago, i never imagined you were still here.
Ooooh? Lookwho 's here, the ugly inopig.
Starting now, it 's fiive days of the survival testwith sasuke.
There's no reason to go home.
- Ugly! - Billboard!
- Ugly! Ugly! - Billboard! Billboard!
- Ugly, ugly, ugly! - Billboard, billboard, billboard!
- Billboard, billboard, billboard! - Ugly ugly ugly!
- Ugly, ugly, ugly, ugly! - Billboard, billboard, billboard, billboard!
Sakura, this is impossible for you.
For your own sake, just hurry up and go home!
I could say the exact same thing to you!
Hey, why are those two on such bad terms?
D-Do you think i care about something stupid like that?
Man... all there is to do is write my name,
Why does it take this much time!
Hey! Hinata! What are you doing over there?
N-Naruto...
Umm... uhhhh..Well...
just like i thought' this kid is strange.
A scratch...
Uh um... this... is
See ya!
Naruto...
it's about time for the scroll exchange.
Well' i wonder how many teams will survive...
teamswho have taken the scroll,
Stay with the representative and move to the gate!
We'll all start simultaneously in 30 minutes!!
Yeah! Survival is our forte!
Hinata, don't show your weakness.
Uh, okay...
life or death...
it's a pain but we just have to do this.
Since it's come to this, naruto will be our target.
For snacks, there's potato chips...
- what about shortcake.? - I can't believe you two!
Okaay! I won't lose!
I'll bring down whoever comes near me.
- Yes! - Cha!
Heh heh... fiinally the opportunity is here...
we have the chance to fuIfill our mission in earnest...
sure' the enemy teams are scary but'
I'm really scared of spending five days with this guy.
Target the rookies first.
They said that from now on it's okay to kill,
Which makes it easier.
Master guy' i'll do my best! I'll definitely succeed!
We now start the second test of the chunin ex. Am!
Look for the brats!
Those three, right?
All right! Let's go!
Okay! First, we search for that thing.
Can you do it, hinata?
Yes.
Byakugan!
Slow down, lee! We just started.
I know. But...
i can't stay still!
Who knows what kind of powerful foe is waiting for us.
Hot-Blooded fool...
as you already understand, we have only one target!
W what are you doing, choji?
Just a little break... i'm already tired, and hungry...
what are you suddenly saying?!
It hasn't been five minutes since we started!
But i can't help it. I'm hungry...
you! If you were able to bring snacks,
You should have been able to bring one k unai knife!
Ino! Hide!
Uh oh!
This kind of thing continuing for five days...?
Anyway, the tower is the goal for everyone, right?
So it would be clever for us to make a trap in the vicinity of the tower.
Okay..Wasting no time, huh?
Where are they?
Heh... kids.
It's like begging to be found, standing in that conspicuous place.
They sensed our presence,
But, evidently they haven't grasped where we are.
What happened? You're pale.
W what is that?!
The flying leeches of leaf village sense body temperature and perspiration,
Then in mass, swoop down on their prey.
If they continue to suck your blood for five minutes,
You go to the other world...
using this behavior,
We'd set a trap on the path enemies would use to escape.
D-Darn it...
that's one team gone!
It sounds like they've already started.
Wasn't that someone screaming just now?
I i'm kinda getting nervous.
I it was nothing. Sakura. Believe it!
I i have to pee...
Y you... fool!
What are you doing in front of a lady!
Go to the grass!
Aah, that was a lot! I'm refreshed.
Like i said, not in front of a lady!
S sasuke... no matter what, you don't have to go that far.
W what was that for...?
What are you doing... all of a sudden?!
What you ask? That's my line, isn't it?
Sasuke!
It can't be helped!
Sasuke, please stop!
Look closely at him!
Talk! Where's the real naruto!
I have no idea what you're talking about!
What happened to the scratch on you face?
I'm asking what happened to the scratch you got before from the proctor!
And your shuriken holster is on your left leg.
That guy's right handed!
You 'reworse at transforrmation than naruto, you phony!
Unlucky! You got me. In that case...
which one of you got the scroll?
If you listen to me obediently, i'll spare your lives.
I see! Then i'll resort to force!
Hey' can you hear it?
The clear' blue sky goes on and on
The ocean spans limitlessly
Please keep that smile on your face forever
Or else i'll cry
You won't have to search around you
It's all ok now.
Everyone is inside this hand
When you want to cry' and you want to run away
When you forget what happiness is
Just sing.
Light is born' and darkness was born
The two are one
Harmonia' feel the telepathy
Hey' can you hear it?
Aww, stupid gas mask man!
Suddenly sneaking up on someone when they're peeing!
I messed up just a little bit.
Now i have to hurry and meet up with sakura.
Wait a minute! What is this giant snake?
Hey! Are you serious?! Wait a minute, hey!
i've been gulped down!
Next episode: "eat or be eaten: panic in the Forest"
Will i return to action?!