Katon, Zukokku!
Fire, too?!
Chouji, Ino, you all right?!
Yes!
Yeah...
Not too shabby.
mijika ni arumono
You've gotta be extra careful
tsune ni ki wo tsuketeinai to
with the things nearest to you
amari ni chikasugite
You know the closer you get to something
miushinatteshimaisou
the tougher it is to see it
anata ga saikin taiken shita
Explain to me this happiness
shiawase wa ittai nan desu ka?
that you just got to experience.
megumaresugeteite
Or maybe you're so blessed
omoidasenai kamo
that you can't even remember?
ima koko ni iru koto
That you stand here now
iki wo shiteiru koto
That you live and breathe
tada sore dake no koto ga
They're all little miracles
kiseki da to kizuku
just by themselves.
mijika ni arumono
You've gotta be extra careful
tsune ni ki wo tsuketeinai to
with the things nearest to you
amari ni chikasugite
You know the closer you get to something
miushinatteshimaisou
the tougher it is to see it
You know the closer you get to something
And I'll never take it for granted
oitsuzuketekita yume
It's fine to say "Never give up."
akiramezuni susume yo nante
and "Keep chasing your dreams."
kirei koto wo ieru hodo
But the more time you spend talking big
nanimo dekichainai kedo
the less you get done.
hitonigiri no yuuki wo mune ni
I'll press that handful of courage against my heart
ashita wo ikinuku tame ni
and with its help, survive another day
And I'll never take it for granted
Let's go
Kakashi-sensei!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Though I've been using my Sharingan this whole time, plus four Raikiris...
We need to finish this quickly.
They're really good at combo attacks.
And Kakashi-sensei's Raikiri attack definitely connected!
How is he not dead?
Yeah, I was sure I crushed his heart.
He should be dead.
But what I actually killed was one of the masked monsters that came out of his back.
We should assume that it died in his place.
It was the same when he dismantled my shuriken shadow mimic.
Something like a heart was attached to his arm, and it moved independently.
What do you mean?
Each of those monsters must have its own heart, along with his real one, and so they're all his.
In other words, he has five hearts.
How can he-?!
Although Kakashi-sensei's Raikiri took one down.
Then, we have to eliminate the four remaining hearts in order to kill him for good?
Yeah.
Very sharp. You're absolutely right.
Each one contains a heart taken from a shinobi I've killed.
I'll have to stock back up...
...and your hearts will be perfect!
Now I see.
By connecting his chakra circulatory system to multiple hearts, he changes his chakra's nature to that of the original owner's.
No wonder he can use so many types of nature manipulation.
Oh, by the way,
does Konoha bury their dead?
'Cuz if they do, it's gonna suck ass.
Kakuzu's gonna be all, "We have to dig up the bounty and take him to the exchange point!"
That fire-spitting bastard, I expected to get a little more mileage outta him...
But in the end, he was worthless!
Says the guy whose head he chopped off...
Shut your goddamned hole!
I know you guys came here looking for revenge, but that ain't happening with your skills.
You all look like kids. I guess you were his students?
With such a pussy for a teacher, it's no wonder you can't handle us.
Don't insult Asuma-sensei like that!
Chouji...
One of those priceless student-teacher bonds?
What a crock!
You bastard!
Chouji!
What was so great about that dickhead,
you fat fuck?!
Chouji!
You dumbass! You see what happens when you let yourself get riled up so easily?
S-Sorry...
Chouji!
At this rate...
Die.
You little tart.
Shikamaru!
Worms.
Die now.
End of the line!
Water
Come on!
You guys okay?
Yeah...
More or less.
Dude, that was weak.
What was up with that?
Same goes for you, being fooled by a shadow clone.
Oops, you saw that?
Shikamaru, what's our next move?
We have to separate them.
Then corner them individually.
After we eliminate their ability to do combo attacks, we'll focus on destroying his four remaining hearts.
But to be successful, someone will have to distract Hidan.
I'll do it!
I've got the most chakra, plus I'm not skilled in straight fighting, so I'll use my Mind-Body Switch and-
No way. That technique only works when I hold the target down with the Shadow Mimic.
If you miss, you won't return to your body for several minutes.
It's too risky.
I'll do it.
I'll bind him with my shadow, and then lead him away.
How do you plan on snaring him, though?
You need to distract him for that, too.
Then, I'll-
Nope.
If his attacks draw a single drop of blood from you, you're dead.
It's like last time. Our team charging in to attack is the wrong move.
Chouji.
You both need to save your chakra for fighting the masked guy with Kakashi-sensei.
I'll capture him by myself.
And...
I'll fulfill that role as well.
I'll capture him by myself.
And...
I'll fulfill that role as well.
Okay. We leave him to Shikamaru.
Take this.
This again?
Are my scythe and abilities that scary?
You're fighting me!
Oh, come on!
Still sneaking off to attack from a distance? You pussy!
Way too slow!
He threw them with his shadow?
He can't dodge in the air!
We got him!
Give me some credit.
That technique's a total joke as long as I stay focused on your shad-
What?!
I wasn't just keeping my distance, and I'm no pussy!
Shadow Mimic Technique, successful.
You son of a bitch...
Go, Shikamaru!
Leave the rest to us!
We're counting on you!
Right.
Let's take a little walk together, just you and me.
Hey, where the hell are you taking me?!
Trying to separate me from Kakuzu, huh?
You little shit!
You sure you want to let him go alone?
He's severely underestimating Hidan.
That Shikamaru kid would've become a big bounty one day.
But now, he'll be dead by the end of the day.
Then again, I can't fault your logic.
I'm strong, myself!
And I've got a lot more experience than all of you put together.
Looking at your forehead protectors reminds me of the first Konoha shinobi I ever fought.
The First Hokage!
How old is this guy?!
Then you really are immortal?!
No, there's no such thing as true immortality in this world.
I've just managed to extend my life by stealing the hearts of powerful shinobi I defeat before my current one gives out.
I'm not getting away, right?
You can only hold that shadow move for about five minutes before you run out of juice...
And now we're all alone.
That's the best situation for me, you dipshit!
The fire and wind masks are merging!
Including my own, I had five hearts total.
Kakashi, it's only fitting I take yours to replace the one you destroyed.
Everything's ready.
I've been waiting for this.
Die!
kondo wa itsu aeru ka nante
What made me think
sonna kao shite yoku ierutte
"How can you say that with a straight face?"
omotteta yo nande darou
when you asked, "When will we meet again?"
any time shaberisugi no KY
Any time you talk too much, I know you don't get it.
chirari miseru tsuyogari na “I cry„
For a moment, I see your bluff and I cry.
namida no kouka wa dore kurai?
Do my tears even work on you?
watashi narini “ai saretai„
I keep saying "I want to be loved"
afureru no ni kimi ga mienai
in my own special way, but you still don't get the hint.
nido to kimi ni aenai
I have this nagging feeling
sonna ki ga surunda...
that I'll never see you again...
tsutaetai no ni umai kotoba miataranai
I wish I could tell you, but I can't find the words
watashi tabun uso demo ii no ni
Maybe I'd rather listen to you lie,
“ikanai de„ mo ienai yo
I can't even say "Don't leave me."
nigitteta te ga hanaretara
When you let go of my hand,
kimi wa itsuka wasurechau no?
will you forget
watashi no koto
about me?
tsutaetai no ni umai kotoba miataranai watashi tabun
I wish I could tell you, but I can't find the words
uso demo ii no ni “ikanai de„ mo ienai yo
Maybe I'd rather listen to you lie, I can't even say "Don't leave me."
Next Episode
All of his careful planning...
All of his preparations...
Along with an unwavering resolve...
He's using all of the information that Asuma traded his life for to the best of his abilities.
Now, with a heart swelling with emotion,
Shikamaru launches his counterattack on Hidan.
The Will Of Fire Is Passed On, A New Technique Bursts Forth!
Naruto Shippuuden Special
The Will of Fire is passed on! A new technique bursts forth!
It's a Naruto Shippuuden Special!
It's an hour long special!
It'll air on Thursday, December 4th at 7:59pm!
Airing Thursday, December 4th at 7:59pm!