It's not them.
Let's go.
Villains!
Please don't cause trouble, gentlemen!
You should have received a notice from the Fire Country prohibiting crossing the borders.
Well, we wanted to help out, too...
We ain't about to let a bunch of youngins outdo us!
That came outta nowhere...
Yeah...
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
must be expressed with words.
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
aoi aoi ano sora
to that blue, blue sky
An Old Monk's Prayer
The twenty platoons are searching the border and a 150km radius around the Fire Temple.
Not even an ant could slip through undetected.
Pardon me.
Here's the report from the 3rd platoon.
No signs of Akatsuki near the northern border.
None?
Reporting in!
Nothing to report from the eastern border!
We haven't located Akatsuki yet.
So...
Why haven't you found them yet?!
Team Asuma headed towards the Fire Temple, any word from them?!
Nothing yet...
Chiriku...
This's...
You all are from Konoha, correct?
Yes.
We've received word from the monk currently at your village.
I am Juushoku of the Fire Temple.
I was away for awhile, but when I heard of the horrors that had befallen the temple, I rushed back as quickly as I could.
What you see here is what I returned to.
Monks from nearby temples have been helping us recover the bodies.
This is horrible...
And where's Chiriku?
Chiriku-sama's body is the only one we haven't been able to recover.
Uh, Captain Asuma...
I really didn't want to bring this up, but Chiriku-san's corpse has a thirty million ryou bounty on the black market.
Bounty?
If they knew about the bounty...
An exchange point.
They're carrying his body there.
Izumo, where's the exchange point?
There are five, including the one closest to us.
The other platoons should reach the rest of the four locations in no time.
Good, let's move out!
Just a moment, please.
Sarutobi Asuma-dono.
Please allow me to pray for your group's safety before you head into battle.
Please.
Go ahead.
Chiriku...
I guess the 12 Ninja Guardians are down to just me now.
I wanted to talk with you one more time.
There were things I wanted to tell you...and ask you.
Please be safe on your journey.
Thank you very much.
At the very least, I'll return Chiriku's corpse.
No, no, please don't push yourself.
As a fellow former Ninja Guardian, there is surely a price on your head, as well.
Please be careful.
Don't worry about me.
My head's worth five million more than Chiriku's!
The only thing you have to worry about with Asuma is him smoking too much.
Is he not training anymore?
I made a ton of soldier pills, too.
No one's here.
Sai?
You came to check up on Naruto, too?
Well, er... Since I've been injured, I'm just taking a walk so I don't atrophy.
Actually, at times like this...
You guessed right.
It's better to be honest.
Is Naruto taking a break?
He must be off relaxing somewhere.
Your mind and body can't keep such a grueling pace forever.
Ramen...
Ichiraku Ramen...
Yeah, yeah, I heard you, at least try to walk a little.
That's right! Sai, you should have one of these too.
What is it?
A mud ball?
It's one of my handmade soldier pills, you jerk.
Made with my special recipe!
Special?
I suppose it's more like medicine than a soldier pill.
It's overflowing with nutritious goodness mixed with fast-acting digestive agents,
all of which I hand-picked and rolled up into one little ball packed with energy!
And in your case, it might even add a little color to that pale skin while it helps you recover!
Of course, medicine always tastes a little nasty, so it tastes kind of strange at first.
But when you consider how much your body will benefit, you won't even care about how it t-
Sai?
Sai
Thank you for the
food.
The world is spinning...
The taste and smell make you worse way before the medicine takes effect.
And...pork...cutlets...
Come on, we're here.
Hello there!
Come on in!
Th-Thanks.
Pops... Extra-large miso with pork cutlets and the works...on the double...
And here's your menu!
I said extra-large miso with pork... Hurry...
Just look at the menu, please.
Sorry, Naruto. We've got a brand-new menu starting today.
We're a tsukemen place now!
(Tsukemen are dipping noodles; the soup and noodles are served separately)
Great... Extra-large miso...pork...tons of ginger...
I'm saying we don't do ramen anymore!
So you do tsukemen exclusively now?
My daughter Ayame here went on a noodle training trip for a while,
and when she came back she said, "Dad, the age of tsukemen is here! Let's switch and unlock Ichiraku's true potential!"
She got a bit cheeky, but I took her advice.
The customer's tastes are bound to change with time!
And Ichiraku will make sure to adapt!
What the hell is wrong with you?
I've been looking forward to my extra-large miso with pork...
Does it really matter? Tsukemen's just like ramen.
Not really. Tsukemen, like soba, involves pouring sauce on the noodles before eating them.
It's the same thing in the end.
But the concept is different.
Yeah, yeah! Ramen and tsukemen are different!
And I wanna eat ramen!
Well, you can't. I only have tsukemen prepared.
Why can't you just put the noodles in the soup? Then it'll be ramen again!
How could you be satisfied with such a weak imitation?!
Naruto-kun, is your love for miso with pork really so fickle?!
It's...It's not...that...
Too much...arguing...stomach...
I don't care... Gimme some tsukemen...
Okay, three tsukemen!
Three tsukemen!
Here ya go!
Yes!
Hold it!
This noodle is undercooked...
It needs to boil another minute.
It does?
And check the water temperature!
Right!
Y-You're making it over?
One Ichiraku tsukemen, comin' up!
Finally!
Hey, where's my soup?
It's smooth, but the soup they had in Yuugao village was much more refreshing.
Make the soup over.
Right!
The first taste is critical!
The customer has to experience us at our best!
That's the spirit, Ayame!
Let's see what your training produced!
Ramen-chan...
One original Ichiraku tsukemen!
This time it's perfect!
Finally...
Hey, pops... Where's the pork...? And sprouts...
Can I have some toppings?
O-Oh... Sure thing...
What are you doing, Naruto-kun?!
If I eat it like this, it counts as ramen!
It's tsukemen!
I won't let you eat it like-
Ayame-san! Your restaurant's forgetting the most important rule...
The customer always comes first.
That comes before all the other stuff.
That's why I put my heart and soul into making tsukemen.
The best ingredients and the best methods.
To make sure the customer experiences their food in the best way, a restaurant must even ignore the customer's requests.
I want ramen, damn it!
Don't say that until you experience tsukemen the right way!
You'll never ask for ramen again!
Thank you very much.
This is so much lighter than ramen. I wouldn't mind having this again.
I'm too old for this...
Making these unfamiliar dishes has me all sore...
Maybe we should hire some kids part-time...
I guess when you're as hungry as I was, anything will taste great!
Thanks for the tsukemen-ramen!
I'm stuffed...
After all that complaining, he still inhaled everything they put in front of him...
I guess I can't complain since he ate three bowls. Even though he did it the wrong way...
Time to get back to training!
Before we do that...
Naruto, I've got something extremely cool to show you.
Extremely cool?
Now that we've eaten our fill, I've gotta explain a few more concepts to you.
Not more confusing lectures...
Relax. I'm a very smooth talker. I'll phrase it in a way you'll understand.
And here's your check...
Yamato, can you get this?
Excuse me? I thought veterans were supposed to treat their junior counterparts.
There are no "seniors" or "juniors" when it comes to people I respect.
Although among my so-called juniors, you're about the only one I respect at all.
But you're right, I should pay.
Come again!
Yep, see you!
Smooth talker, indeed!
I'm really getting fed up with the shit that keeps coming out of your mouth.
I haven't traveled in forever, and when I finally get a chance, they stick me with a jackoff like you...
We're not on vacation.
I'm already sick of looking for a Jinchuuriki when we have no idea where it is,
and now I'm getting dragged on this retarded side job.
I think I deserve a little sympathy here!
Just shut the hell up and walk.
We're already late.
We're late because we're going to your stupid exchange point!
You keep making this friggin' mission longer and longer.
Seriously, it's pissing me off.
Pissing you off?
This is a vital mission, too.
Yeah, yeah, you're the treasurer or whatever.
Admit it, that chump change is what you're charging them to help hunt the Bijuu.
Okay, I'm sorry.
That corpse is heavy, right?
Lemme take him off your hands for a while.
What're you going to do with my valuable bounty?
I'm just trying to be nice...
You'd throw him away.
The hell're you saying?
I see right through you.
This body is a nuisance, and you want to get rid of it.
Ah shit, you got me.
But seriously, dump that thing and we'll look-
Gotcha.
Lousy son of a bitch...
Hey, hey, hey!
You're done already?
I don't have time to mess around with you.
But someday, our mission will be complete, and my schedule will be wide open.
And then I'll send you straight to hell.
There you go again...
I really hope the next guy we fight lasts long enough for me to let loose on him. I really need to vent.
What're you gonna show me, Kakashi-sensei?
This is the extremely cool thing I told you about.
That's-
R-Rasengan?
Kakashi-sensei can use Rasengan, too?
iijiina riyuu
It's so very easy
issai yurusu jakuhai
for youth to forgive everything
resukyuutai mo yondeoita
I called in the rescue squad
dakara
So please kiss me, please kiss me all night
puriizu kisu mi puriizu kisu mi
datenshi no mahou ka koakuma no chachina itazura
Is it a fallen angel's magic, or a mischievous monster's prank?
tsumaranakunacchau mae ni
Before we get bored
soore de houre
Let's let go
bouringubooru
Of that bowling ball. We lead such strange lives
ibutsu na sonzai daro
shouchi no suke
You've gotta understand
kowaresoude...
We're gonna smash it...
docchirakatta kanjou de kirihirake yo
Cut through the inner turmoil
kowaresou de
We're gonna break...
kowasenai bokura no shouri
I can't break it...our victory.
Next Episode
The fight against Akatsuki finally begins.
Team Asuma gets the drop on them,
but Hidan and Kakuzu's unique abilities have them cornered.
And Captain Asuma, with no other options, makes a dramatic decision!
The Naruto Shippuuden Special
Collision Course! Akatsuki vs Team Asuma
Collision Course! Akatsuki vs Team Asuma!
The Naruto Shippuuden Showdown Special!
1 full hour!
Airing on 9.25 at 7:59 P.M.!
A full hour, airing on 9/25 at 7:59 PM!
I know this is sudden, but I've got a big announcement.
Next episode, the title of this series is changing!
Asuma Shippuuden!
I'm not buying it.
Wh-What?!
You need to let your super-popular protégé handle this.
A cool new hero for a new generation.
Shikamaru Shippuuden starts next episode.
Nothing starts next episode!
Quit horning in on my racket!
We've got a troublesome guest star already.
Listen, you!
No one but me can handle being the title character!
Right, guys?
But, uh... You don't do jack for a long time.
I don't?
Hey...
The hell...
It can't be...
I need more screen time, please!