hey' can you hear it?
The clear' blue sky goes on and on
The ocean spans limitlessly
Please keep that smile on your face forever
Or else i'll cry
You won't have to search around you
It's all ok now.
Everyone is inside this hand
When you want to cry' and you want to run away
When you forget what happiness is
Just sing.
Light is born' and darkness was born
The two are one
Harmonia' feel the telepathy
Hey' can you hear it?
The 44th training field, also known as the forest of death.
From here on it's a serious battle between the ninjas,
Anything could happen!
It's going down in earnest now!
This is getting interesting!
A life risking survival game in the forest!
I will survive without fail!
Next time: "the chunin exam stage 2: the Forest of death!
As for me, i'm going to kick butt again!