When dealing with a hostile opponent that is more skilled than you, defeat him by outnumbering him.
That is one of the basic strategies you taught us.
I didn't expect you to go this far for just one old man.
As Tsunade-sama's ordered, we will detain you and escort you back to Konoha.
This is-!
The Hidden Rain!
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
must be expressed with words.
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
Habataitara
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
to that blue, blue sky
aoi aoi ano sora
Konoha,
Completely Locked Down!
Strict Guard Naruto Shippuuden Special
When your friend's mood turns bad, it may be that a change in diet is the cause.
Like the color of udon and soba...
I don't know what the hell this book is talking about.
To be honest with you, me neither.
I know, right! I wonder if there's a key that makes it easy to understand what people are thinking.
Sakura-san said that you should learn that through experience.
No way. I don't wanna, uh...grapple with... No, uh...
Team up with... I mean...
You know, whatever they say, stick with him.
But, maybe that's better suited for you guys?
So I need to read up on it more.
I don't get it.
Just when I thought Sora was starting to get used to the village...
What happened with him?
Danzou-sama...
Where are Asuma and Yamato?
They've been summoned.
Explain yourself, Danzou!
When the border situation with the Hidden Rain is in such chaos, what is so important that you'd risk meeting with enemy shinobi?!
Are you listening?!
Just a moment, please.
I remember seeing this guy before.
When I was in ANBU, he went missing during a mission.
I believe his name is...Tatsuji.
So this is the plant that Danzou sent to the Hidden Rain.
So you've been stirring things up on your own.
I don't know what you were looking for in the Hidden Rain,
but you will share the information you've gathered.
Was the Hidden Rain involved in the attack?
You don't even have that much information.
Princess Tsunade, it's fine with me if you put on airs for the moderate faction, but your carelessness will lead the village to ruin.
You didn't plan on cooperating from the start.
Fine with me. In that case...
Stop.
Do you think he'll talk that easily?
There are plenty of ways to deal with this.
Did you call me, Fifth Hokage?
I'm counting on you, Ibiki.
Leave it to me. I'll have him talking in ten minutes.
Tsunade, why are you being so hasty?
As Hokage, you should have a better idea of the situation before making decisions like this.
Even dragging out Ibiki...
I can't accept this as part of your tactics.
There, there, looks like I've troubled you.
Danzou, Tatsuji is not only your plant.
He has been sharing information with us at the same time.
We are all Konoha citizens. Call him a double agent.
According to reports, the Hidden Rain was not involved in the border attack.
And according to Tatsuji, a few days ago, a gang of four people robbed the tombs at the Fire Temple.
Apparently the four strange priests who attacked and violated Fire Temple were on a sacred mission.
That means...
As you have seen, those four were trying to get their hands on that boy Sora from the Fire Temple.
Tsunade, you should know about what happened with that boy at the Fire Temple.
I do.
We don't know the reason, but he seems to have some special powers.
It may be connected to the theft of the corpses, or there might be something bigger going on.
And you just blithely invited him into the village.
If we're truly concerned about the village's well being, we should hurry and make a decision quickly.
But knowing this, we can't send him back to the Fire Temple.
Should we imprison him?
No. His presence would stir up fear in the villagers, so we must deal with this in a more direct manner!
So kill him?
This is your real strength.
Why is my power so hated?
This time... This time...
Mister Asuma!
Tsunade, since you are the Hokage, make a decision.
One that's beneficial for Konoha, that is.
I refuse-
Let me go!
Bastard. I'm telling you to let me go! Bastard!
Be quiet!
Sora!
He was hiding near the ceiling.
Is this a joke? What do you mean by killing me?!
Is my power that unwanted?! You guys are just like the people at the Fire Temple, aren't you?!
You are the seed of chaos!
Danzou!
Damn it, everyone. Is this what you mean by comrades?! Team Kakashi?!
Sora.
Are you saying that I am getting punished for opening up a little bit?!
Calm down, Sora!
Asuma, there's something that I want to ask you.
My... My father...
Former member of the Twelve Guardian Ninja, the traitor, Sarutobi Asuma.
Was it you who killed my father?
It was.
The one who gave the final blow to Kazuma... No, killed him, was me.
Asuma!
Kazuma!
So that's how it is.
This is...
How dare you...? How dare you? How dare you?!
Stop it!
This abnormality...
Sora, what is your power?
How dare you kill my father...?
How dare you?!
Are you okay, Sora?
Naruto!
Why did you come here?!
You said that before, didn't you?
I came here to save you.
No one asked you to.
I heard what I heard, so it can't be helped.
Bastards, why did you attack Sora?!
Root?
Sora!
Naruto?
I'm fine.
Your comrade... My father... You betrayed him!
I'll have vengeance for my father!
Sora!
Wait!
That idiot...
Naruto!
Don't let it out under any circumstances!
All of the gates are locked.
All right, we'll group together and cast a binding ritual to repel the evil.
How terrible...
All our defenses have been broken one by one...
What?
The same dream again...
The problem is that there are two kings.
The Fire Country's Feudal Lord and Konoha's Hokage.
If there are two kings, there are bound to be conflicts and suspicions.
If something were to happen, other countries could easily invade due to slow decisions.
Kazuma's idea was simple. Consolidate the Fire Country into one organization.
But what Kazuma tried to do, the two kings... It was his downfall.
After all, the people in this village follow its king.
Asuma choose to follow the Hokage, this king.
They don't get it at all. They don't understand the fundamental reason.
It only shines because of the Fire Country's true king.
Everything was for the Fire Country, That was Kazuma's purpose.
Isn't the power entrusted to you by Kazuma for that purpose?
My purpose is to avenge my father.
That's fine, but look beyond that.
To the revenge that Kazuma is longing for, that is.
Let's do it together, Sora. Let's bring Kazuma's ambitions to fruition.
If you do, I'll make sure there are plenty of opportunities for you to defeat Asuma.
The other king...
The Hokage!
Sora...
Sora!
Jeez, what a troublesome bastard.
So this is where his scent ends.
Your recovery rate is always impressive.
Everyone's looked all over for him.
He may not be in the village anymore.
No, I have a feeling that he's still somewhere in the village.
Is that so?
Well then, sleep well!
Okay!
That damn Sora...
This chakra!
This chakra's feeling...
Rage?
I'm sure of it!
Sora!
Granny Tsunade!
Are you all right, Granny?
Yeah.
Sora!
What is this chakra?!
Stop it!
Don't interfere!
Why are you after Granny?
Move, Naruto!
Tsunade-sama!
Wait!
Sora! Naruto!
Wait! Sora!
Oh, you're looking at something unusual, aren't you?
Well, sometimes.
The photos from Naruto-kun to the Third Hokage...
It shows an uninterrupted flow of generations, doesn't it?
This is...
The two advisers were really cute back then, too!
Where?!
Not cute at all!
Look! Those conceited eyes... It just shows indecency and it's just unbearable to look at them! They haven't changed a bit!
So, I wonder how that guy looked when he was younger?
That guy?
Danzou.
That's bad, Tsunade-sama!
Who cares?
Wa-! Tsunade-sama!
I found it! This is it!
All right, here it goes.
What should I say...? Better looking than I thought.
Where the heck did Sora run off to?
Wait!
Wait! Sora!
Tsunade-sama!
Sakura?
I'm having all of the team captains gather for a meeting.
I'll talk with you later.
What in the world?
Sora came here and attacked me.
No way!
Have we ever had this big a power outage before?
This may not be a normal black out.
Are we going to be okay?
Of course we're going to be okay!
We have Hokage-sama here in this village!
Are you saying you don't trust Hokage-sama?
Quit making such a fuss!
Y-You're right.
We have Hokage-sama!
It's not the breaker.
Then we need to be ready for action at all times.
Right. But we're at least prepared for emergencies.
Even the captains who are supposed to be off-duty are being summoned to the gate.
In which case...
This is super yummy!
I'm all ready!
Now I can go at full throttle!
Let's hurry, Shikamaru!
Yeah!
You can't escape me!
What's going on?
I wonder if it's a power outage.
I don't like this!
I hate the dark!
It looks like something weird is going on.
We're closing the main gate!
We've confirmed the channels are secure.
No matter where the enemy attacks from, we should be able to get there quickly.
Well done.
This is all we've got?
I guess we sent too many people to the Hidden Rain and the other villages.
As all of you can clearly see, we've completely lost power and are in a total black out.
Although there's still the possibility that this was some sort of accident,
when you consider the fact that we haven't heard from the power plant,
we should assume that someone did this intentionally and act appropriately.
As such, I'm placing the village under a Level Two state of emergency!
Squad Three will split up between the eastern, western and northern gates!
Squad Two will take the main gate!
Squad One will be in charge of going to the power plant and seeing what's causing this power outage!
Asuma, stay here.
Don't let even the smallest thing slip by! Go!
I was attacked by Sora.
By Sora?!
Luckily, no one got hurt.
Wait a second!
You mean that he attacked you, Tsunade-sama? Sora did?
Naruto's going after him right now.
I want you to go after them immediately.
You may not want to accept it, but this is reality! Deal with it!
Capture Sora once you find him!
Yes, sir.
What's wrong?
It looked like the forest moved just now.
An earthquake?
Travelers, I'm sorry, but the village is under a lock-down right now.
We can't let outsiders in-
What?!
Enemy attack verified!
They're attacking the main gate!
Squad Two has engaged in battle!
So it's begun.
Go!
Don't let them near the main gate!
How's the situation?
Stay on guard when you approach them!
I'm going to give the orders from here out!
We're going to attack in groups!
The enemy isn't slowing down! They're one kilometer from the main gate!
Security, begin preparations!
Naruto...
That way!
Sora!
Wait a second, you jerk!
Why the hell did you attack Granny Tsunade?!
Leave me alone!
This isn't any of your business!
What did you say?! Like hell this isn't my business!
Kekkaimon Gofuu Jutsu, Hachimon Heijou!
(Kekkaimon Gofuu Jutsu, Hachimon Heijou: Five Point Barrier Seal Technique, Hachi's Gate)
Wh-What?!
Hey!
There's another one at the eastern gate...
The same at the western gate!
Tsunade-sama, this is-!
We're no longer in a Level Two state of emergency! This is now a Level One!
Have everyone head towards the main gate!
Yes, sir!
Get Shikamaru!
Inform him of the situation and have him come up with a defense plan.
Yes, sir!
Sakura, prepare to head out.
Okay!
What? What's going on?
They're here! It's them!
Wait! Who are they?!
What are you doing?!
It's a defense barrier.
A defense barrier?
What?! What's going on?
The e-ne-my set a de-fense bar-rier!
De-fense bar-rier?
What's that?
Isn't it a defense barrier?
It's just like it sounds! A barrier used for defense!
You use it to block enemy attacks and set up a wall so that enemies can't break in.
Why are the enemies setting up a defense when they're the ones attacking us from the outside?
Setting up a barrier when you're trying to get inside is kinda strange.
It isn't strange!
Using defense when they're trying to break in...
In other words, we're...
That's right. Thanks to that barrier, we're trapped inside the village.
What is it now?!
We are the chosen ones, destined to bring justice to the Fire Country!
And now, the time has come to fulfill our purpose!
Listen to me for a bit. I won't talk for too long.
We have but one desire.
We want the Fire Country to have only one ruler, the Feudal Lord!
Enter
However, there is another ruler in the Fire Country who lives in this very village and is terrorizing our sole, rightful ruler.
We will not tolerate there being two rulers.
Don't you get it?!
I'm saying we don't need your boss, the Hokage!
What?!
There's no need to get worked up!
After all, you're all going to help us out.
By becoming corpses!
So a defense barrier is a techinque that prevents people from coming in or out?
Exactly.
In a situation like this, it's safe to assume that the enemy has some sort of special technique that will allow them to leave as they like.
Right now, the village has been sealed in and only the enemies are able to enter and leave at will.
Now that we've let invaders into the village, we must take the proper procedures for a Level Two surprise attack.
We can fight at any time!
No! We need to work on a counter-attack after we've helped everyone take shelter.
Your job is to move everyone to a safe location!
This will be your first A-Rank mission!
I understand!
Dismissed!
I'm counting on you!
I'm going to try to buy you some time.
He's saying whatever the hell he likes!
We won't let him lay his hands on the Fifth!
We have to hold out until backup comes.
Fudou!
Yeah!
Doton, Uitenpen!
(Doton, Uitenpen: Earth Element, Wheel of Fortune)
Move!
Tsunade-sama, I've finished my preparations.
Right now it's impossible to avoid fighting them directly.
A medical ninja's job is to save as many lives as possible.
Go!
Yes!
Although I can't say it's perfect, we've got all the medics out that we have.
But what's with this awful feeling I've got?
It's one thing after the next!
They're formidable!
This is the ultimate earth-element resuscitation technique, Land of the Corpses.
Come back to life, all of you dead bums!
You're going to be fighting against my corpse shinobi!
You don't know anything about me!
I sure don't!
Who are those guys?!
What did you do?!
Konoha tried to kill me first!
Granny Tsunade wouldn't do something like that!
She did!
I'm gonna kill them before they kill me!
I've finally caught up with you.
Asuma-sensei!
You traitor, Asuma!
Sora, why did you attack the Hokage?
The one you want revenge on...
...is me.
Don't touch me!
I just copied you!
I'm going to kill the king that you decided to follow!
King?
This time I'm going to do it!
What are you talking about?!
That doesn't even make sense!
No, it's true.
Sora, you just referred to Tsunade-sama as a king, didn't you?
The Fire Country doesn't need two kings!
There doesn't need to be a Hokage!
We only need one leader, the Feudal Lord!
According to reports, the Hidden Rain was not involved in the border attack.
And according to Tatsuji, a few days ago, a gang of four people robbed the tombs at the Fire Temple.
Apparently the four strange priests who attacked and violated Fire Temple were on a sacred mission.
As you have seen, those four were trying to get their hands on that boy Sora from the Fire Temple.
Something isn't right.
What's that?
This is horrible!
What's wrong, Asuma-sensei?!
If my guess is right, our village is in serious trouble!
Don't rush!
Stay calm and keep moving!
Most likely, the guys attacking the village want to kill everyone.
What did you say?!
Don't be ridiculous!
It's all linked together!
Why did they steal the four Lightning Masters' caskets?
Because they know all about lightning techniques and how powerful they are.
And they figured out a way to use their power to wipe out the entire village.
W-Wipe out?
Hey, Sora, is that true?!
Wiping out the village means that you'll be killing everyone!
I-I didn't know!
I don't know anything about it!
Sora!
I've got to go.
This is going to be bad if we don't stop them as quickly as possible.
Naruto, sorry, but please take care of Sora!
Yeah!
All of the pieces finally fit together.
Sora's talking about the kings, too...
I'm sure that someone in that group is trying to carry out the coup d'etat that was attempted back then.
Fully charged!
iijiina riyuu
It's so very easy
issai yurusu jakuhai
for youth to forgive everything
resukyuutai mo yondeoita
I called in the rescue squad
dakara
So please kiss me, please kiss me all night
puriizu kisu mi puriizu kisu mi
datenshi no mahou ka koakuma no chachina itazura
Is it a fallen angel's magic, or a mischievous monster's prank?
tsumaranakunacchau mae ni
Before we get bored
soore de houre
Let's let go
bouringubooru
Of that bowling ball. We lead such strange lives
ibutsu na sonzai daro
shouchi no suke
You've gotta understand
kowaresoude...
We're gonna smash it...
docchirakatta kanjou de kirihirake yo
Cut through the inner turmoil
kowaresou de
We're gonna break...
kowasenai bokura no shouri
I can't break it...our victory.
Next Episode
What did you say?!
The people attacking us right now are Fire Country shinobi?!
Yeah. Judging by their features, I'm certain that they're from the Kohaku Clan that lives near the country's border.
But, wasn't the Kohaku clan essentially killed off in that last enemy attack?
They probably brought the villagers back to life by using some sort of revival technique.
That's terrible!
I can't forgive them!
They killed so many people just to attack us!
Next time: Resurrected Souls!
Resurrected Souls
Konoha
Konoha Celebrity Profiles!
Cele
brity
Pro
fi
les
Today we're going to introduce our teacher, Ebi-sensei.
Ebi-sensei has raised many of the people who have the potential to become Hokage!
Since I'm the Third Hokage's grandson, he taught me a bunch of things.
In particular, he taught me how to control my chakra.
He even helped train Naruto-niichan some!
Despite how great he is, Sensei actually has a weakness!
A long time ago Naruto-niichan-
Konohamaru-kun, you promised that you would keep that a secret!
You mean about how you were knocked out by his Harem Technique?
K-Konohamaru-kun, keep your voice down!
I'm hungry! Ebi-sensei, treat me to a meal!
Why should I?!
Harem Techni-
Okay everyone, let's go to Ichiraku Ramen!
Yay!
Oh, boy...