I never imagined his arms could still move
on their own after being detached!
But when did he...?
When I threw the explosive tags?
He hid in the smoke long enough to send his right arm underground!
He's a true blue Akatsuki...
Their abilities are all out of this world!
You said we were finished, but you still had no idea what I was capable of.
So it was better to keep your distance as you played your next hand.
You actually think, unlike my partner.
Shit! Kakuzu!
Do something, Kakuzu!
Shit!
Now, Chouji!
Nikudan Hari Sensha!
(Nikudan Hari Sensha: Spiked Meat Tank)
Kakuzu!
My god...
It doesn't look like Naruto's taken a single break.
I wouldn't think so. He has to perfect his new technique as soon as possible, if we're going to be sent as Kakashi-sensei's backup.
The time limit's twenty-four hours, right?
It's a difficult situation, but all we can do is believe in Naruto.
Right now, we're the only team who can
work smoothly with Kakashi-sensei's.
Yes, I've almost got it!
And when I finish, I'll catch up to Sasuke!
Indeed.
But you need to be wary of Sasuke's fire element.
It's time I explained the elemental vulnerabilities
of the five nature manipulation types.
What're elemental vulnerabilities?
To put it simply, fire, water, wind, lightning and earth each have an elemental advantage and vulnerability connecting them to the other elements.
What's that mean?
Let me draw you a picture.
There are five types of nature manipulation.
Here they are, drawn in a circle.
So, let's take fire.
Now I'll add its relationships.
It's stronger than wind,
but at the same time, it's weak against water.
Each element has an advantage over another and is weak to another.
Okay...
And?
He doesn't get a word I'm saying...
Dumbing it down even further,
Naruto, your wind element techniques will lose
against Sasuke's fire element ones.
The only way to beat fire is water.
Why can't wind beat fire?
Think about it for a minute.
When fire comes into contact with wind, it burns stronger.
But if you throw water on it, it goes out.
In other words, if you countered Sasuke's fire techniques with a wind one of the same strength, it'd backfire by making the fire even larger.
But take a look at wind's relationships.
Wind is weak against fire, but strong against lightning.
Meaning that your new technique can overcome Sasuke's ultimate lightning technique Chidori!
Naruto, it's a good thing you didn't have an earth affinity.
So I have the correct affinity for Sasuke, right?
Right. Wind is the one element that can defeat lightning.
No, I mean...
The only thing that can save a fire from dying, and give it even more power, is wind.
Yeah, that's true.
Naruto!
You're awesome!
Your training is progressing well, I see.
I guess!
You'll be finished soon, right?
No, hold on a minute.
Give us a little more time.
There's something I want to try.
What's going on?
This is just like Raidou-senpai described!
It's gotta be a body-solidifying technique!
That's his ability!
Another good analysis.
You're right. No physical attack can harm me.
I accounted for their abilities up to a point, but this is...
If direct attacks won't work, what do we do?
Shikamaru...
Cower in fear, you pathetic atheists!
Yeah, now it's our turn!
Kakuzu, break this technique already!
Sure.
H-How the hell...? I couldn't even sense you, and you got me from behind?
Too bad for you.
Cower in fear, you pathetic atheists!
Yeah, now it's our turn!
Kakuzu, break this technique already!
Sure.
H-How the hell...? I couldn't even sense you, and you got me from behind?
Too bad for you.
Amazing!
What the hell happened?
I thought physical attacks didn't work on you!
That's right! Kakashi-sensei, how did you...?
I saw everything. I watched you perform that iron-skin technique.
The seals you used were for earth-typed nature manipulation.
It only took me a second. You managed to read my seals at that speed?
And to use such a powerful lightning technique...
Now I get it! You're Sharingan Kakashi!
Earth is weak against lightning.
You got matched with the wrong guy.
And now you're dead.
Kakashi-sensei really is amazing!
Now we've just got one left to worry about!
He was so quick! Kakashi-sensei really is incredible!
Yeah. Things would be a lot tougher if we
didn't take out the mortal one first.
Are you okay, Shikamaru?!
It's getting tough.
Kakashi-sensei!
His Shadow Mimic's reaching its limit.
Did he get your heart?
You can't just go around getting killed outta nowhere. Man, you suck!
You're next.
We've got him!
That's what he gets for acting cool and saying crap like, "You're dead."
What happened?
There's no way I missed his heart!
Nice. Now let's slaughter these idiots!
I intend to.
I can't hold the Shadow Mimic any longer.
Um, Shikamaru, what's going on?
And why didn't that guy die after getting hit by Raikiri?
Dunno.
But with these two, nothing they do surprises me anymore.
Finally, I can move.
What are those?
So, are you ready to kill them, Kakuzu?
Yeah.
Wh-What are those?!
The chakra they're giving off is disgusting.
Lord Jashin, watch me!
I'm gonna go nuts, seriously, go crazy, non-stop insane on all of 'em!
Get ready, Chouji!
What?
Kakuzu! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
One of 'em died right after you let it out!
God, could you suck any more?
If one of those masks died right after it was released,
then it must've been what I hit with Raikiri.
I have to remember that.
Hidan, sit this one out.
I'm going to fight him.
Hold up!
No way! I'm getting really pissed that they keep tricking me!
Let's do it like always, 'kay?
Fuuton, Atsugai!
(Fuuton, Atsugai: Wind Element, Bleeding Force)
Chouji, be careful!
Kakashi-sensei!
No way... He even attacked his partner!
That's right! They're taking advantage of his immortality!
Here it comes, Chouji.
No, they can't let that hit them!
Chouji, Shikamaru, get away!
Raiton, Gian!
(Raiton, Gian: Lightning Element, Mock Darkness)
It won't make it in time!
Watch out!
Kakashi-sensei...
Are you okay?
Well, I'll survive.
These guys are strong!
Especially the one in the mask.
No one should be able to use elemental attacks at this level unless they had the innate affinity for the element.
But he's already used earth, wind, and now lightning!
What the hell is going on?!
I'm impressed.
You're the first person to survive that combo, Hatake Kakashi.
His Sharingan saved him again.
But can he keep it up?
What?!
Katon, Zukokku!
(Katon, Zukokku: Fire Element, Cranium Carver)
It'd be easier to fight them if we could just split them up.
Which means we need someone to take care of Hidan.
Then we'll use my Mind-Body Switch technique!
No, that's too risky.
Then I'll fight him.
I can't let you go, either!
If he even scratches you with an attack and gets your blood, you're finished!
But-!
I'll handle him all by myself.
And fulfill that role as well.
Next time: The Terrifying Secret.
Sai-kun, what are you doing in a place like this?
Just drawing...
What's this? You're not very energetic.
You look pale!
I always do.
A burning vigor is what makes the youth young! And you're lacking passion!
Okay, I'm going to give you a very special item as a present!
This!
What is that?
This gorgeous suit is specially made so it breathes,
is durable, and always fits perfectly.
It's the perfect bodysuit!
Of course, I wear one, too!
This is a highly sought-after item and is hard to get your hands on!
Look at these beautiful body lines!
I guarantee that if you wear it during training once,
you'll never be able to stop!
This is truly a miracle gown for all youth!
A miracle gown?
Just between the two of us, this suit has made
both Naruto and Lee power up big time!
Naruto, too?
So that's what happened. So how does it look?
To be blunt, gay.