Zetsu?
I see you've finished the job,
and that ridiculously long sacrifice ceremony.
You all piss me off to no end!
Friggin' atheist cocksuckers!
When you're sad and alone,
the only one you can truly depend on is yourself.
No, not quite.
I say the only thing you can believe in is money.
There it is!
Seriously, your damn side jobs are why it's taking us so long to find our Jinchuuriki!
I only partnered with you because I figured I could make money off your religion.
Besides, I also have to manage Akatsuki's finances. Put yourself in my shoes for a minute.
Money is important.
Not as important as getting the next one!
I'll take the Two-Tails.
You're sure you're okay? You were in the hospital until yesterday.
Like I said, it's not that big a deal.
Let's cut the chit-chat and continue the training...
...is what I want to say, but let's review the basics first.
Forget all that! Hurry up and teach me a new technique!
Like the Ultra Super Deluxe Rasengan, or Naruto Special Uzumaki Rasengan?
That's why you're doing chakra nature manipulation training, remember?
The five basic elements are fire, wind, water, lightning and earth. And yours is-
I'm wind-natured!
Shall we continue from where you left off last time?
Yeah!
Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Thin and sharp!
I did it!
You like that, Kakashi-sensei?
Huh?
Sheesh...
Pushing himself like that when he's just recovered...
Plus, the mass shadow clones are to make the training more efficient.
There's no need to use it just to show off the results!
Well, that's our Naruto.
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
must be expressed with words.
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
to that blue, blue sky
aoi aoi ano sora
“Akatsuki” Invades
How deep in the mountains is this place?
Just a bit further.
You've been saying that the whole time!
Oh, are you kidding me?! More stairs?
There's no way the Jinchuuriki's way out here.
I'm getting pissed here!
Like I give a rat's ass about you.
And if you keep whining like a little baby,
I will kill you.
Yeah, yeah. Like you could pull it off, Kakuzu.
Inconsiderate prick.
Even if there are a lot of variables,
this is the best plan of attack given what we know right now.
Yes.
Have that compiled and ready to transmit in two to three days. Get going.
Understood.
Sorry to put you through all this trouble.
But we don't have time to be sitting around.
You awake?
Wha-? I... Not again...
Keep resting.
Overuse of mass shadow clones will tire you out easily, too.
We'll start the next level of training after you've rested a bit more.
What are we doing next?
Next?
The next step is...
Cut this waterfall.
Place your hands on the waterfall, and slice it in half using your wind chakra.
Cut it? The waterfall?
This exercise requires you to use nature manipulation on a large amount of chakra in an instant.
If you can't, you'll never cut the waterfall.
At the very least, clearing this stage means you'll be able to use wind chakra in real combat.
Kakashi-sensei!
If I can do this, I'll have mastered one chakra element, right?
All right! I'm improving!
A goof like Naruto... I never thought he'd
pick up nature manipulation this quickly.
This training method was perfect for him.
Break's over!
Time to start training again!
Mokuton no Jutsu!
That's where you'll be training.
Hold your horses.
What is it?
I already told you we need Yamato's chakra control for this training, didn't I?
I'm counting on you, Yamato.
Right.
S
i
t
We're all set, Naruto.
Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Picture the wind chakra...
Listen up. For wind, you picture your chakra splitting into two halves that rub against each other.
Rub against each other?
After they sharpen each other into thin, fine pieces, you rejoin them.
Thin and sharp... Like a blade?
Exactly. As thin and sharp as possible.
Thin and sharp.
Let's do it, guys!
Yeah!
Damn it! The water's barely splitting.
Keep going!
Right!
This is going to take a while, isn't it?
Yep. We'll have to be patient.
(Kanhou Pharmacy)
Now I've got all the ingredients.
Time to make the Sakura Special Soldier Pill!
I'm sure he's pushing himself too far in his training.
I mean, becoming strong through sheer guts just isn't the "in" thing these days!
Pushing yourself too hard not only puts stress on the body, but can actually make your skills worse.
And he's the type who tries harder than anyone else out there.
That's right...
I have to help him however I can!
God damn it!
Shit!
I think he's ready to see an example.
This is a temple.
You think he'd be here?
Dunno.
But this isn't your typical temple.
It's very likely that he's here.
What happened?!
Someone broke down the iron gate!
Report this to Chiriku-sama!
Doesn't look like anyone here'd be interested in converting to Jashin. Not a soul in sight!
Those cloaks! Then the rumors...
There's no mistaking it! They're Akatsuki!
Intruders!
Who are they?
They belong to Akatsuki!
I knew this day would come eventually.
I'll face them.
Everyone else will be my backup!
Looks like we've got another wannabe hero on our hands.
He doesn't just look the part.
Our hit list says there's a 30,000,000 ryou bounty on his head.
Hey, don't tell me we're after this guy for money.
Killing a priest is like a one-way ticket to hell.
Even hell runs on money.
I'd be fine.
I don't know what you want here, but leave now!
What, you don't want any unnecessary casualties?
Well, shit like that doesn't fly with my religion.
I'd heard there was a temple in the Fire Country inhabited by ninja monks.
It's said they wield some sort of power called "The Gift of the Gods."
The 30,000,000 ryou man is an elite ninja who once belonged to the 12 Guardian Ninja, charged with protecting the Feudal Lord.
That sash with the symbol of the Fire Country is proof.
So he's tough, or something?
Don't get lazy. You'll die.
Like it's even possible, Kakuzu!
What is that?
Who cares?!
Keep charging!
You're mine!
I'll give you a funeral.
Like I'd let myself be buried by some other religion.
Lord Jashin would smite me.
Now I'm pissed...
Yo, this fucker's not a Jinchuuriki, right?
Meaning I can follow the scriptures here?
Do as you like.
But his corpse is worth some real cash.
Make sure he's still recognizable when you're through with him.
People shouldn't be in the business of trading lives for money, asshole.
Kakuzu, don't interfere!
I'm gonna slaughter him!
I am Chiriku of Fire Temple, and I won't lose to the likes of you!
Raigou Senjusatsu!
(Raigou Senjusatsu: Amida's 1000-arm Death Embrace)
Looks like the Jinchuuriki wasn't here.
We'll hit the next spot after I finish praying.
No.
We need to exchange this corpse for the bounty.
Money comes first.
Seriously, can I beat the crap out of you someday? Just once?
I must inform Konoha!
Anyways, let's get going.
The Fire Country is huge.
We can take our time.
See? You're the reason we're always late!
Ow, fuck!
Hey, wait up!
Kakashi-sensei!
Don't I need more clones?
You won't be able to break the waterfall unless you generate large amounts of wind-natured chakra.
The more clones you make, the less chakra each one gets.
Besides, the waterfall's only wide enough for ten of you.
What? Who cares?
Then give me a tip so I can get better at this!
You're not keeping the chakra inside your body long enough.
Take your time and do it right.
But if I take too long, I won't be able to use it in a fight!
Look, you're training now.
You don't need to worry about actual combat.
You'll get faster as you get used to it.
But-!
You know, nature manipulating normally takes years.
Even cutting a leaf in half is supposed to take six months!
You managed it in just a few hours.
There's no need to rush.
You're advancing much faster than we expected.
When I taught Chidori to Sasuke, a true genius,
it took him several long days to get lightning element down.
I've gotta catch up to Sasuke!
Oh, boy.
Tenzou.
If you say so.
That was a bit much, huh?
No!
I'm completely...fine...
Way too much.
How's that, Naruto?
No complaints now?
Tajuu Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
iijiina riyuu
It's so very easy
issai yurusu jakuhai
for youth to forgive everything
resukyuutai mo yondeoita
I called in the rescue squad
dakara
So please kiss me, please kiss me all night
puriizu kisu mi puriizu kisu mi
datenshi no mahou ka koakuma no chachina itazura
Is it a fallen angel's magic, or a mischievous monster's prank?
tsumaranakunacchau mae ni
Before we get bored
soore de houre
Let's let go
bouringubooru
Of that bowling ball. We lead such strange lives
ibutsu na sonzai daro
shouchi no suke
You've gotta understand
kowaresoude...
We're gonna smash it...
docchirakatta kanjou de kirihirake yo
Cut through the inner turmoil
kowaresou de
We're gonna break...
kowasenai bokura no shouri
I can't break it...our victory.
Next Episode
The next episode of Naruto Shippuuden is: Beneath the Starry Sky!
Naruto continues training so that he can reach his goal.
All Sakura can do now is watch him.
Beneath the Starry Sky
Her feelings come together to form a single tear.
Let's try together!
Let's Try
Together!
Hello, everyone! Listen up!
Today we're going to try to do a technique together!
Fireball
nd Fireball
Grand Fireball
nt Grand Fireball
Element Grand Fireball
Fire Element Grand Fireball
It's the fire element technique, Grand Fireball!
Fire element Grand Fireball?
Very good!
The Grand Fireball is a basic ninjutsu taught in the Uchiha clan.
You change the chakra inside of you to fire and then spit out a large fireball.
It's Sasuke's specialty.
There are six necessary hand seals:
Snake, Ram, Monkey, Boar, Ox and Tiger.
Snake
There are six necessary hand seals:
Snake, Ram, Monkey, Boar, Ox and Tiger.
Snake
There are six necessary hand seals:
Snake, Ram, Monkey, Boar, Ox and Tiger.
Snake
Ram
Monkey
Boar
Ox
Tiger
It's a bit hard, so you may need to practice!
While quickly making the hand formations, build up the chakra inside of you.
After letting it build up in the back of your throat, you spit it out all at once.
So let's try it together now!
Snake
Snake!
Ram
Ram!
Monkey
Monkey!
Boar
Boar!
Ox
Ox!
Tiger
Tiger!
Building up your chakra and...
Spit it out all at once!
Even Sasuke wasn't very good when he first started!
Practice makes perfect!
So then, later!
Bye-bye!