What the...?
The resurrection technique is wearing off!
This means the other squads defeated the enemies, right?
Yeah, hopefully.
Then we can finally rest easy.
I wouldn't say that yet...
What?
We did it!
All their techniques have ended!
We kept Konoha safe!
No, according to Shikamaru's calculations,
this was all a diversion. It's too soon to be celebrating.
Now, what about the technique Konohamaru warned us about that could burn the village to the ground?
Didn't Yamato-san and Sakura head to Asuma-sensei's location?
Any word from Sakura?
None.
That's not good...
Shikamaru.
If the threat's still present,
shouldn't we be looking at the resurrection technique's ending as another trick, to lull us into a false sense of security?
We'll have to find Sakura and Yamato, or the enemies themselves, right?
That's right. Gather up a team and go investigate the village.
Understood.
Limelight.
Damn it!
The other three are in position.
Once Kitane reaches his, the village will-!
Sora!
Surpass your father! Crush him!
You have the power.
Power that you were chosen to have, not Kazuma!
Shut up!
Not the village, not Asuma!
Not your father!
That's right, not even your pathetic father!
If you insult my father again...
You'll do what?
I won't forgive you!
You won't forgive me?
So what?
My father never wanted this mindless slaughter!
I'll...
I'll stop you!
Slaughter...
Isn't that why you were born?
What?
What do you mean by that?
Have you seen your hand?
It looks just like a monster's!
Monster! Monster!
Monster...
You were finished so quickly, little boy.
How dare you...?
How dare you cut me?!
Damn...
I'll get you for this!
Shiki Tenshin!
(Shiki Tenshin: Color Change)
What the hell? Her wound healed just like that?!
Katon, Housenka no Jutsu!
(Katon, Housenka no Jutsu: Fire Element, Mythical Firebird Technique)
You're mine!
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Too slow!
Even if you make clones, I've got a lock on the real one.
A pointless diversion.
It's not a diversion...
The real me is the bait!
Rasengan!
I did it!
No, not yet...
What's with her?
What's going on?
How dare you do that to my body?
Not just once, but twice!
Shiki Tenshin!
You're not an average little boy.
Her wounds have all healed again. She's...
Suiton, Haran Banshou!
(Suiton, Haran Banshou: Water Element, Stormy Blockade)
Water...
Crap, after water comes....
Doton, Doro Houshi!
(Doton, Doro Houshi: Earth Element, Mud Spores)
Earth? She always uses lightning after water,
why...?
Wait a second, she was using lightning elements before I hit her with my Rasengan.
And once she healed her arm, water element.
I see! Then she must be-!
Are you switching bodies?!
That's how you can use all five elements!
Nothing will come of that knowledge.
Suiton, Ja no Kuchi!
(Suiton, Ja no Kuchi: Water Element, Mouth of Evil)
Shiki Tenshin!
Doton, Doro Houshi!
I can't allow anyone who knows my secret to live.
In exchange, I'll be taking your body.
Or you can die.
Kiss my ass!
I won't let you get away with this!
Enough of your bluffing!
Damn you!
Doton, Ganchuusou!
(Doton, Ganchuusou: Earth Element, Stone Spines)
How dare you mess up my hair?!
Damn you!
Sora...
Come to think of it,
your chakra is wind-natured, isn't it?
There aren't many people with wind nature, so I need to stock up...
Shikkei Seppun!
(Shikkei Seppun: Kiss of Death)
I'll make his vast reserves of chakra all mine!
Even though she changed bodies, the blood in her hair's still there.
What a weird ability...
Wait a sec...
What are you doing?
I finally figured it out.
I know the truth behind your technique!
Frickin'...
You little snot!
It was the same then, too!
You were more concerned with your hair than your body!
There must be something special about your hair!
Damn you...
You leave me no choice. I'll take your body!
I'll suck you dry!
Freakin'...
How dare you...?
The hell-?
Kage Bunshin!
Not this time!
Rasengan!
What a crazy bitch...
Sora, wait for me!
Fuuton, Suiran Reppu!
(Fuuton, Suiran Reppu: Wind Element, Verdant Mountain's Violent Wind)
Have you heard? About the real monster that attacked this village once, and almost completely annihilated it?
The nine-tailed demon fox.
Nine-tailed demon fox...?
There are different types of those monsters, called Bijuu.
We humans have sought their power since ancient times.
Specifically, to obtain the massive amounts of chakra each one holds.
The goal is obvious, of course.
To use them as weapons.
Those who had control of the Bijuu were on the top of the world.
Each country conducted various experiments and research, and finally found a way to control the Bijuu.
It's done by sealing them into human bodies.
People with Bijuu sealed in their bodies are called Jinchuuriki.
Each country scrambled to capture one and make their own Jinchuuriki.
And then we had a chance to obtain a Jinchuuriki here in Konoha, too.
It was fifteen years ago.
When the Kyuubi attacked Konoha,
the Fourth Hokage sealed it into a baby's stomach.
And Konoha had itself a Jinchuuriki.
Konoha's chance was our chance, as well.
We managed to harvest some of the chakra that the Kyuubi was leaking.
Of course, that power couldn't be sealed right away.
It took five years to implant it into a certain boy.
You mean...
Yes!
It's you, Sora!
You're a pseudo-Jinchuuriki!
How long...?
Even if you're not a true Jinchuuriki, you should have powers equal to a real one!
Since when?
Since the beginning.
You were born to bring death.
You're the weapon we made.
That's not...
You probably don't remember, but right after the chakra was sealed in you, you lost control and went berserk.
You even destroyed the Fire Temple's iron defensive walls.
I...
I was born for that?
To be alone, hated and ostracized?
To never to have friends?
Kitane...
The two kings?
What does a king really mean to us?
Asuma, do you know who the king represents?
Of course.
It's the Fire Country's Feudal Lord or the Hokage, yeah?
But I say we should only have one king to protect, Pops.
It seems you still don't get it.
I probably felt the same way as Kazuma back then.
I know.
I just couldn't go along with his plans.
Do you have your answer now?
I think so.
Then it's...all up to you.
A resurrection technique combined with earth element techniques?
Where's Sora?!
Come on, we've got work to do.
Business is about to pick up, for both of us.
The scent of earth...
It's coming from the north?
They got you, eh, Kitane?
That makes the other three useless now.
The Limelight plan failed.
Then, the village will be...?
Now that it's come to this, I'll have to force your hand.
I'll completely release the seal!
Release!
That's...
Sora!
Naruto!
The Third...?
Why're you here?
Am I dreaming?
I've been watching your actions as of late.
You've grown up from being a bratty little prankster.
I guess.
I'm glad to see that Konohamaru is doing well, also.
Though he's learned a rather strange technique thanks to your influence...
Well, it doesn't compare to my new technique...
What? Hayate-sensei?
Third, it's almost time.
What, already?
Going? Where?
Old man, your legs! Your legs!
I'll always be watching over you!
This is a dream... isn't it?
Come and visit my grave sometime! And be sure to bring Konohamaru with you! - The Third Hokage and Hayate
Visit... Grave...deh...buh...
Tsunade-sama!
The enemy's defensive barrier and resurrection techniques have ended, and the main gate area is almost back to normal.
And it seems that the enemy technique Asuma-san warned us of, that could've eradicated the entire village in an instant,
has been stopped as well.
I see.
What's that red light?
Sora!
Asuma-sensei, what's going on?
I don't know.
That's it, Sora!
Curse them, hate them!
Turn your rage into power!
We'll crush the damned Konoha scum!
We're going to kill every last one of them!
Screw you!
I wasn't born for this!
Yes, you were!
Everything exists to serve the true ruler of the Fire Country.
He needs your power now, Sora!
What the hell are you talking about, you son of a bitch!
You're...
Asuma!
Kazuma!
It can't be... You're...
Asuma-sensei, do you know this guy?
Yeah. He used to be a fellow ninja of the Twelve Guardians.
You... What the hell did you do to Sora?!
I just had him take some of your overflow.
What'd you say?
Sora is the same as you.
Stop it!
Sora!
Naruto!
What is this...incredible pain?
Am I really...? Am I the Kyuubi?
How did you do this to Sora?
You know a whole lot more about when the Kyuubi attacked Konoha than I do.
Back then, at the cost of his own life,
the Fourth Hokage sealed the Kyuubi within a baby.
Konoha had finally gotten its hands on the Kyuubi.
We didn't let that chance slip by us.
We gathered up the remnants of Kyuubi's chakra leftover from its rampage.
We cultivated it and placed it inside of Sora five years later.
You...
Sora's your own-
So what?
Konoha gained an incredible power that day, as did we.
All for the sake of protecting our respective kings.
What's wrong with that?!
Naruto...
I could tell.
Yeah. I knew it right away...
But I... I just...
That... That was Sora's voice screaming out!
Why didn't I notice?
Why didn't I sense his pain, and his screams,
when I was the only one who could ever understand!
Just like at the Fire Temple.
All of those eyes looking at Sora.
Cold eyes, filled with hate.
It's like they were saying, "Get the hell out of here!"
Why couldn't I tell that he was going through the same thing I did?!
They were the same eyes as the ones I'd always endured.
Naruto...
Your eyes are just like the countless others that looked at me like I shouldn't even be there!
Your eyes are the exact same as theirs!
Like I care about that now.
Those are the eyes!
Those are the eyes that look at us like we're monsters!
Those are the eyes that made us feel all alone!
That say you're trying to use us for your own gains!
Gaara went through the same thing.
What's wrong with you adults?
You don't even try to understand how we feel.
And Sora is... Sora is...
Why'd you have to put this monster inside of him?!
Why?! Why did you do this to Sora?!
Shut up.
Naruto!
Sora!
Stay away!
Everyone stay back!
I'm not messing around! I'm not gonna let anyone fool me anymore!
You killed my dad, but talked to me like nothing had ever happened.
And your "special power" bullshit! You tricked me!
Sora!
I said to stay back!
And you... You're from Konoha!
I can't trust you, either!
What the...?
What is this?
Sora has a demon fox's cloak?
Don't tell me that you merged the Kyuubi's cells with Sora's?!
That's...
What the hell is going on?
Unlike the real Jinchuuriki over there, the Kyuubi's chakra was too great for Sora's body to handle.
So for the past ten years I've been using sealing techniques to keep the Kyuubi's chakra under control.
But now that I've released its chakra, that delicate balance has been destroyed, and eventually it will take control of Sora's body.
When all nine tails have formed, Sora will become the Kyuubi itself!
And the pseudo-Kyuubi will become the real thing!
You bastard!
Fine. I'll hand my body over to that damned fox!
Sora!
In exchange, I want to destroy this world!
Stop it, Sora!
Mokuton, Mokujou Heki!
(Mokuton, Mokujou Heki: Wood Element, Locking Wood Wall)
Naruto!
Sakura-chan!
Asuma-san!
Captain Yamato!
That red light from earlier was...
That's...the Kyuubi!
There's no doubt about it. That's the demon fox's cloak.
That's...Sora.
What did you say?!
That's it, Sora!
More! Show us even more of your power!
Stop it, Sora! Don't use its power!
Shut up!
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Naruto!
You're late, Shikamaru!
You're sure it's this way?
Don't underestimate my and Akamaru's noses!
It isn't just Sora. Naruto and Asuma-sensei are there, too.
I can also smell someone else who isn't from the village.
The enemy, huh?
What could that be?
Naruto!
Are you okay, Naruto?
That was a close call.
You're so pathetic!
I'm your opponent, Kazuma.
Damn you!
Hey, Captain Yamato. Can't you suppress the Kyuubi's chakra, like you did with me?
I was able to suppress the Kyuubi's chakra in you because you were wearing the First's necklace.
Without the necklace, it won't work on Sora!
Sora!
So that's it, huh? Am I that big of a nuisance?!
You don't need me, do you?! Huh?!
That's not it, Sora!
We just don't want you to use that power!
This power is a part of me.
It's the only thing that I can trust now!
Sora...
I'm going to get revenge on everyone who made me feel like I was all alone!
Naruto!
I hate this power.
I hate hurting others.
I hurt Sakura-chan once.
The one who hurt Sakura...
...was you, Naruto.
If you continue to rely on the Kyuubi's power,
you'll only hurt yourself, as well as your friends.
That's why...
That's why I don't want you to use that power to hurt someone!
Like you could know what I'm going through!
I know exactly what you're going through!
The source of the Kyuubi's energy that he merged with you is sealed within me.
What are you saying?
I'm a Jinchuuriki.
There's... You're lying!
Sora...
Stay back!
What you said...
You...
...aren't fooling me!
Shadow Mimic technique, successful.
Shikamaru, Chouji!
Ino!
They're here!
Damn it! More of your friends, huh?!
Do your thing, Chouji!
Bubun Baika no Jutsu!
Both hands!
Damn you!
We did it!
He's not going anywhere now.
This makes no sense...
If the real Kyuubi is sealed inside of you, why do you have so many friends?!
I was always on my own.
So why...?
Why...?
Why do you have...?
I was the same as you.
When I was a kid, I was always on my own.
The thing is, I never wasted any time feeling lonely.
I wanted to force everyone to acknowledge me.
And these are the people who finally became my friends.
I don't have friends like you-
Aren't all of us your friends?
Ouch...
Chouji!
Ino...
I'm on it!
Ninpou, Shintenshin no Jutsu!
(Ninpou, Shintenshin no Jutsu: Ninja Art, Mind-Body Switch Technique)
Did you get him?
What happened, Ino?!
Are you okay?
Ino, what happened to your Mind-Body Switch?!
There's no sign of a human heart left inside of him.
What?!
And I've about hit my limit.
Oh, no! The third tail's formed!
Captain Yamato, Naruto looks a bit strange!
That's...
Don't tell me his Kyuubi's chakra is leaking out again!
No way!
I can't believe he's going berserk at a time like this!
Why's it doing that? Naruto's wearing the First Hokage's necklace!
It's reacting differently than it normally does!
Damn it! What's going on?!
I can't believe my technique isn't working on him at all!
Next time: Resonance.
It's time for the 4th Konoha Super Quiz!
We've got a new set for this game!
I'm your host, Yamato!
And I'm basically here to spice things up.
I'm his assistant, Sakura!
Today's question comes from the Sasuke Retrieval Arc!
The four people who snuck into Konoha to get Sasuke-kun were...
The Sound-
Four!
And!
Huh?
Among them was a stout man who could absorb chakra through Earth-based techniques...
Jiroubou!
And!
There was a girl who controlled the raging ogres with her demonic flute...
Tayuya.
And!
Finally, there was the Sound Ninja who had six arms!
Hey, who fought him?
I think it was...
It was Neji.
Man, I bet all those arms made the animators cry.
Time's up!
The correct answer is Kidoumaru!
By the way, he's supposedly very skilled at cat's cradle.
Who cares?!
Right now, he's...
The episode's about to end!