Everything seems fine.
Okay, we'll discharge you today.
Is it because you want me to get rid
of the extra "baggage" over there?
That was a factor.
Naruto. He's been holed up here the whole time,
saying that his training could start any minute!
I thought I'd have a few days to be
lazy...err, recover at my own house,
but I'm completely out of books to read,
so we might as well get his training going.
Yeah.
Rasen-!
Wake the hell up, Naruto!
Ugly whore...
The hell?!
Sakura-chan?!
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You've yet to learn what sadness is
Kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And are just now grasping what pain is like
Setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even the feelings I have for you
Anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
ima kotoba ni kawatteku
must be expressed with words.
As you awake from a dream into an unknown world,
Michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Spread your wings, and take flight!
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
You say if you could fly, you'd never come back down
Habataitara
modorenai to itte
You only have eyes for that blue, blue sky
Mezashita no wa
aoi aoi ano sora
You know if you can just make it through, you'll find what you seek
Tsuki nuketara
mitsukaru to shitte
so keep trying to break free,
Furikiru hodo
aoi aoi ano sora
to that blue, blue sky
Wind
All right, let's get started.
What?
It's just, it's like, you haven't trained me in so long...
I dunno why, but this makes me happy!
I see.
Well, if you want to laugh, now's your only chance.
Because we're really short on time.
Like I said at the hospital, the aim of our training
is for you to create your own ultimate ninjutsu.
One that even surpasses Rasengan.
Chakra nature and shape manipulation are essential to this process.
Shape and nature manipulation?
Ah, yes, you won't get it if I explain both at the same time.
Sensei is sorry.
We'll start with shape manipulation.
Yes, sir!
Do a Rasengan.
Coming right up!
Let's do it!
Okay!
Rasengan!
Okay, stop.
You've already mastered chakra shape manipulation.
That's what your Rasengan is.
Rasengan is...?
You rotate your raw chakra wildly at
extreme speeds, and compress the energy.
That is shape manipulation itself, which you
could say Rasengan takes to the ultimate level.
So I've passed shape manipulation, then?
That's right.
All right!
Okay, the next step is chakra nature manipulation.
Let's see...
Take Chidori.
This technique uses both shape and nature
manipulation at the same time. Watch carefully.
I'll focus chakra into my right hand...
And change its nature into an electric current.
That's nature manipulation?
That's right.
Next, I change its shape to that of a power
surge, which determines the power and range.
To create a technique more advanced than your usual Rasengan,
you need to use both shape and nature manipulation
at the same time, like I do with Chidori.
So if I use that nature-thingy on Rasengan,
I'll have a new technique in no time!
Don't take this so lightly. You have no idea
how to use nature manipulation, for starters.
Actually, you don't even know which element you have an affinity for.
Element-what?
I figured I'd have to explain this...
There are only five basic types of chakra elemental natures.
Fire
They are fire, wind, water, lightning and earth.
Wind
Fire
Water
Wind
Lightning
Water
Earth
Lightning
The Five Great Shinobi Nations are named for these elements,
and they form the foundation of all ninjutsu.
Oh... Cool...
Most people's chakra naturally leans toward a certain element.
For example, the Uchiha were geared towards fire, thus,
they were exceptionally skilled in fire element techniques.
For wind, it's wind element. Lightning is lightning element.
Chidori is a lightning element technique.
So Sasuke's got fire and lightning natures, then?
Yeah, and you currently have zero.
You don't even know which elemental nature you're most suited to.
What're those?
We'll find out your nature with these slips of paper.
How?
If you're lightning-natured, the paper will wrinkle.
It'll tear in half for wind.
Burn if you're fire.
Get soggy if you're water.
And crumble if you're earth.
It's a unique paper that reacts to even the slightest amount of chakra,
made from special trees fed and nurtured with chakra.
If you run your chakra through this paper,
we'll find out which nature you have.
All right...
Your chakra's nature is wind.
Wind?
Wind can slice anything to bits.
A chakra that's perfectly suited for battle.
Damn, I am so awesome!
Not yet, you're not. We only just found this out.
Your manipulation training starts now.
Yes, sir!
It usually takes a huge amount of time to learn the method.
But, I've thought of a way to get it done extremely fast.
Sweet!
What we'll do is-
Captain Yamato!
Hey, why are you here?
Kakashi-san asked me to help with your training.
Sorry to interrupt, Kakashi-senpai.
No problem. So-
Hey, hey, what kind of nature manipulation is your wood element?
Well, that's...
He's focused on you now, just show him.
Well then!
Doton, Doryuu Jouheki!
(Doton, Doryuu Jouheki: Earth Element, Earth Rampart)
Wh-What?
Suiton, Takitsubo no Jutsu!
(Suiton, Takitsubo no Jutsu: Water Element, Waterfall Basin Technique)
He made a waterfall...
I use two elements, earth and water.
So you have two as well, Captain Yamato?
By the time they're a jounin-class ninja, most people can use at least two types.
I can use more than just lightning, too.
Then with the wood element, Captain Yamato has three?
No, not exactly.
I can only use earth and water.
Wood isn't one of the basic elements.
Then, how did he...?
He uses them simultaneously.
By using earth and water natures at the
same time, he creates a new element, wood.
Earth in my right hand, water in my left.
Amazing...
When you can perform multiple kinds of nature
manipulation, it's pretty easy to use them separately.
But using two at the same time and combining them?
Earth
Water
But using two at the same time and combining them?
That's another story.
Using two elemental natures at the same time to
create a new nature is called a Bloodline Limit.
I know you've heard that phrase before.
That boy Haku you fought had the same ability.
He had a bloodline limit that I'd call "Ice Element",
but he was actually combining water and wind to create ice.
Bloodline Limits are genetic. Only his
clan could perform that technique.
Haku, too...
That's why I couldn't copy it with my Sharingan.
Then what about Shikamaru's Shadow
Mimic, or Chouji's Multi-Size techniques?
And medical ninjutsu and genjutsu? How do those work?
Explaining all that will take more time,
and you won't get it even if I do.
Kakashi-senpai, why not save explanation
on light and dark manipulations for later?
Light and dark?
Say what?
Good call.
Trust me, you wouldn't understand a word of it.
Now where was I?
How to make the training take no time?
I said take less time...
Yeah, yeah, that!
How do we do it?
We use...
...your Mass Shadow Clones.
That's it, your Mass Shadow Clones.
It's what?
Like I said, it's how you're going to do your
training in an extremely short period of time.
I don't get it at all.
I'm going to explain it now then, so listen carefully.
Yes, sir! Please explain it as simply as possible, sir!
Right, right.
Listen up.
Normal Clones
You already know that unlike the normal clone technique,
the Shadow Clone technique makes real, physical clones, correct?
Normal Clones
Shadow Clones
the Shadow Clone technique makes real, physical clones, correct?
Yeah! Of course I know that!
In other words, the technique makes a complete copy of the user.
Although not to the same extent as you, I can also use shadow clones,
so I know about the special side-effect this technique has on the user.
Since you use it constantly, you've probably noticed...
Huh?
When you release the technique, any experience
and knowledge gained by the clones...
...will transfer back to the user's original body.
I told you to make it simple!
So you haven't noticed, eh?
No, I don't get what you're saying!
Let's both make a shadow clone, then.
Just one.
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Okay! Now the originals and the shadow
clones are going to separate into two groups.
The clones will go hide in the woods over there.
Naruto's clone, come with me.
Okay!
The originals can't see us shadow clones through these woods.
So, the two of us are going to play rock, paper, scissors.
Why?
Just do it.
Hey, wait! Just normal old rock, paper, scissors isn't any fun!
I don't care if it isn't fun!
So then, how about, whoever loses has
to treat the winner to Ichiraku Ramen!
All right, fine!
Hell yeah! Now I'm pumped up!
Rock, paper-
What are our shadow clones doing?
You'll find out soon enough.
Sweet! I win! Kakashi-sensei has to treat me to dinner!
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, now we both have to release the technique and vanish.
Right!
What did they do?
Kakashi-sensei has to treat me to Ichiraku Ramen,
because I beat you at rock, paper, scissors!
You forced that bet on me!
But now you understand, right?
Anything a shadow clone learns or
experiences goes back to the original body.
I see.
I use the technique all the time, I guess I just never noticed until now.
This technique was originally used for recon missions in dangerous areas, infiltrating enemy bases, and information gathering.
Okay, great, so how exactly is this related
to shortening my training time?
Yeah, yeah. I'll explain that, too.
Yay!
Jiraiya-sama, how the hell did you ever teach this
kid a technique like Rasengan? Unbelievable...
Hurry! Hurry!
If you and one clone go through the exact same training,
then you end up getting twice the benefit from it.
To put it another way,
If you and a clone do the same training, you
accomplish the same amount in half the time.
If there are three of you, you can do it in a third of the time.
Three... In a third the time...
If there's 1,000 of you, you can get it
done in one one-thousandth of the time.
Now I get it.
Something that would take two days by yourself
would only take one with a clone alongside you.
With a thousand clones, something that would
normally take you twenty years would take a week.
Awesome!
So that's what you had up your sleeve!
He finally gets it!
You're to have as many clones as possible working with
you at all times during your nature manipulation training.
Okay!
Now I know why you're so strong, Kakashi-sensei!
You've been training like this all your life, huh?
Actually, I've never once trained like this.
Huh? Why not? You can use shadow clones, too!
This is true.
Like I said, I don't have your stamina or as much chakra
as you, so I can't maintain the technique for very long.
Since it splits the chakra evenly across the clones,
ninja with low chakra capacities, like
me, can't use it to its full potential.
Really?
So I have more chakra than you, Kakashi-sensei?
You have about four times as much as me.
That much?!
Man, I really am awesome!
If we don't suppress the Kyuubi's chakra, then
you'd have about 100 times as much as me.
Kyuubi's chakra...
That's why you're the only one who can handle this kind of training.
But since you're going to be using up a lot of chakra,
there's a chance that you might awaken the Kyuubi.
That's why I'm here.
I'm here to control the Kyuubi's chakra.
The one who hurt Sakura was you, Naruto.
I'm counting on you!
The first step is to strengthen your control over your chakra element.
Yeah!
Hold a leaf between your two hands and cut it with just your chakra.
All the way through.
Okay! Let's do this!
As I've already said, I want you to do
this training using shadow clones.
How many should I make?
Well, if each one of you gets a single leaf...
About that many.
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
He's already starting to cut them?
This may go faster than I thought.
Kodomo no koro mita niji wo
If I look up now for the rainbow I saw as a boy,
ima miageru to nana iro de wa naku
there are no longer the seven colors,
Yagate kiri ga kakari
only mist and fog...
Jikan wa sugi kawatte yuku
As time passes by, and the world around me changes,
Kimi wo sagashitemo doko ni mo inai
no matter where I search for you, you're nowhere to be found.
Me wo toji, kokoro hiraite
So I close my eyes, and open my heart...
mata nagamete mitemo nanimo kawaranai no ka
I need to know, if I gaze up again,
tashikamete mitai
will things be different this time?
Sunao ni narereba kono kiri ga hareru to
Maybe if I was more honest, the fog would fade away.
kokoro ni negai sou sakenderu
So I pray, screaming that wish deep within my soul.
Nanika wo nakushiteshimatta koto de sou
When you lose one thing,
te ni shita mono mo kitto arun darou
you gain another, don't you?
Dakedo mada bokura wa otona ni tomadoi
But still, no matter how often the adults confuse us,
ikite yuku sube sagashiteru
we'll keep looking for the right way to live our lives.
Next Episode
The next episode of Naruto Shippuuden is "Squirm".
A town by the country's border is suddenly attacked.
This is merely the prelude to a huge
problem that will involve the entire village.
Squirm